<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Evil Tactician's RimWorld Tweaks</name>
	<author>Evil Tactician</author>
	<packageId>ETRT.RimWorldTweaks</packageId>	
	<supportedVersions>
	  <li>1.3</li>
	  <li>1.4</li>	  
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
	  <li>
		<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
		<displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
		<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
		<downloadUrl>https://github.com/AndroidQuazar/VanillaExpandedFramework</downloadUrl>
	  </li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>		
		<li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
		<li>spoonshortage.fashionrimsta</li>
		<li>leafzxg.MasterOfCooking</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VIEHAR</li>		
	</loadAfter>	
	<description>A set of tweaks and additions which enhance the vanilla experience.

&lt;size=20&gt;Evil Tactician's RimWorld Tweaks&lt;/size&gt;

You can disable any of these tweaks in the mod settings for Vanilla Expanded Framework, which is used to enable all of these changes to be toggable.

&lt;b&gt;Medicine Production&lt;/b&gt;
- Adds research projects for Neutroamine, Luciferium and Glitterworld Medicine crafting.
- Neutroamine combining 4 Psychoid leaves and 1 herbal medicine. (Req. 10 Medical skill)
- Luciferium combining 30 Psychoid leaves, 1 Plasteel and 3 Neutramine. (Req. 12 Medical skill)
- 4 Glitterworld Medicine combining 4 Neutroamine, 1 Luciferium and 4 Medicine. (Req. 14 Medical skill)
- Included Bulk Recipes to Craft Medicine, Luciferium and Neutroamine in stacks of 4.

&lt;b&gt;Industrial Tweaks&lt;/b&gt;
- Smelting steel slags now gives 50 steel. (up from 20)
- Refine 10 Plasteel from 50 Steel and 15 Chemfuel at a smelter.

&lt;b&gt;Kibble Bulk Production&lt;/b&gt;
- Craft Kibble in stacks of 4.

&lt;b&gt;Power Usage Tweaks&lt;/b&gt;
- Standard Lamp from 30 to 15.
- Autodoor from 50 to 25.
- Sun Lamp from 2900 to 1100. You can now power 1 Sunlamp with 1 Water Mill Generator.
- Vanometric Cell from 1000 to 1500.

&lt;b&gt;Room Size Tweaks&lt;/b&gt;
- Room sizes more reasonable across the board.
- Now brought in line with other mods which do the same.

&lt;b&gt;Tribal Apparel&lt;/b&gt;
- Added Fur Coat, Fur Hat, Desert Robe and Desert Head Wrap for Tribals in harsh conditions.
- Textures (with permission) from &lt;b&gt;spoonshortage's&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;FashionRIMsta&lt;/b&gt; mod.
- Compatible with FashionRIMsta if you want to use the full set, just load my mod &lt;i&gt;after&lt;/i&gt; hers.
- Added Wolf Hood, Deer Hood, Megascarab Hood, Megaspider Hood and Spelopede Helm.
- Each have subtle bonuses for specific roles within the tribe to add some variety early game.
- Textures (with permission) from &lt;b&gt;Diana Kitty's&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Tribal Hoods&lt;/b&gt; mod.
- NEW: If you own Ideology, the tribal apparal can be picked when creating your Ideoligion.

&lt;b&gt;NEW: Anima Tree Tweaks&lt;/b&gt;
- Ability to Minify and Move the Anima Tree.

&lt;b&gt;NEW: Hay Tweak&lt;/b&gt;
- Hay will no longer spoil, but it will deteriorate when not roofed.

&lt;b&gt;NEW: Royalty Hoods Tweak&lt;/b&gt;
- Embroidered Hood which satisfies noble requirements.
- Royalty Prestige Helmets have scaling Social and Negotiation Bonuses.

&lt;b&gt;NEW: Muffalo Milk&lt;/b&gt;
- Muffalo's can be milked again as it used to be in the past.

&lt;b&gt;NEW: Practical Pemmican&lt;/b&gt;
- 1 Pemmican counts as 1 portion, no more crafting or eating batches of 16 Pemmican.
- Recipes and values tweaked accordingly, entirely vanilla friendly!

&lt;b&gt;NEW: Sow Grass&lt;/b&gt;
- Sow grass in growing zones. Useful in Animal Pens!

&lt;size=20&gt;What is this all about?&lt;/size&gt;
This mod was created to suit my personal preferences. There are other mods which do similar things for many of the listed tweaks. Most of them either didn't quite do it the way I would prefer, and luckily RimWorld let's you change pretty much anything you want. 

Whilst this mod should be compatible with most other mods, there is no point having two mods which modify the exact same thing. 
In fact, this mod potentially eliminates the need for quite a few other mods in your list - be sensible and you will be fine.

Of course, if you do prefer the tweaks in another mod - simply place that mod below this one (or vice versa). The lowest mod in your load order 'wins' and overwrites the other for those specific changes only.

&lt;size=20&gt;Credits&lt;/size&gt;
&lt;color=orange&gt;spoonshortage&lt;/color&gt; - Tribal Apparel Textures.
&lt;color=orange&gt;Diana (Kitty)&lt;/color&gt; - Tribal Hoods Textures.
	</description>
</ModMetaData>