<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
	<QuestPrefix>Quest</QuestPrefix>

	<Quest_RequiredItems>Requested resources</Quest_RequiredItems>
	<Quest_HelpItems_Site>Resource delivery site.</Quest_HelpItems_Site>
	<HowToCheckReqList>To view a list of required items, open detailed information.</HowToCheckReqList>
	<HelpResourcesDescriptionTitle>Faction {0} requested resources. We need to send a caravan with the necessary supplies to this point in order to deliver them.

List of required resources:</HelpResourcesDescriptionTitle>
	<GiveItemsSuccessTitle>Resources delivered.</GiveItemsSuccessTitle>
	<GiveItemsSuccess>You have successfully delivered the requested resources. The reward was sent to your base via cargo pods.</GiveItemsSuccess>
	<GiveItemsSuccess2>You have successfully delievered the resources. The award was given to your caravan.</GiveItemsSuccess2>
	<NotEnoughItemsToQuest>Not enough items</NotEnoughItemsToQuest>
	<GiveItemsOption>Deliver resources</GiveItemsOption>
	
	<Quest_HelpItems_Label>Request for resources</Quest_HelpItems_Label>
	<Quest_HelpItems_Description>The leader of the {0} faction contacts you and tells you that they are going to expand their settlement, but they don’t have enough available resources. They request some resources from you and in exchange they will give what supplies they have in abundance. \nWe can form a caravan with the necessary items and send it to them.
</Quest_HelpItems_Description>

	<HowToGivePawns>To assist the settlement, send a caravan with the required number of pawns ({0}) to the construction site. \nConstruction time: {1}</HowToGivePawns>
	<Quest_BuildNewBase_Label>Construction of a new settlement</Quest_BuildNewBase_Label>
	<Quest_BuildNewBase_Description>The faction {0} is requesting aid in moving one of their settlements. They explain that their current location has run low on natural resources and poor soil fertility has rendered is unsustainable. They have enough supplies stockpiled, but do not have enough capable construction workers and request that you send assistance. \n\nConstruction may take several days and during this time your colonists will be unavailable. Upon completion of construction you will be rewarded and your colonists will be returned.
</Quest_BuildNewBase_Description>
	<Quest_BuildNewBase_Place>Construction site {0}</Quest_BuildNewBase_Place>
	<NotEnoughPawnsToHelp>Not enough colonistss in the caravan</NotEnoughPawnsToHelp>
	<HelpStartedTitle>Construction started</HelpStartedTitle>
	<HelpStarted>Your caravan has arrived at the construction site of the new settlement. According to preliminary calculations, construction will take {0} days, after which your colonists will be returned.</HelpStarted>
	<BuildingAlreadyStarted>Construction has already begun</BuildingAlreadyStarted>
	<Quest_HelpWithBuilding_Option>To help</Quest_HelpWithBuilding_Option>
	<PawnsRequired>Pawns required: {0}</PawnsRequired>
	<BuildingSeccessEndTitle>Construction completed</BuildingSeccessEndTitle>
	<BuildingSeccessEnd>Construction of the settlement for {0} is over. They are grateful and inform you that they will be willing to return the favor by providing supplies or military aid. (You can make requests through the Geoscape)
</BuildingSeccessEnd>

	<Quest_AttackFriendlySettlement_CardLabel>Attack on a friendly settlement</Quest_AttackFriendlySettlement_CardLabel>
	<Quest_AttackFriendlySettlement_Description>The leader of the {0} allied faction {1} reports that their scouts have spotted an approaching enemy raid on their settlement. They explain that most of their fighters are away on a classified mission and request combat assistance. \nIf you help them repel this attack, they will be able to provide you with intelligence information from time to time. \n\nTo help repel the attack, form a caravan with everything you need and head to the rally point on the map. \nThe reward depends on the number of surviving settlers of the allied settlement.
</Quest_AttackFriendlySettlement_Description>
	<ScoutComp_GiveTitle>Intelligence agreement</ScoutComp_GiveTitle>
	<ScoutComp_Give>You have signed an intelligence agreement with the {0} faction. They will provide intelligence data every {1} days for {2} days that may contain information about imminent threats, but warn that it may not always be completely accurate.</ScoutComp_Give>
	<ScoutComp_AlreadyGiveTitle>Intelligence agreement</ScoutComp_AlreadyGiveTitle>
	<ScoutComp_AlreadyGive>An intelligence agreement with faction {0} has already been signed, so it has been extended for {1} days.</ScoutComp_AlreadyGive>
	
	<Quest_MissingPeople_CardLabel>Missing settlers</Quest_MissingPeople_CardLabel>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_Description>The leader of the faction {0} contacted us and reported that a small group of their settlers went on a journey to gather resources but has not returned. Their journey was estimated to take {1} days, but more than {2} days have already passed. Attempts to get in touch have failed and they are worried that the settlers might have gotten lost or been attacked. \nThey should enough food for about {3} days, after which they will starve. He asks us to find the missing settlers and return them home.</Quest_MissingPeople_Description>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_PlaceLabel>Potential Settlers Place</Quest_MissingPeople_PlaceLabel>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_PlaceLabelSaved>People destination</Quest_MissingPeople_PlaceLabelSaved>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_InspectString>Potential place for lost settlers. \nFood will run out in: {0} (days)</Quest_MissingPeople_InspectString>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_InspectString2>House of missing settlers. \nTime to deliver settlers: {0} (days)</Quest_MissingPeople_InspectString2>
	<Quest_CheckMissingPeople_Action>Inspect the place</Quest_CheckMissingPeople_Action>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_CheckFailTitle>Nothing found</Quest_MissingPeople_CheckFailTitle>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_CheckFail>We've find signs of the missing settlers, but nobody is here. There are fresh tracks leading away from the site, we should follow them. (A new destination is marked on the map)</Quest_MissingPeople_CheckFail>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_EnterToMapTitle>Missing settlers</Quest_MissingPeople_EnterToMapTitle>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_EnterToMap>Entering the territory we quickly spot the small camp of missing settlers. They are weak, but not ready to give up. While preparing to leave, a group of hostiles appear on the horizon. We will have to fight our way out and protect the settlers we came to rescue.</Quest_MissingPeople_EnterToMap>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_Stage2Title>Caravan formed and ready to move</Quest_MissingPeople_Stage2Title>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_Stage2>We were able to repel the attack, now we must escort the settlers home within {0} days. If we do not deliver them in time, we will be condemned as scavenging thieves taking advantage of the situation. (Take the caravan to the marked settlement base)</Quest_MissingPeople_Stage2>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_End>You arrived at the Allied settlement.\n</Quest_MissingPeople_End>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_EndFull>\nYou managed to bring all the settlers alive, for which the faction {0} is very grateful to you.</Quest_MissingPeople_EndFull>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_EndPart>\nYou tell the story of what difficulties you faced, that those who died did not do so in vain and the rest should be proud of them.</Quest_MissingPeople_EndPart>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_Fiasko>\nYou came with nothing but excuses. The leader of the {0} faction is very upset. You try to explain, but with nothing to show for it they simply shake their head and walk away.</Quest_MissingPeople_Fiasko>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_EndQuest>Quest result</Quest_MissingPeople_EndQuest>
	<Quest_CheckMissingPeople_Action2>Transfer settlers</Quest_CheckMissingPeople_Action2>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_ThiefTitle>Prosecution</Quest_MissingPeople_ThiefTitle>
	<Quest_MissingPeople_Thief>You did not return the surviving settlers in time, those that were rescued left you to return on their own. They told their leader about this and he accused you of harboring the settlers against their will. The agreement between you has been broken.</Quest_MissingPeople_Thief>

	<Quest_TradeRequestComp_CardLabel>Trade request</Quest_TradeRequestComp_CardLabel>
	<Quest_BanditCamp_CardLabel>Bandit camp</Quest_BanditCamp_CardLabel>
	
	<Quest_KillLeader_CardLabel>Order to kill an enemy leader</Quest_KillLeader_CardLabel>
	<Quest_KillLeader_Description>{0} talks about the enemy leader-dictator {1} from faction {2}, who has made threats against their settlement and asks you to eliminate them. Your target's location is marked on the world map.
News of an assassination attempt will not stay secret for long and will spread quickly, you must strike soon.</Quest_KillLeader_Description>
	<Quest_KillLeader_PlaceLabel>Target location</Quest_KillLeader_PlaceLabel>
	
	<Quest_SuppressionRebellion_CardLabel>Suppression of insurgency</Quest_SuppressionRebellion_CardLabel>
	<Quest_SuppressionRebellion_Description>The faction {0} has problems with rebellion from within. The insurgents demand independence and have commited reckless and volent acts for their cause, resulting in civilian fatalities. The soldiers of {0} faction were able to push them from the settlement, but they are gaining strength and will attack again.
We can help suppress insurgency or stand aside and let the conflict resolve itself. In the end, if the rebels win, a new faction will be formed.</Quest_SuppressionRebellion_Description>
	<Quest_SuppressionRebellion_PlaceLabel>The location of the insurgents</Quest_SuppressionRebellion_PlaceLabel>
	<Quest_SuppressionRebellion_Dia>You have entered the territory. In the distance you see a group of insurgents preparing to attack.

You can complete the quest in two ways.

You can do kill all the insurgents. In this case, you can salvage whatever supplies are lef tin the camp.
Or you can try to incapacitate as many as possible, they are still under the jurisdiction of the {0} faction. You will be rewarded for doing so.

In any case, the task will be considered successful.</Quest_SuppressionRebellion_Dia>
	<Quest_SuppressionRebellionFailTitle>Suppression of the insurgency failed</Quest_SuppressionRebellionFailTitle>
	<Quest_SuppressionRebellionDesc>The attempt to suppress the insurgency was unsuccessful and they were able to defeat you.
They will have already gone to attempt their coup, the outcome is no longer in your hands.</Quest_SuppressionRebellionDesc>
	<Quest_SuppressionRebellionWinTitle>Victory</Quest_SuppressionRebellionWinTitle>
	<Quest_SuppressionRebellionWinDesc>You were able to defeat the insurgents and spared the lives of {0} of them, for which the {1} faction decided to add another {2} silver to your reward.
--------------
{3}</Quest_SuppressionRebellionWinDesc>
	<Quest_SuppressionRebellionRebelWinTitle>The insurgents won</Quest_SuppressionRebellionRebelWinTitle>
	<Quest_SuppressionRebellionRebelWinDesc>The insurgents were able to defeat the soldiers from the settlement {0}. {1}
This led to a change of leadership and a new political regime has taken over.</Quest_SuppressionRebellionRebelWinDesc>
	<Quest_SuppressionRebelplayerAffect>The insurgents will remember that your settlement tried to stop them, because of that your relationship has worsened.</Quest_SuppressionRebelplayerAffect>
	<Quest_SuppressionRebelNonplayerAffect>Your settlement did not participate in this.</Quest_SuppressionRebelNonplayerAffect>
	<Quest_SuppressionRebellionNewFactionTitle>The insurgents lost</Quest_SuppressionRebellionNewFactionTitle>
	<Quest_SuppressionRebellionNewFactionDesc>The rebels could not defeat the {0}, the rebellious survivors formed their own splinter faction and called themselves {1}</Quest_SuppressionRebellionNewFactionDesc>
	<CaravanArrivalAction_EnterToRebelMap_AlreadyStart>The insurgency has already begun</CaravanArrivalAction_EnterToRebelMap_AlreadyStart>

	<Quest_KillOrder_CardLabel>Kill order</Quest_KillOrder_CardLabel>
	<Quest_KillOrder_Description>{0} requests to eliminate {1} from {2} faction for silver. He marked the target's location on the world map.</Quest_KillOrder_Description>
	<Quest_KillOrder_PlaceLabel>Target location</Quest_KillOrder_PlaceLabel>

	
</LanguageData>