<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>Wealthy Traders Forked</name>
	<author>Tziirh</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.5</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>Tziirh.WealthyTradersForked</packageId>
	<description>Wealthy Traders. More silver and more stuff. Forked edition

Original mod by TRP
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2031752213
This mod may be removed anytime if requested by the original author.


A continuation of the Wealthy Traders mod by TRP as their latest update was for Rimworld 1.1.

Been playing around with this a bit more. It should now support clients with and without Royalty and patch the added traders automatically
Traders seem to work as expected. 
I have yet to craft Speedskin but I can see it is a craft option. Unsure why this was originally included but some seem to like it. May update to match the current version of Glitter Tech at some point or see if it’s changed at least.
Please report issues in the comments

New Changes
Should detect and Patch Traders from:
	-	Royalty Expansion
	-	Expanded Prosthetics and Organ Engineering (EPOE)
	-	Sparkling Worlds (Full)
None of the above Expansions or mods are required, this should only apply IF they are loaded.
If there are any other common mods with traders that you would like me to add to this list, please add in the comments and I’ll look into it

Key points as from original: 
All traders have increased variety and quantity of goods e.g., more clothes types plus more of each item
Orbital traders silver increased to roughly 60k-140k
Caravans silver increased to roughly 4k-12k
Added - Orbital tradertype The Liquidator, buys it all, but only offers gold to buy.
Added - Craftable speed skin suit and fibreskin suit*
Added - Textile Trader**


* speedskin suit and fibreskin suit are part of the Glitter Tech mod. This mod just expands on that and made it craftable.
http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=725576127 
** Textile trader is part of the OPOE mod.
http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=725956940
	</description>	
 
     <loadAfter>
		<li>Albion.SparklingWorlds.Full</li>
		<li>vat.epoeforked</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VGeneticsE</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VFE.Vikings</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VFE.Insectoid</li>
		<li>Dubwise.Rimatomics</li>
		<li>QX.AstraMilitarum</li>
		<li>Aelanna.EccentricTech.Core</li>
		<li>ludeon.rimworld.biotech</li>
		<li>Phonicmas.40kFactions</li>
		<!-- New -->
		<li>Cabbage.RimCities</li>
    </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>