<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>Red Wolves</name>
    <author>Pausbrak</author>
    <url>https://github.com/RadHazard/RimworldRedWolves</url>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.0</li>
        <li>1.1</li>
        <li>1.2</li>
        <li>1.3</li>
        <li>1.4</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>tachyonite.pawnmorpher</li>
        <li>tachyonite.pawnmorpherpublic</li>
        <li>Owlchemist.AnimalGear.Equipment</li>
    </loadAfter>
    <packageId>pausbrak.redwolves</packageId>
    <description>&lt;size=24&gt;Red Wolves&lt;/size&gt;

Red wolves on the Rim!  Enjoy these timid, elusive canines in a future where they're no longer endangered.

A smaller, more timid species of wolf, known for their russet color and warbling call. Originally native to the old Earth continent of North America, they were once driven to extinction in the 21st century following a long history of human persecution. In the mid 22nd century, they become one of the first extinct species to be restored with cloning from only DNA samples. Today they can be found on many planets all over human-settled space, having made a recovery far above and beyond what any conservationist could have ever hoped for.

They pose somewhat less of a threat than their grey wolf cousins, but make up for it with +20% adorableness. They're quite shy and hard to tame, but should you find yourself a red wolf companion they will make an amazing, loyal friend and/or hauling animal (you monster)

&lt;size=24&gt;Recommended Mods&lt;/size&gt;

- Animal Variety Coats
    (1.0) Without this, you'll only get red wolves with the original pelt color. Get this to have all the variations!
    (1.1+) No longer required as of 1.1 or above, but still recommended!

&lt;size=24&gt;Mods With Integrations&lt;/size&gt;

- Pawnmorpher
  - Adds a red wolf morph with custom mutations
- Animal Gear &amp; Animal Equipment
  - Cute wolf sweaters, armor, and more!


&lt;size=24&gt;Other Supported Mods&lt;/size&gt;

- Combat Extended
- A Dog Said

&lt;size=24&gt;Save the Red Wolf&lt;/size&gt;

The backstory above doesn't need to be the real future of the red wolf! These elusive canines are extremely endanged, with only a dozen or so left in the wild. Their future may look grim, but they don't have to disappear off the face of the Earth. Hundreds of conservation organizations, public and private, are cooperating to give these wolves a future right now.

I personally know of and support the Wolf Conservation Center of New York, which has done amazing work with their captive breeding program.  However, they're just one of many organizations across the country working to save red wolves. These organizations can always use more volunteers, donations, or even just word-of-mouth support. Don't let cloning become the only way to save these wolves!</description>
</ModMetaData>
