<Defs>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>AvP_Concept_Gauntlet</defName>
    <label>AvP: Gauntlet</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>Basic Equipment taken into the field by almost all Yautja when hunting.\n\nThe most basic version of the gauntlet only contains a Wristblade and Self Destruct Device. The gauntlet can only be removed by the wearer.\n\nIt can be upgraded via reseach to also contain the MediComp, Shard Injector and Cloaking Device.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>  
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>AvP_Concept_Wistblade</defName>
    <label>AvP: Gauntlet - Wristblade</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>One of the most Iconic peices of Yautja equipment, it is rare indeed to see a hunter without one.\n\nWhile the Hunter Gauntlet is equipped, the wearer gains an extra melee attack.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>  
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>AvP_Concept_SelfDestruct</defName>
    <label>AvP: Gauntlet - Self Destruct</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>Yautja will go to extreme lengths to prevent their technology being scavenged by 'lesser' races, this device is one of the most extreme solutions.\n\nThe Device has two modes, a ten second timer and an instant trigger.\n\nThe timer button acts as a toggle, so you can disarm it by clicking it again.\n\n WARNING!! There is No safty on the instant detonation trigger!.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>  
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>AvP_Concept_MediComp</defName>
    <label>AvP: Gauntlet - MediComp</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>The MediComp upgrade to the gauntlet allows the wearer to tend to their own wounds in the field.\n\nThe tend quaility is the same as herbal medice.\n\nAn unlimited number of wounds can be tended.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>  
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>AvP_Concept_ShardInjector</defName>
    <label>AvP: Gauntlet - Health Shards</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>The Shard Injector upgrade to the gauntlet allows for the storage and self-administration of a maximum of three Health Shards.\n\nWhen used, a Health Shard heals one of the worst untended wounds on the pawn, but it will not replace lost or destroyed parts.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>  
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>AvP_Concept_Cloak</defName>
    <label>AvP: Gauntlet - Cloaking Device</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>One of the most well known and coveted peices of Yautja technology, Active Optical Camouflage bends light around the user rendering them invisible.\n\nHowever it can be disrupted by the wearer taking sufficent damage and rain can give away the wearers position.\n\n Rain and water Disruption planned but not yet implemented.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>  
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>AvP_Concept_Plasmacaster</defName>
    <label>AvP: Plasmacaster</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>Another iconic peice of Yautja technology the plasmacaster offers a hands free ranged weapon.\n\nWhen active it will automaticlly target enemies in range, prioritizing the wearers target.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>  
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>AvP_Concept_SmartDisk</defName>
    <label>AvP: Smart Disk</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>The Smart Disc, also known as the Smart Weapon, Cutting Disk or simply the Disc, is a primarily thrown Yautja weapon.\n\nIt is an extremely sharp circular cutting device that is typically thrown like a discus and yet returns to the user like a boomerang. It also features a hand grip for use as a melee slashing weapon</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>  
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>AvP_Concept_CombiStaff</defName>
    <label>AvP: Combistaff</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>Combistaffs are Yautja Melee weapons that can be thrown at a target to pin it in place.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>  
  
 </Defs>  