<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
 
  <ColdFusionReactor.label>Cold fusion reactor</ColdFusionReactor.label>
  <ColdFusionReactor.description>A reactor operating with uranium, but based on the principle of cold fusion. Generates a good amount energy with producing much heat waste while being more stable than a standard nuclear reactor.</ColdFusionReactor.description>
  <ColdFusionReactorHeath.label>Cold fusion reactor core</ColdFusionReactorHeath.label>
  <ColdFusionReactorHeath.description>The main part of the cold fusion reactor. With it, it will be possible to modify a nuclear reactor in order to obtain a much more efficient and stable source of energy.</ColdFusionReactorHeath.description>
  <MiniColdFusionReactor.label>Minified cold fusion reactor</MiniColdFusionReactor.label>
  <MiniColdFusionReactor.description>Mini cold fusion reactor. Still effective, but takes up much less space, so it can be used in a wider range of objects.</MiniColdFusionReactor.description>
  <MiniArcReactor.label>Minified arc reactor</MiniArcReactor.label>
  <MiniArcReactor.description>Smaller form arc reactor. A modified cold fusion reactor that is even more efficient.</MiniArcReactor.description>

  <Mk1PowerStation.label>MK1 power station</Mk1PowerStation.label>
  <Mk1PowerStation.description>Charging and production station to create MK1 Power Armor</Mk1PowerStation.description>

  <ArcReactor.label>Arc reactor</ArcReactor.label>
  <ArcReactor.description>A reactor operating with uranium, but based on the principle of cold fusion. Emits almost no waste heat, but is a good source of energy.</ArcReactor.description>
  <PalladiumCore.label>Palladium core</PalladiumCore.label>
  <PalladiumCore.description>The main source of energy. Despite the radioactivity, the design of the reactor keeps it safely contained.</PalladiumCore.description>
  <Enricher.label>Enricher</Enricher.label>
  <Enricher.description>Stimulates the core by bombarding it with charged particles, enhancing the generation of energy.</Enricher.description>
  
  <ZeroPointReactor.label>Zero point reactor</ZeroPointReactor.label>
  <ZeroPointReactor.description>A reactor built upon incomprehensible technology. These generators extract usable energy from the vacuum between matter particles, providing an almost unlimited supply of power.</ZeroPointReactor.description>
  <VacuumTube.label>Vacuum tube</VacuumTube.label>
  <VacuumTube.description>The main part of the reactor, it generates energy.</VacuumTube.description>
  <VacuumStabilizer.label>Vacuum stabilizer</VacuumStabilizer.label>
  <VacuumStabilizer.description>Stabilizes pressure, creates zero electromagnetic radiation.</VacuumStabilizer.description>
  <VacuumPump.label>Vacuum pump</VacuumPump.label>
  <VacuumPump.description>A pump used to control the level of oxygen and its composition in the room down to the atom. It is an important component for the operation of the zero point reactor.</VacuumPump.description>
  
  <SingularReactor.label>Singularity reactor</SingularReactor.label>
  <SingularReactor.description>A reactor where microscopic black holes are used to generate energy. The reactor harvests the Hawking radiation released from the black holes and converts it directly into usable energy.</SingularReactor.description>
  <SuperMagnetNewGeneration.label>Super Magnet Suspender</SuperMagnetNewGeneration.label>
  <SuperMagnetNewGeneration.description>A portable super magnet that allows the physical transfer of microscopic black holes. Try not to drop it.</SuperMagnetNewGeneration.description>
  <QuantumConverter.label>Quantum converter</QuantumConverter.label>
  <QuantumConverter.description>The main component that harvests radiation from the evaporation of a black hole and converts it into energy.</QuantumConverter.description>
  
  <Catapult.label>Medieval Catapult</Catapult.label>
  <Catapult.description>A massive launcher that uses a large lever that uses stone balls as projectiles. The stone balls shatter on impact, dispersing rock shrapnel nearby to cause further damage.</Catapult.description>
  <Artillery_Catapult.label>Medieval Catapult</Artillery_Catapult.label>
  <Artillery_Catapult.description>A massive launcher that uses a large lever that uses stone balls as projectiles. The stone balls shatter on impact, dispersing rock shrapnel nearby to cause further damage.</Artillery_Catapult.description>
  <BigBalls.label>Stone big ball</BigBalls.label>
  <BigBalls.description>A massive stone ball designed for catapults.</BigBalls.description>  
  
  <Ballista.label>Medieval ballista</Ballista.label>
  <Ballista.description>A massive weapon that uses huge arrows as projectiles. Slow, but devasating.</Ballista.description>
  <Artillery_Ballista.label>Medieval ballista</Artillery_Ballista.label>
  <Artillery_Ballista.description>A massive weapon that uses huge arrows as projectiles. Slow, but devestating.</Artillery_Ballista.description>
  <BigArrows.label>Ballista Bolt</BigArrows.label>
  <BigArrows.description>A giant arrow made from stone and steel intended for a ballista.</BigArrows.description>  
  
</LanguageData>