<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
  <!--STARTUP DIALOG TRANSLATIONS-->

  <!--Update Dialog-->
  <NewUpdate>Congrats! RimRadio: Remade has been updated! You can view the changelog on Steam (https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/changelog/2299591546) or on the repository (https://gitlab.com/KuroNekoTNG/RimRadio/blob/master/CHANGELOG.md or https://gitlab.com/KuroNekoTNG/RimRadio/-/tags).\n-KuroNeko Kyubi Felis</NewUpdate>
  <NewUpdateTitle>OwO *Notices I've been update.*</NewUpdateTitle>
  <ContinueButton>Continue</ContinueButton>
  
  <!--FFmpeg Gone Dialog-->
  <FFmpegGone>FFmpeg is gone, to some it might seem disappointing. Nevertheless, I do have a good reason for it. FFmpeg is an external dependency/program, and to avoid risking the users to download from a potentially sketchy website, I have decided to remove it. Feight not though, I have a good replacement. Mpeg 3, or more commonly known as mp3, is one of the most common audio file types out there. It just so happens that the NAudio group also has a fully managed version of their Mpeg Layer 1, 2, and 3 decoder. This means that it does not rely on Windows (in the case of NAudio) to decode mp3's. So you Linux/macOS/Unix users out there can rejoice!\nAlso, audio streaming! Audio is now streamed instead of loaded all into memory, which will lower that memory footprint on the system, allowing for even more mods to be used! There's no need to think me, just loving to program and reduce size of a program.</FFmpegGone>
  <FFmpegGoneTitle>UwU *Notices FFmpeg Support Gone*</FFmpegGoneTitle>
  
  <!--Backend Choose Dialog-->
  <NAudioLoaded>NAudio has been detected. NAudio is a well known .NET to Media Foundation. However, for cross-platform support, NLayer is also loaded. Which do you prefer to use for the backend?\nNAudio:\n	Uses Windows to decode Mpeg 3 files.\n	Supports other audio formats like.\nNLayer:\n	Uses Managed (usually a bit slower) code to decode Mpeg 3 files.\n	Only supports Mpeg Layer 1, 2, and 3.\n	Makes for a portable configuration if you only use MP3's.\n\n\n\nFor info on what NAudio supports, see https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/win32/medfound/supported-media-formats-in-media-foundation for a list of audio files.</NAudioLoaded>
  <NAudioLoadedTitle>OwO *Notices NAudio*</NAudioLoadedTitle>
  <UseNAudio>NAudio backend</UseNAudio>
  <UseNLayer>NLayer backend</UseNLayer>

  <LoadingRuntimeStations>Loading Runtime Stations</LoadingRuntimeStations>
  
  <!--SETTINGS DIALOG TRANSLATIONS-->

  <!--Clearing the cache dialog messages.-->
  <ClearCacheMessage>Do you wish to clear the RimRadio: Remade cache? Doing so will restart the game, so it is recommended to do this if RimRadio: Remade is not playing songs correctly.</ClearCacheMessage>
  <ClearCacheOk>Clear Cache</ClearCacheOk>
  <ClearCacheStop>Don't Clear Cache</ClearCacheStop>
  <ClearCacheTitle>Clear RimRadio: Remade Cache?</ClearCacheTitle>
  <ClearCache>Clear RimRadio: Remade Cache</ClearCache>

  <!--This is for the restart dialog.-->
  <RestartQuestion>All of the settings have been reset, however Runtime Stations have not updated to reflect this change. Would you like to restart the game now?</RestartQuestion>
  <RestartOk>Restart Now</RestartOk>
  <RestartNo>Restart Later</RestartNo>
  <RestartTitle>NOT ALL CHANGES HAVE BEEN REFLECTED</RestartTitle>

  <!--This is for the long event queue.-->
  <CreateCache>Checking/Creating Music Cache (may take awhile)</CreateCache>
  <VerifyRuntime>Verifying and Building Runtime Station(s)</VerifyRuntime>
  <LoadingRuntimeStations>Loading Runtime Station(s) and Music Cache to memory</LoadingRuntimeStations>
</LanguageData>
