<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>TradeHelper</name>
  <author>TimmyLiang</author>
  <packageId>TimmyLiang.TradeHelper</packageId>
  <supportedVersions>
	  <li>1.1</li><li>1.2</li><li>1.3</li><li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <description>Trade Helper is a small tool which expands the Trading Dialog and helps you trade in RimWorld. This includes:
- A Wish list: a configurable list of desired items, when a trader holds any matched items, these items will be clearly highlighted so you won't miss what you seek (especially handy when you are targeting certain goods).
- Items to be bought: clearly displays the items you are buying.
- Items to be sold: clearly displays the items you are selling (minimise the risk selling the wrong item).
- Slightly enhanced the Trading Dialog (mouse hover highlights etc).
- Enhanced the Caravan Dialog so it has similar features to the Trading dialog (updated 2020/06/02).

Compatability:
- Should work with most MODs as this only tweaks the Trading/Caravan UI;
- Work with existing saves;
- Requires Harmony.
- This Mod assumes your screen resolution is wider than 1300px as it adds 300px side space to the Trading/Caravan Dialogs.

Updates:
- 2020/06/03: fixed a small display issue.
- 2020/06/06: fixed a mod conflict.
- 2020/08/15: now supports v1.2 (not tested with Royalty though).
- 2020/08/16: fixed a conflict with mod RimThemes.
- 2021/07/31: now supports v1.3 (not tested with DLC as I don't have).
- 2022/10/22: now supports v1.4 (not tested with DLC as I don't have).

Trade Helper是一个稍稍优化交易窗口的小工具。它的功能包括：
- 愿望单：可配置的愿望清单，当商人持有你愿望单中的物品时，该物品整行会高亮显示。
- 购入物品栏：清晰地显示你准备买入的物品。
- 卖出物品栏：清晰地显示你准备卖出的物品（再也不会忘掉把人皮沙发卖掉啦！）。
- 稍微优化了交易窗口，例如增加了鼠标悬停高亮等。
- 优化了远行窗口，现在远行窗口拥有和交易窗口类似的功能（2020/06/02更新）。

兼容性：
- 由于只是稍调整了交易和远行窗口的显示方式，所以应该可以兼容绝大部分Mod。
- 旧档可兼容，不需要开新档。
- 需要Harmony。
- 由于在交易和远行窗口增加了侧边栏，所以本Mod需要玩家屏幕的分辨率至少达到1300像素宽。

更新：
- 2020/06/03: 修正了一个显示问题。
- 2020/06/06: 修正了一个Mod冲突问题。
- 2020/08/15: 支持1.2版本（但尚未针对Royalty版本测试过）。
- 2020/08/16: 修正了与RimThemes的Mod冲突问题。
- 2021/07/31: 支持1.3版本（但因为我没有DLC，所以尚未针对DLC测试）。
- 2022/10/22: 支持1.4版本（但因为我没有DLC，所以尚未针对DLC测试）。</description>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>