<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>Friendly Fire Tweaks</name>
    <author>Alex</author>
    <url>https://github.com/RSAlxander/Rimworld-Mods</url>
    <packageId>Alex.FriendlyFireTweaks</packageId>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.0</li>
        <li>1.1</li>
        <li>1.2</li>
        <li>1.3</li>
        <li>1.4</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    </loadAfter>
    <description>Changes how friendly fire works in Rimworld, mostly by removing it.
        Works for both the player, and the AI, though I have no idea if raiders or visitors can even shoot each other in the back. Includes most mod added weapons and turrets. You can still target friendly things manually. Explosions are still not safe.

        Safe to add to or remove from games in progress.

        Config options.
        - Shooting skill affects friendly fire chance, or just disable it all together. No more will your ‘Legendary Master’ sniper kill your front line fighters for the 13th time.
        - Customize that amount each shooting level decreases the likelihood of friendly fire. Want to make it so at level 10 your pawns stop shooting each other? You can do that now.

        You can decide exactly what can and can’t be accidentally shot as each option can be toggled separately. So if you want to protect just animals, or just the walls of your killbox you can.
        - Pawns, yep.
        - Animals, no more dead attack squirrels.
        - Buildings, stop breaking your killbox walls.
        - Mineable Stones/Resources, no longer worry about bringing down the roof of the mountain just because you missed a few hundred shots at the infestation currently destroying your rec room, again.</description>
</ModMetaData>