<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<Defs>

	<ThingDef ParentName="BodyPartArtificialBase">
		<defName>MM_ThermalLance_ThermalCore</defName>
		<label>thermal core</label>
		<description>A cybernetic heart made by fusing mechanoid technology with living tissue. The only known source of these organs is to harvest them from the polar colossi that inhabit some RimWorlds. In addition to being a slight improvement over a natural human heart, it generates a grat deal of heat and can interface with the thermal lance assembly.</description>
		<statBases>
			<MarketValue>2800</MarketValue>
			<Mass>1</Mass>
		</statBases>
		<graphicData>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Health/HealthItemArchotech</texPath>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<drawSize>0.80</drawSize>
		</graphicData>
	</ThingDef>
	
	<ThingDef ParentName="BodyPartArtificialBase">
		<defName>MM_ThermalLance_OpticalTargetingSystem</defName>
		<label>optical targeting system</label>
		<description>A cybernetic eye made by fusing mechanoid technology with living tissue. The only known source of these organs is to harvest them from the polar colossi that inhabit some RimWorlds. While only slightly better than a natural eye, it also provides significant aiming, tracking and targeting information, ideal for any shooter.</description>
		<statBases>
			<MarketValue>2800</MarketValue>
			<Mass>1</Mass>
		</statBases>
		<graphicData>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Health/HealthItemArchotech</texPath>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<drawSize>0.80</drawSize>
		</graphicData>
	</ThingDef>
	
	<ThingDef ParentName="BodyPartArtificialBase">
		<defName>MM_ThermalLance_FiringAssembly</defName>
		<label>thermal lance firing assembly</label>
		<description>A cybernetic jaw made by fusing mechanoid technology with living tissue. The only known source of these organs is to harvest them from the polar colossi that inhabit some RimWorlds. In addition to functioning as a normal jaw, the thermal lance firing assembly allows for the cration, direction and release of a concentrated blast of thermal energy. It's effectiveness is somewhat limited by the size of the creature it is adapted to fit.</description>
		<statBases>
			<MarketValue>2800</MarketValue>
			<Mass>1</Mass>
		</statBases>
		<graphicData>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Health/HealthItemArchotech</texPath>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<drawSize>0.80</drawSize>
		</graphicData>
	</ThingDef>

</Defs>