<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>Load NPC Ideos in Dev Mode (Legacy)</name>
	<author>GearheadLydia</author>
	<url></url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<packageId>GearheadLydia.IdeoLoadDev</packageId>
	<description>(Outdated for game versions subsequent to 1.3.3117: this mod's purpose is now core functionality.)
	
Adds a simple load button in the vanilla location for NPC ideoligions. Uses the vanilla load methods to the greatest extent possible, in an attempt to make sure IDs are regenerated and to avoid game errors. Own faction load button should still use vanilla methods.

Global game dev mode must be enabled for the button to show up.

Unlike the old version, there is absolutely nothing stopping you from loading identical ideoligions into every single available slot. Doing so is probably not wise, but I'm not even sure it'd technically break anything if you did.

This is my first Rimworld C# / HarmonyLib injection mod; please give me every bit of code feedback you can.

Thanks to Kentington for the original mod; I did look at that as a reference, but this was a clean-sheet rewrite using different methodology, and (as far as I'm aware) none of Kentington's code made it into this mod. This should be compatible with the Kentington mod, though use of both at once is redundant.

Known bug: icons don't show up right at first. Opening the edit symbols dialog and immediately clicking "Done" should fix it.

Permission is pre-emptively granted to fork or otherwise continue this mod if it becomes outdated.
	</description>
</ModMetaData>