<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>

	<name>[RF] Advanced Bridges Continued [1.0+]</name>
	<author>Rainbeau Flambe - troopersmith1</author>
	<url>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=46165</url>
	<supportedVersions>
	<li>1.0</li>
	<li>1.1</li>
	<li>1.2</li>
	<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>Troopersmith1.AdvancedBridges1.1</packageId>
	<description>(Last update: 12/05/2018)

"Advanced Bridges," as the name so subtly suggests, allows you to build bridges which are, well, a bit more advanced than those available in vanilla RimWorld. (Well, technically, you could also create piers or even a boardwalk. It's really up to you.) All you need is wood, stone or metal. And a bit of extra steel for reinforcement if you're building over deep water. (Yes, this mod allows you to build bridges over deep water as well as over shallow water.)

Light bridges (built from wood) require no special research, and support light construction, so you can, for example, use a light bridge to run a power conduit across a river. Heavy bridges (those built from stone or metal) do require research, but will support heavy construction, so you can actually place walls on them.

NOTE: "Advanced Bridges" does not disable construction of default vanilla bridges, so you can actually use both types of bridges on your maps if you so desire. But you won't be able to build vanilla bridges over deep river water, and won't be able to place walls over them. (In other words, they'll function just like the mod's light bridges.)

- Rainbeau Flambe (dburgdorf)

=====

Compatibility:

"Advanced Bridges" can safely be added to a game in progress, but if you try to remove it from a game in which you've actually built any bridges, you will of course make the map unplayable.

The mod should be compatible with any mods that add additional water tiles to the game, so long as those mods have assigned the "bridgeable" affordance to those water tiles.

There seem to be some issues when using "Advanced Bridges" together with Jec's "Doors Expanded." I haven't tracked down the cause yet, but if a boardwalk or bridge is built under a large door or gate, the door will (not always, but sometimes) stop working properly. Doors seem to work fine if built on top of existing bridges or boardwalks, though, so if you must build a large door on top of a bridge or boardwalk, make sure to place the bridge or boardwalk first. But to be perfectly safe, try to avoid putting such doors on bridges or boardwalks at all.

If you want to be able to catch fish from your bridges, you'll need to utilize an additional mod to add that capability. Obviously, I'd recommend my own "Fishing," though it's not the only option.

IMPORTANT NOTE: If you remove bridge tiles with dev tools, or "minify" them to move them (which isn't possible in vanilla, but might be thanks to other mods), you will end up with problematic "pseudo" terrain tiles on your map where the bridges used to be. Please don't do this! If you need to remove a bridge tile, deconstruct it properly!

=====

Credits:

The code in "Advanced Bridges" borrows a bit from Sulusdacor's "[sd] Bridges" mod. And obviously, the mods are very similar on a conceptual level.

The traditional Chinese language files were provided by Steam user Alane. The simplified Chinese language translation files were provided by Steam user kghostSATORI. The Japanese language files were provided by Proxyer.

=====

License:

If you're a modpack maker and want to include "Advanced Bridges" in your pack, or if you're a modder and want to use it as the basis of a derivative mod, please feel free to do so. I ask only that you let me know about it. 

=====

If you have any (helpful) suggestions for improvement, please let me know!

	</description>
	
	<loadAfter>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.MedievalModule</li>
	</loadAfter>

</ModMetaData>
