<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Vanilla Fishing Expanded - Xtra Fish</name>
	<author>Lorsieab2</author>
	<supportedVersions>
	<li>1.2</li>
	<li>1.3</li>
	<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>V1.0
    This simple XML mod adds more types of fish you can catch! Featuring hand-drawn graphics by me :) Disclaimer: This is my first mod, so there might be some bugs/typos that slipped through the cracks. Please give me your feedback/criticism/mod ideas in the comments! 
	
	I made this mod because I felt that there was something missing from VFE. I liked catching shellfish from Rainbeau Flambe's Fishing Re-Work and FishIndustry so I decided to add them here. IDK if I'll add any seafood recipes - would be great but it's a lot of work for me. (Modding noob LOL)
	
	Permissions:
	Feel free to make your own version/expansion of this mod (with your own graphics please). In fact, please do! I'd love to see more catchable fish for Vanilla Fishing Expanded and more uses for them besides food :D (Caviar and fish leather anyone? What about more seafood recipes??) 
	You're allowed to update this mod but please credit me!
	You're not allowed to steal my art for your own mods without crediting me.
	
	Compatibility:
	Definitely works on 1.4. Untested on 1.2 and 1.3
	Unless VFE changes drastically this mod should still work on future Rimworld versions.
	Should be compatible with everything
	
	Changelog: 
	Removed "Unnecessary Stuff.rar" (aka my attempts at making the mod work)
	
	References I used to code this mod:
	Oskar Potocki and Sarg Bjornson for Vanilla Fishing Expanded and its Treasures Addon
	SkillerDankOP for Vanilla Fishing Expanded - Shrimp Addon (Your mod was super helpful for fixing errors in my XML - Thank you!)
    Other Credits:
	Rainbeau Flambe, Si-Cafe and Mlie for [RF] Fising Re-work (Continued)
	Si-Cafe for [RF] Fishing-ReWork Seafood and Sushi Addon
	Zaljerem for [RF] Fishing Recipes
	Rikiki for FishIndustry
	
		</description>
		<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>VanillaExpanded.VCEF</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Fishing Expanded</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=1914064942</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/Vanilla-Expanded/VanillaFishingExpanded</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
		<packageId>VanillaExpanded.VCEFXtraFish</packageId>
	<loadAfter>
	   <li>VanillaExpanded.VCEF</li>
    </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>