<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Marro</name>
  <author>Zot!</author>
   <packageId>zot.marro</packageId>
   <supportedVersions><li>1.2</li></supportedVersions>
  <description>This is a mod that adds a new alien race, the Marro.
  
Marro are a alien race made up of hives. These hives contain multiple sub-races such as the worker drones, the warriors, the overlords, and at the top of the hives, the hivelords. The drones aren't very powerful in combat but are hard workers. Warriors are about equal to humans in combat but aren't very good workers. Overlords are stronger than humans in combat but aren't great workers. Hivelords are very powerful in combat but most aren't useful for basic labor types.
The Marro can also create alien creatures that obey them.

The Marro are unique because they can all be crafted at a special workstation. They can be crafted from a special resource called Marroflesh. This resource can be grown from a new plant. The Marro can even craft weapons and animals from this resource.

You grow the Marro from Marro Larvae which are crafted. To mature they require high temperatures in excess of 25 degrees.

This Mod is a work in progress and has many more features that I hope to add in the future including more creatures and subraces as well as some fun events. It probably also isn't the most balanced right now, but I am working on it.
  
This Mod is based on the Marro race from the board game Heroscape. 
  
Thanks to the Humanoid Alien race discord for the help and SargBjornson for his open license on his C# code in genetic rim (https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=35158.0).
  </description>
  	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
			<displayName>Humanoid Alien Races 2.0</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		  <li>
			<packageId>jecrell.jecstools</packageId>
			<displayName>JecsTools</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=932008009</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://discord.gg/AaVFA7V</downloadUrl>
		  </li>
	</modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>