<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
  <packageId>Sielfyr.ImprovedMeditation</packageId>
  <name>Meditation</name>
  <author>Sielfyr</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <description>
  
Many nice stuff to make meditation more fleshed out like a meditation spot, some small bonus effect on meditation, a meditation breakdown and some others things.
Those stuff have low impact except on pawn who are incredibly good at meditating !
  


You can add this mod to an existing save, all pawn will get a random meditation skill value.
I don't advice to remove this Mod from a save who use it but if you still want to do it you should clear the meditation effect(hediff) and breakdown first, the meditation furniture and skill can disappear with a non game breaking error.



Some possible future change :
  - skygaze can use a meditative cushion 
  - meditation in bed less effective
  - pawn can still chose to meditate in bedroom even if there no spot in that room
  
  
  
A list of what this mod add : 
  
  
  - a meditation spot and a meditation cushion ( in the furniture tab ) :
	* it design spot where you pawn can meditate 
	* pawn can still meditate in their bedroom if there no dedicated spot 
	* pawn favor more comfortable spot that in a meditation room or in their bedroom
	
  - a meditation room if the room contains a meditation item : 
	* low priority over another room type 
	* room don't count wealth in impressiveness calculation
	
  - a meditation skill :
	* mainly increase while meditating and slowly throughout other meditative activity
	* it determine the chance to meditate ( pain also increase the chance to meditate )
	* it increase meditation effect
	* it increase meditation breakdown chance over another breakdown
	* when skill levelup the passion can increase
	
  - meditation effect :
	* effect increase while meditating and decade over time doing something else
	* reduce pain
	* reduce hunger rate
	* reduce figth chance
	* increase healing speed (low)
	* increase immunity rate (low)
	
  - a meditation breakdown :
	* it make pawn to meditate for a long time
	* pawn with high meditation value will have higher chance to have this breakdown
	* the breakdown is considered for any breakdown intensity (minor - major - extreme)
	
  - possibility to force meditation :
	* can be done on meditation item
	* a pawn can only perform it above a minimal meditation skill 
	
	
  </description>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
        <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
        <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
        <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
</modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>