<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
		<modNameReadable>Children, school and learning</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>Children</modIdentifier>
		<defName>Children_1_6_3_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.6.3.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
		 &lt;b&gt;Changes:&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- New config-table for per species settings&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;color=silver&gt;Some of the existing and some of the new options can be configured per species in this new table.&lt;/color&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] The number of children in one birth can be influenced per species. (This is a multiplier for the normal amount that the species itself has configured)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] A trait that is added on birth can be configured for the species.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] Draw- and part-scaling for AlienRaces can also be influenced!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] Some previously hard-coded settings for certain species are now in here by default.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- New config-table for custom hybrid species&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;color=silver&gt;With an enabled and matching entry for both parents, a hybrid species can be born. (see the info text in the table-header)&lt;/color&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] This was previously only hard-coded for orassan:nekos and lotr:half-elves.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] There is also a new option to show the species('Show species') that is likely to be born from a pregnancy, which is quite helpful when messing around with the new table.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- New config-table for medical conditions(hediffs) to be inherited&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;color=silver&gt;(see the info text in the table-header and options)&lt;/color&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- New color mixing options, which should add a bit more variation to children.&lt;/b&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] I would recommend: '50/50 + slight variation', it is on '50/50 exactly' by default, as this is how it was before&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- New option to prioritize traits, if both parents have them.&lt;/b&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] It is recommended to also look into one of the mods that lets colonists have more traits, as they are pretty limited by default&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- New option 'retry birth on issue' which should be able to preserve the pregnancy in case a mod messes with a successful birth.&lt;/b&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] Default:on(!) It tries to determine if a child was created. As I did not have the issue myself, it remains a bit experimental.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- New option to enable a partner dialog when using the medical operation for pregnancies.&lt;/b&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] only when using glitter-medicine!.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- New option to block addictions for younger children.&lt;/b&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] Default:on(!) when under 5 can be turned off when set to 0 years.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- New option to always show miscarriages, regardless if the pregnancy is visible.&lt;/b&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] Default:on(!) to avoid confusion.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- New (experimental) option to hide items related to children or related to school.&lt;/b&gt;
		|
		|- Performance has been improved for a couple of functions that get called very often like drawing AlienRace addons or need_Food.
		|
		|- The number of children should now always be based on the child-species.
		|
		|- Info: for those who asked about skill-passions changing etc. I have seen this mod: 'Gain Skill Passions' 
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;It does currently not restrict the changes to a life-stage/age, but maybe that is something that can be requested as an option.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
		|
		|img:images/newsPa
		|caption:&lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;Should have used these update-news sooner ^^&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
		<modNameReadable>Children, school and learning</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>Children</modIdentifier>
		<defName>Children_1_7_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.7.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
		 &lt;b&gt;School rework:&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- Changed: There is now no longer a hard requirement for the teacher being present to avoid some schedule issues.&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- New: Each blackboard can now have a schedule and changes its tasks automatically when active.&lt;/b&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] Everything should behave similar to before without configuring a new schedule.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] With a schedule active the tasks on the blackboard get replaced completely.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] There is a new tab for this next to 'bills' with a selected blackboard.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] The room does consider sculptures, items and production-tables which fit the current subject and their quality.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Info] Additionally skill-books from 'Vanilla Books Expanded' and other items stored inside the room are considered aswell.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;
  &lt;color=silver&gt;&lt;i&gt;(There is some basic information for the multipliers on the new schedule-tab, it is kind of like the beauty / cleanliness score of a room)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
		<modNameReadable>Children, school and learning</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>Children</modIdentifier>
		<defName>Children_1_7_6_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.7.6.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
		 &lt;b&gt;(Changes only for Rimworld 1.5+)&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- Fix: Biotech childhood should now work correctly for older children&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- Fix: Eye color should now be mixed/inherited aswell for some HAR species (for example Kurin)&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- Fix: Some HAR species where born with items if born with age 0 (sometimes with guns ^^)&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- Enhanced some texts/alerts + pregnancy checks + added ModIcon&lt;/b&gt;</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
		<modNameReadable>Children, school and learning</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>Children</modIdentifier>
		<defName>Children_1_7_6_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.7.6.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
		 &lt;b&gt;(Changes for Rimworld 1.4 and 1.5+)&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- (Both) Scaling should now work in 1.4 and 1.5 and with HAR (turn it off if things look weird)&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- (Both) Scaling: Additional options to enable/disable with Biotech active&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- (Both) Fix: Feeding children meals without Biotech should now work the same as for a patient in the hospital if they are lying in a bed&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- (Both) Fix: Prevent error-messages when growing up without Biotech active&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- (Both) Fix: Prevent error-messages in work-tab without Biotech active&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- (Both) Fix: Crown inherit error can cause miising heads on HAR hybrid child&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- (Both) Fix: Prevent setting ideology and causing an error if not active&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- (1.4) Fix: Eye color should now be mixed/inherited aswell for some HAR species (for example Kurin)&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- (1.4) Kown issue: Some HAR species can be born with items if born with age 0 (sometimes with guns ^^)&lt;/b&gt;</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
		<modNameReadable>Children, school and learning</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>Children</modIdentifier>
		<defName>Children_1_7_6_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.7.6.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
		 &lt;b&gt;(Changes for Rimworld 1.4 and 1.5+)&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- (Both) Fix: Babies would look like adults with development stages value set in per species settings (Settings are now reset and have to explicitly be enabled to disable development stages, if this is needed for a HAR species etc.)&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- (Both) Fix: Prevent inheriting bodytype for babies (only works now for older born children)&lt;/b&gt;</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
		<modNameReadable>Children, school and learning</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>Children</modIdentifier>
		<defName>Children_1_7_6_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.7.6.3</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
		 &lt;b&gt;(Changes for Rimworld 1.4 and 1.5+)&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- (Both) Addded a new option to hide colonists which don't have study/teach-work enabled in the menus of the blackboard/desk&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- (Both) Added a new drop down in the school-desk to assign all slots to one student / clear all&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- (Both) Added a new drop down in the school-desk to set a max level for learning and also stop at level 20 by default&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- (Both) Fix: High milk usage when breastfeeding with Biotech / hunger multiplier of young children was too high&lt;/b&gt;
		|&lt;b&gt;- (1.5) Fix: Healh tab height with fertility&lt;/b&gt;</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>