<?xml version="1.0" encoding ="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Age Matters 2.0 [1.2+]</name>
	<author>Troopersmith1</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>Troopersmith1.AgeMatters</packageId>
	<url></url>
	<modDependencies>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
	</loadAfter>
	<description>
This rework of Age Matters Updated would not have been possible without the MoHAR hediffs mod, made by Gouda quiche, ( https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2057001924 ) so head over and give that mod a positive rating as well if you like this mod.

Makes being very young detrimental for your abilites, as well as adding penalties for advanced age that affect all pawns. Intended to be used alongside mods that add children to get the full experience but does add to the game even if you do not use one of those mods, and none of the mods that add children are necessary for the mod to function.

This mod utilizes the lifestages of humans, as well as modded races, to simulate the effects of aging on a pawn over their life from birth to death. Adds a lifestage after adult, called elderly, that is used to express the effects of advanced age, even on those without specific issues, like a bad back.

Also adds a crib for young children, only usable by pawns under a certain bodysize. Artwork for the crib provided by the talented Onyxae.
		
Life Stages:
		
Newborn (Not currently implemented)
	Completely dependent on others for all needs, can't feed or dress themselves. Very short duration compared to other stages ~ 2 quadrums (30days). Will be confined to bed until reaching the "Baby" stage.
	I would like feedback from you guys, let me know if this is something you would like added.

Baby
	Unable to speak yet, very poor manipulation, slow movement speed, very sleepy, periodically throws up

Toddler
	Limited ability to speak, poor manipulation, still slow and sleepy, but less so than babies, occasionally throws up

Child
	Small speech penalty, slightly reduced manipulation, slightly slower movement speed, rarely throws up
	
Teenager
	Largely the same as adults, but erratic. Has occasional mental breaks (mostly minor) for no particular reason. (Still ungoing balance changes, any feedback here would be welcome)

Adult
	No changes

Elderly
	Slightly reduced movement speed and manipulation, as well as a penalty to immunity gain speed, making them more vulnerable to diseases.
	
Compatibility:
NOT ALL ALIEN RACES USE ALL LIFE STAGES. I have done the best I can to keep true to the design from the base mod when I added compatibility, but if anyone has suggestions, I'm not opposed to changing things around.
Each alien race will require a patch to work with this mod. If you have a race that doesn't work, just let me know and I can add compatibility.
		
Currently compatible with the following races:
[O21] Forgotten Realms
[O21] Star Trek
[O21] Stargate
[Ry]Rimcraft
[Ry]Rimcraft Allied Races
[SYR] Harpy
[SYR] Naga
[SYR] Thrumkin
Angels and Devils
Antinium
Anthro Races
Anty the war ant race
Apini Playable Race, Continued!
Arachne Race
Argonians of Blackmarsh
Astoriel
Avian Races
Beast Man Tribes
Beetle People (cont)
Bob's Krogan
Braixen - Fire Pokemon [1.2]
Bun Race
Cactaceae (Continued)
Callistans
Centaurs (cont)
Crystal Race
Crystalloid
Cutebold Race
Dragonian Race
Elona Imouto Race
Engi Race
Fantasy Goblins Updated
Fell Tribes
Ferian Race
Ferrex Race
Filthy Orc Invasion (Continued)
Forsaken
Frieza Race
Gerzee Race
Half Dragons
Ikquan Race
Jello People
Kerbal Race
Kijin
Kilhn Race
Klickmala Race
Kurin HAR Edition
Lanius Race
Lapelli Race
Leeani Playable Race
Littluna Race
Lizardmen/Lizardmen Lite
Llisceans
Logann Race
Lombax - Desert Warriors [1.2]
Lord of the Rims Dwarves
Lord of the Rims Elves
Lord of the Rims Hobbits
Mantis Race
Mincho, The Mint Choco Slime
Mincho, The Mint Choco Slime ~ HAR ver.
Minotaur Race
Monstergirl Races
MorrowRim - Altmer Race
MorrowRim - Bosmer Race
MorrowRim - Dunmer Race
MorrowRim - Falmer Race
MorrowRim - Orsimer Race
Moyo
NewRatkinPlus
Ni'hal 1.0-1.2
Nyaron Race
Oni of the Rim
Orassans
Pawnbold Race
Poleepkwa Race
Rabbie Race
Racc Race
Rakkle the rattle snake Race
Raptor Race
Revia Race
Rim-Hivers!
Rim-Shek
Rimeffect Races
Rimeffect: Asari of The Rims
Rimhammer - The End Times - Beastmen
Rimhammer - The End Times - Dwarfs
RimVali: Far From Avalon
Rock People
Rockmen Race
ShadowRimRaces
Silkiera Race
Slither Race
Slug Race
Star Wars Races
The Drow Race Continued
The GiantRace by HellCross
Thrumboian Race
Tree People (Continued)
Trench Cats
Twi'lek Race
Vulpes
Vulpine Race Pack
Warhammer"ish":Dryad
Warhammer: Daemonettes
Warhammer: Fimir
Warhammer: Gor
Warhammer: Skaven
Warhammer: Zhthy'hl
Xenn Race
Xenohumans - Anthromorphs
Xenohumans - Gen-spliced Xenos on the Rim
Xenoorca Race
Zabrak Race (Continued)
Zeta Reticulan
Zoltan Race

	</description>
</ModMetaData>
