<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
	<ModMetaData>
		<name>Caution Tiles [1.0+]</name>
		<author>EsseCoisa</author>
		<url></url>
		<supportedVersions>
			<li>1.0</li>
			<li>1.1</li>
			<li>1.2</li>
			<li>1.3</li>
			<li>1.4</li>			
		</supportedVersions>
		<packageId>essecoisa.CautionTiles</packageId>
		<description>[b]Safety is the key to a happy, healthy and efficient settlement, and nothing guarantees safety* better than striped flooring![/b]

		[b]DESCRIPTION[/b]
		This mod is pretty straight forward - metal tiles with stripes and fancy colors to boot. It stems from my work maintaining [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1543196802]Floored Re-Reupload[/url] and [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1543195051]Floored - Yellow and Striped Tiles Only[/url] after Curundir ceased working on the original (and wonderful) Floored mod and left it to the public to caretake. 

		From the first time I saw those stripes on the workshop, I knew I had to have them in different colors... and if I'm honest I never really cared for the border around individual striped tiles. It took me far, [i]far[/i] too long to figure out that it wasn't that difficult to make the changes I wanted, so here we are.

		[b]NOTES[/b]
		I've made this a separate mod from Yellow and Striped Tiles Only because the changes here might not be for everyone and it would have definitely broken some saves. While this shares the plain yellow metal tile with YaSTO, it doesn't seem to throw any errors and you can use both together if you wish.

		You're free to add this mod to any existing game without worry, just keep in mind that removing it without first disassembling these Caution Tiles will result in sand... everywhere.

		I haven't tested this with every mod, but I doubt it will have compatibility issues with any mod. It's just a bit of flooring.

		b]TO DO[/b]
		- [strike]See if I can't condense the colors into fancy right-click menus to save some space in the floors menu[/strike]
		- More colors (maybe)
		- Stripes in different directions
		- Ludeon forum post (when the game exits early access)
		- That's probably enough, let's not get too nuts here

		[b]VERSION[/b]
		Version 1.2-R1.0
	
		[b]LIKE I'M GOING TO ACTUALLY SUE YOU BUT PLEASE BE NICE THANKS[/b]
		Original code in Caution Tiles is licensed under the [url=https://opensource.org/licenses/MIT]MIT license[/url] with the condition that I, EsseCoisa, am given credit for my work.

		Original content in Caution Tiles (imagery, text) is similarly licensed under the [url=https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/]CC-BY-SA 4.0 license[/url] - in summary, you're free to do whatever you want with this mod so long as I'm (again, EsseCoisa) given credit. Unless you find something terrible and foul you can use this mod for... leave me outta that.


		[spoiler]*Safety not guaranteed.[/spoiler]
	</description>
</ModMetaData>