<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
	<!-- used as the default string for all these settings. -->
	<!-- used as the default string for all these settings. -->
	<ChickenProvisionsDefaultText>USSOC provisions</ChickenProvisionsDefaultText>
	<!-- Faction Relations letters -->
	<!-- For letter labels, {0} is the colored name of the faction. -->		  
	<RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_Coalition>Message from {0}</RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_Coalition>
	<RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_Allegiance>Message from {0}</RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_Allegiance>
	<RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_141>Message from {0}</RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_141>
	<RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_Umbra>Message from {0}</RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_Umbra>
	<RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_CordisDie>Message from {0}</RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_CordisDie>
	<RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_Ghosts>Message from {0}</RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_Ghosts>
	<RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_MSF>Message from {0}</RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_MSF>
	<RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_MSFH1>Message from {0}</RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_MSFH1>
	<!-- For letter text,
		 {0} is the title of the faction's leader,
		 {1} is the colored name of the faction's leader,
		 {2} is the colored name of the faction. -->
	
	<RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_Coalition>You have received a message from {1}, {0} of {2}:\n\n"This is Zero Actual. Welcome to the outer rim. \n\nGood to see more friendly faces out here. Please be advised there are rogue operators, insurgents and other unkown hostiles in the area. We've encountered mechanoids here but thankfully it's not like back home. I'm sure you'll be grateful to know that the boys from USSOC will drop you supplies every week. We have officially disavowed rogue first wave coalition forces, and we will pass the message on to any of our allies throughout the coming days. Drop by sometime to grab a decent meal at bastion, we've got some nice grub in the mess hall. \n\nDon't forget why we're here and stay safe out there always. Goodluck, Zero Actual out."\n\n{2} is now your ally.</RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_Coalition>
	
	<RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_Allegiance>You have received a message from {1}, {0} of {2}:\n\n"Greetings comrades, this is Aurora One. \n\nDid you boys and girls enjoy space? I found it a bit, what's the word? ah- nauseating. I needed some vodka and hardbass to get over it. \n\nNo I'm just screwing with you, I don't drink. I'll get to the point comrade, we're your allies now. Please don't forget about us out here if we're ever in trouble and we will do the same for you. Let's work together for our people's benefit and put the past behind us.\n\n Dasvidanya, Aurora One out." \n\n{2} is now your ally.</RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_Allegiance>
	
	<RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_141>You have received a message from {1}, {0} of {2}:\n\n"This is Bravo Five. \n\nGood to see some old comrades back in the game. We're 1-4-1, I'm sure you've been briefed by Bravo Six. We've got different objectives to focus on and any help from you would be appreciated. \n\nYou ever hear the old saying, "the enemy of my enemy is my friend"? Well, there's a lot of moppets here that will shoot anything that moves, you best start getting popular with the locals.\n\nGive us a ring if you run into trouble, we look after our friends. Bravo Five out."\n\n{2} is now your ally.</RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_141>
	
	<RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_Ghosts>You have received a message from {1}, {0} of {2}:\n\n"This is Ghost Six-Four. You Coalition guys sure know how to make an entrance, a loud one at that. \n\nWelcome to no man's land. Out there, you will learn to guard each other, to hunt, to speak without speaking. You'll become men. No offense to the ladies in your team, but you get what I mean.. \n\nAnytime you guys wanna resupply just drop by our ouposts. We'll help your team out if you run into trouble, please don't forget about us too. Anything you can do to help us will be appreciated.\n\nStay safe out there. Ghost Six-Four out."\n\n{2} is now your ally.</RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_Ghosts>
	
	<RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_Umbra>You have received a message from {1}, {0} of {2}:\n\n"This is Butcher Two. Pleasure to speak with you. \n\nI'd like to call for a cease fire between our troops. Our intel suggests that you are third wave Coalition? we know what it's like to lose your home because of mechanoids. I think we can work together. We've had difficulties negotiating with your other "friends" but I'd wager that you're smarter than the rest of them. \n\nWe have a contract to fulfill in this sector, and Coalition presence does not make our lives easier. Please don't be the hero that gets shot for people that you don't know, these locals are animals that would butcher your meat and use your skin to make a new armchair. Step out of our way and we'll keep them away from you. We're very interested in a mutually beneficial stay. \n\nI'll order our contractors not to engage your people. Please don't insult us and shoot us with our backs turned, consider this a professional courtesy.\n\nHave a good day, Butcher Two out."\n\n{2} is now neutral.</RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_Umbra>
	
	<RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_CordisDie>You have received a message from {1}, {0} of {2}:\n\n"I know the smell of government dogs from miles away. \n\nYour people are a plague in your dying world, and now you look elsewhere to spread your disease? We are the cure.\n\nYour leaders, where are they? Still hiding in air conditioned bunkers while you eat dust here? What a joke that you reward them with loyalty, to think they're looking out for your best interests.\n\nCordis Die is judgement day, you are either with us or you are against us. \n\nYou will hear from us again soon."\n\n{2} is now your enemy.</RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_CordisDie>
	
	<RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_MSF>You have received a message from Kazuhira Miller, {0} of {2}:\n\n"This is Commander Miller from MSF. We hear you could use a hand. \n\nI apologise for the late call, we've been busy. We're nothing but grateful for Coalition using our services, we promise nothing but satisfactory results until our contract expires. \n\nIf the times demand it, we'll be revolutionaries, criminals, terrorists. The world calls for wetwork, and we answered. No greater good. No just cause.\n\nTry some of our burgers some time, we've opened the Maxi Buns franchise here. Drop by Mother Base or any MSF outpost for some decent food, promise you won't regret it! \n\nMiller out."\n\n{2} is now your ally.</RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_MSF>
	
	<RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_MSFH1>You have received a message from Kazuhira Miller, {0} of {2}:\n\n"Hey this is Miller again, I have bad news. \n\nYour contract just expired, and I regret to inform you that someone just hired MSF to take you down. We've spoken to Coalition's chain of command and a few of your allies, some of which are currently under our protection. They agreed that they will stay out of this since it is within their best interests not to make enemies out of us. I know it's real awkward having to deal with politics and all this stuff, but we get paid to do our jobs and we aim to do it well. It's nothing personal. \n\nFor what it's worth? I didn't wanna take the contract cause you guys buy our burgers, but Big Boss gave the green light to take you on, he thought it'd be interesting.\n\nSee you in the battlefield and goodluck. Miller out."\n\n{2} is now your enemy.</RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_MSFH1>
	
	<RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_MSF2>You have received a message from Kazuhira Miller, {0} of {2}:\n\n"Hello it's Miller, pleasure to speak to you again. \n\nI'm glad to inform you that Coalition renewed their contract with us, we'll be covering your backs this time round for the coming years. I understand some of you may hold grudges from our past interaction, but you've managed to survive the ordeal. I'm not even surprised, the Boss himself was impressed, wanted me to tell you that "You're pretty good." \n\nAnyway, we've got burgers and other delicious food waiting for you here at Maxi Buns as always, I'll even give you guys a discount! You guys are getting at least 10% off. \n\nSay goodbye to Pax Americana, say hello to Pax HAMBURGANA! Miller out."\n\n{2} is now your ally.</RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_MSF2>
	
	<RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_TribeCivil>Message from {0}</RH_RelLabel_PlayerFaction_TribeCivil>
	<RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_TribeCivil>You receive a smoke signal from afar, apparently sent by {2}. It signals a cryptic greeting.\n\nYour relations with {2} have improved.</RH_RelText_PlayerFaction_TribeCivil>
	<!-- Provisioner strings -->
	<!-- start letter -->
	<RH_ProLabel_PlayerFaction_Start>Provisions begin</RH_ProLabel_PlayerFaction_Start>
	<!-- For text, {0} is the def label of the player faction. -->
	<RH_ProText_PlayerFaction_Start>You have received a care package from USSOC space station.</RH_ProText_PlayerFaction_Start>
	<!-- end letter -->
	<RH_ProLabel_PlayerFaction_End>Provisions end</RH_ProLabel_PlayerFaction_End>
	<RH_ProText_PlayerFaction_End>You will no longer receive care packages from USSOC space station.</RH_ProText_PlayerFaction_End>
	<!-- drop/no drop message -->
	<RH_ProMsg_PlayerFaction_Drop>You have received a care package from USSOC space station.</RH_ProMsg_PlayerFaction_Drop>
	<RH_ProMsg_PlayerFaction_NoDrop>You don't seem to have received your scheduled care package.</RH_ProMsg_PlayerFaction_NoDrop>
</LanguageData>