<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>Vanilla Faction Expanded - better textures and pawnkinds</name>
    <author>Qux</author>
	<supportedVersions>
<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>qux.factionexpanded.bettertexturesandpawnkinds</packageId>
    <description>This mod is an addon for the Vanilla Faction Expanded series (Settlers - Medieval - Vikings)

It adds two things:

- First of all, new textures in 512 pixels for the majority of the weapons of these mods.

- Then, I was always embarrassed by the fact that the pawns appeared with mismatched clothes, see anachronistic (I know that rimworld is happening on another planet in the future blablabla, but I don't like to see knights of a medieval faction appeared with baseball bats, or cowboys with hoodies).

This mod therefore reworks from zero the appearance of clothes and weapons for pawns, thanks to a series of patches from other mods, you will now really have the impression of dealing with cowboys, knights or vikings , the immersion is greatly improved.

Find a selection of the chosen textures:

If you only want the weapon re-textures, you can use this mod with just the 3 factions expanded.

If you want the pawnkind improvements, here are the links of the different mods that interact here (you don't have to download all the mods, each patch is independent and will improve its part):

- https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2585571655 Crown and Regalia : All crowns in this mod can appear on the heads of kings.

- https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2054588241 Darkest Rim Core : Add outfits for the "sellsword", "knight in black", "lord", and "bandit leader".

- https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2580034867 Faction  Hippies : Medieval and Viking peasants will appear with farming tools.

- https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2603735147 FCP NCR Armor and Apparel Pack : Add an outfit for the '' Frontier Trader '', the '' Deputy '', the '' Militia '', the '' Sheriff '', and cowboy hats for all the 'Settlers'

- https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2580034867 Rimmu_Nation_Weapons : Add weapons for all pawns in the settler mod.

- https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1522429439 Slave outfits : Add outfit for Viking Slave, Viking Peasant, Medieval Peasant, and tunics for all Medieval pawns.

Textures come from flaticon.com, thanks to their autors :
- dague, mace , seax, double barrel shotgun, double revolver, harpoon, hunting rifle, sword, tomahawk by Freepik
- dynamite by Creaticca Creative Agency
- beard axe, throwing axe by Nikita Golubev
- dane axe by Good Ware
- arrow by pixel perfect

</description>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.SettlersModule</packageId>
      <displayName>Vanilla Factions Expanded - Settlers</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2052918119</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>OskarPotocki.VFE.Vikings</packageId>
      <displayName>Vanilla Factions Expanded - Vikings</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2231295285</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.MedievalModule</packageId>
      <displayName>Vanilla Factions Expanded - Medieval</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2023513450</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.SettlersModule</li>
    <li>OskarPotocki.VFE.Vikings</li>
    <li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.MedievalModule</li>
  </loadAfter>
    </ModMetaData>