<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Syntho: Phytotech</name>
	<author>SkylorBeck</author>
	<packageId>SkylorBeck.Syntho.Expac1</packageId>
	<url>http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1234438466</url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
			<displayName>Humanoid Alien Races 2.0</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>SkylorBeck.Syntho.Base</packageId>
			<displayName>Syntho Base</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1234438466</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadBefore>
	</loadBefore>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
		<li>SkylorBeck.Syntho.Base</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<incompatibleWith />
	<description>
Welcome to the first expansion for Syntho, Phytotech! This expansion is all about growing a new plant called Fibril. With it, you can craft new prosthetic limbs, new brain implants and new weapons! This is an expansion on Syntho but it is optional. Nothing here is required to enjoy Syntho, but Syntho is required to enjoy Phytotech. This is mostly complete, but please leave ideas for more in the comments below!

[h1]Current Version:[/h1] [b]0.9.1[/b]
[b]PLEASE SEE CHANGE NOTES FOR ALL PATCHES/UPDATES[/b]

[h1]Features:[/h1]
Fibril, a new plant that produces a strong fiber. Useful for crafting clothing, implants, limbs and weapons.
Includes new limbs, organs and even eyes!
Three new guns. A Sniper, a shotgun and an SMG. The SMG has a melee attachment.
A hammer. For...fixing people...with force.
Implants that help with old age and sleep.
Additions to the Syntho research tree. 

[h1]The Stats:[/h1]
The Hammer is a slow but deadly melee weapon. Generally higher than average Blut damage.
The SMG fires four quick shots but does less damage per bullet than a pistol. It is incredibly accurate at close range and has a strong bayonet. 
The Shotgun is very high damage but slow to fire and low accuracy.
The Sniper is extremely high damage with high accuracy but very, very slow to fire.
All of the limbs are 10% better than normal but cause pain.

Like what I do?
[url=https://ko-fi.com/skylorbeck][img]https://i.imgur.com/Rw0ZpIx.png?1[/img][/url]</description>
</ModMetaData>