<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>Faction Blender</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>FactionBlender</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1734490820</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>FactionBlender_1_3_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.3</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
&lt;b&gt;Fixes:&lt;/b&gt;
- Fixed a few critical bugs with the apparelStuffFilter injections and patch
        </content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>FactionBlender_1_3_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;Additions:&lt;/b&gt;
- The blacklists accept * as a wildcard now

&lt;b&gt;Fixes:&lt;/b&gt;
- Added SmashPhil's Boats to default blacklist
- Fixed errors from missing traderKindDef.label
- Fixed errors from generating ancient pawns
- Removed Manifest.xml to fix dep mismatches from Fluffy's Mod Manager
- Added More Vanilla Biomes to the "Is pack animal allowed?" patch

&lt;b&gt;Tweaks:&lt;/b&gt;
- Biome pack animal error is now just a warning
        </content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>FactionBlender_1_3_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;Fixes:&lt;/b&gt;
- Fixed "Sequence contains no elements" crash that occurred on certain mod combinations
        </content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>FactionBlender_1_3_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;Fixes:&lt;/b&gt;
- Now fully compatible with RimWorld v1.1!
- Fixed conflict with apparelRequired and factions' apparelStuffFilter during apparel generation
        </content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>FactionBlender_1_2_5</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.2.5</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;Additions:&lt;/b&gt;
- Ancient dangers are a bit more interesting

&lt;b&gt;Fixes:&lt;/b&gt;
- Trader kinds for FB factions are merged together, so that they can all fit on the faction negotiation dialog

&lt;b&gt;Tweaks:&lt;/b&gt;
- Added a bunch more biomes to the "Is pack animal allowed?" patch; re-adjusted temperatures
        </content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>FactionBlender_1_2_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.2.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;Additions:&lt;/b&gt;
- Mixed race starting colonists now work for Lost Tribes scenario
- Added config option to blacklist specific races ("Excluded pawn kinds by race")
- Added Chinese translations.  (Thanks, CaptainSnafu!)

&lt;b&gt;Fixes:&lt;/b&gt;
- Different racial backstories no longer get mixed together.  The same goes for hair styles.
- Xenomorphs and Better Infestation's Queens are in the blacklist by default
- Blacklist config options now use a larger textbox

&lt;b&gt;Tweaks:&lt;/b&gt;
- Badly-behaving pawns (ones that attack their own faction) will get a debug warning that will include the defaultFactionType and race defName to use in one of the blacklists
- Blacklist filter displays will update their cache properly while entries are being changed
- Blacklist config options will detect defaults based on the previous mod version and upgrade them
        </content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>FactionBlender_1_1_5</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.1.5.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;Additions:&lt;/b&gt;
- Now you can use all your races for vanilla starting scenarios!
- Added all races for wanderer, refugee, and slave types as well
- All of these options are adjustable in Mod Settings
        </content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>FactionBlender_1_1_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.1.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;Additions:&lt;/b&gt;
- Added a config menu.  Now you can tweak which pawns are included in various groups.
- Replaced the caravan pack animal generation algorithm.  Now, trade caravan pack animals will vary in count based on the wares weight, will sometimes show up with a variety of pack animals, and will try to balance the cargo's weight without overloading themselves (usually).

&lt;b&gt;Fixes:&lt;/b&gt;
- The new Archotech Centipede from Genetic Rim is no longer a threat.  Unless you want to re-adjust the slider...

&lt;b&gt;Tweaks:&lt;/b&gt;
- A few more variations on faction names
- The herdAnimal property is no longer a factor in determining if they are appropriate in combat
- Since the pack animal algorithm has been replaced, body size is no longer a factor in determining appropriate caravan pack animals
        </content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>