<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Nudist's Evasion</name>
	<author>Fuu Chan</author>
	<packageId>Fuu.NudistsEvasion</packageId>
	<description>
While there are obvious disadvantages to not having armor or protective clothing, it would be a mistake to underestimate the speed, agility, and footwork of an unhindered warrior.

To increase the diversity and viability of low armor and nudist playthroughs, this mod gives lightly armored and naked colonists a bonus to their melee dodge and a new ranged evasion mechanic.

Primary Changes
When someone has an equipped apparel mass of less than 8 kg (Ccnfigurable in options), they will increasingly gain the following bonuses until reaching the maximum bonus when they're fully unhindered:
1. 40% Melee dodge. (Configurable in the options)
2. 40% Ranged evasion.
3. 20% Movement speed when drafted.
(Belt/Utility items are not counted for apparel mass).
(The ability to dodge/evade can increase or decrease past the above value based on movement stat: Affected by buffs/debuffs, drugs, implants, or injury!)
(This is added multiplicatively to the existing accuracy formula, meaning no combination of effects will make someone invulnerable with 100% dodge/evade).

Compatibility
*0% performance impact (0.000ms in Dub's Performance Analyzer).

*Safe to add and remove mid-game, but undraft everyone first when removing.

*Independent, isolated, and minimal in scope, with no unsafe modifications to vanilla behavior/code: A 100% safe post-fix multiplier is added at the end of the hit chance formula, so it should be compatible with nearly every mod, leaves no permanent changes to your saved game, and will not brick your game.

*Confirmed compatible with Vanilla Expanded series, Alpha series, Dubs series, and hundreds more.

*NOT compatible with Combat Extended however, because they completely remove and replace vanilla's combat system with their own.

Updates
~4.0 update: Now compatible with 1.5! Increased maximum mass limit in options from 15kg to 50kg. Added localization keys for "dodge" and "evade" in pawn info tab.
~3.1 update: Allow dodge and evade chance to increase past the maximum value if buffed beyond normal speed due to buffs, drugs, and implants (Up to a maximum of 85% dodge/evade).
~3.0 update: Now compatible with 1.4! Increased default setting for maximum apparel mass from 6kg to 8kg. Removed the "require nudist meme/precept" setting option, to increase speed and reduce bloat because it was more of a 1.0 feature that is no longer needed.
~2.4 update: Fixed Vanilla Factions Expanded: Pirates' Warcaskets not being recognized. Increased maximum mass/dodge/evade limit in the options for more freedom in customization.
~2.3 update: Added "DisappearsOnDeath" to the Nudist's Swiftness buff, to prevent it from being listed as a cause of death when a pawn dies due to another reason.
~2.2 update: Changed setting "Only apply to player controlled colonists and slaves" to default to True. Otherwise this mod can make certain humanoid-based raids stronger than intended since the extra evade/dodge isn't taken into account by the raid points system.
~2.1 update: "Apparel Mass" no longer includes Utility items. Maximum movement speed buff when drafted increased to 20% from 15%. Apparel Mass in stats page shows decimal values now.
~2.0 update: Dodge and evasion have been reworked to scale based on "Apparel Mass", which enables all types of light armor evasion builds instead of being useful only for nudism playthroughs! In addition, balance has been adjusted after mathing and testing various values. Existing users are recommended to the go the mod options and press "Reset" to update to the latest values!

Github Link: https://github.com/tenguin/Rimworld_NudistsEvasion

Credits to: personal ami and Ninomae Ina'nis for the artwork used in the thumbnail and tanosii_chan for the upvote animation! Give them a visit!
	</description>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Anomaly</li>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>