<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- BinaryProcessor -->

  <BinaryProcessor.label>binary processor</BinaryProcessor.label>
  <BinaryProcessor.description>A binary computer that syncs with the user's brain and processes some of the tasks independently.</BinaryProcessor.description>


  <!-- NeuroConnOverclocker -->

  <NCO.label>NCO</NCO.label>
  <NCO.description>A neuro-connection overclocker that combining signals in an internal micro-computer and producing more accelerated organized signals.</NCO.description>


  <!-- NeuroRedistributor -->

  <NeuroRedistributor.label>neuro redistributor</NeuroRedistributor.label>
  <NeuroRedistributor.description>An incredibly powerful nano computer that combines sensoric signals and reorganizes them in the most effective group for task.</NeuroRedistributor.description>


  <!-- NeuroActivator -->

  <NeuroActivator.label>neuro activator</NeuroActivator.label>
  <NeuroActivator.description>Neuro activator shell that returns a small part of the spent energy of the owner's brain to a special
neural translator. The excess gate also outputs this energy to stimulate the" happiness " of the host.</NeuroActivator.description>


  <!-- NeuroInterface -->

  <NeuroInterface.label>neuro interface</NeuroInterface.label>
  <NeuroInterface.description>Neuro-interface. In fact, it is incredibly complex. It has over a thousand connection points, and the process of installing it can be lethal with a fairly high chance. Despite all the difficulties, it gives only average bonus to work and other tasks.</NeuroInterface.description>


  <!-- NeuroAssistances -->

  <NeuroAssistance.label>neuro assistance</NeuroAssistance.label>
  <NeuroAssistance.description>Neuro Assistant is a versatile voice assistant that helps you focus on tasks and perform them more efficiently. Connected to the Neural Link fold network.</NeuroAssistance.description>


  <!-- ExoAI -->

  <ExoAI.label>exo AI</ExoAI.label>
  <ExoAI.description>Exo AI its a new non-combat AI. It concetrates on work much more effective then Assistant.</ExoAI.description>


  <!-- MoodAmplifier -->

  <MoodAmplifier.label>mood amplifier</MoodAmplifier.label>
  <MoodAmplifier.description>Mood amplifier makes you feel better..</MoodAmplifier.description>


  <!-- Holo-Partner -->

  <HoloPartner.label>holo-partner</HoloPartner.label>
  <HoloPartner.description>A holo-partner that helps you to live in this cruel world with its love!</HoloPartner.description>


  <!-- AMD -->

  <AMD.label>AMD</AMD.label>
  <AMD.description>AMD - Advanced Memory Descriptor. It uses the new neuro technology that blocks natural memory bridge connections and translate this into binaric signals. More effective</AMD.description>


  <!-- NeuroTrainer -->

  <NeuroTrainer.label>neuro trainer</NeuroTrainer.label>
  <NeuroTrainer.description>Neuro Trainer is a brand new AI trainer that helps you to learn every part of universe in a moment!</NeuroTrainer.description>


  <!-- CombatAssistant -->

  <CombatAssistant.label>combat assistant</CombatAssistant.label>
  <CombatAssistant.description>Combat assistant helps you in a combat. He takes a part of body tasks and make the control of it much more effective!</CombatAssistant.description>


  <!-- PsyDefender -->

  <PsyDefender.label>psy defender</PsyDefender.label>
  <PsyDefender.description>Psy defender - Advanced protection AI that blocks a part of incoming psy waves in brain gates.</PsyDefender.description>


</LanguageData>