<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
 
  <IAmAlive.label>I Am Alive</IAmAlive.label>
  <IAmAlive.description>You come from a distant and ancient galaxy. All the memories that happened before you wake up are lost. There is no doubt that you have been brainwashed by crazy scientists. After years of suffering, you managed to escape from this place of right and wrong and take a shuttle to the unknown galaxy.\nYou think bitterly on the spaceship: Why did they hunt down the ancient people?\nThere is no doubt that the blood flowing from ancient people is as attractive as Tang Monk's flesh. No matter nobles, pirates or scientists, they all want to get the blood. It is said that it can keep their youth forever. Who knows.\nAfter you open the autopilot system, you enter the cryptosleep casket.\n\n\n\nNote: I don't recommend using Edb Prepare Carefuly, because every Ancient is unique.\n\n</IAmAlive.description>
  <IAmAlive.scenario.description>You come from a distant and ancient galaxy. All the memories that happened before you wake up are lost. There is no doubt that you have been brainwashed by crazy scientists. After years of suffering, you managed to escape from this place of right and wrong and take a shuttle to the unknown galaxy.\nYou think bitterly on the spaceship: Why did they hunt down the ancient people?\nThere is no doubt that the blood flowing from ancient people is as attractive as Tang Monk's flesh. No matter nobles, pirates or scientists, they all want to get the blood. It is said that it can keep their youth forever. Who knows.\nAfter you open the autopilot system, you enter the cryptosleep casket.\n\n\n\nNote: I don't recommend using Edb Prepare Carefuly, because every Ancient is unique.\n\n</IAmAlive.scenario.description>
  <IAmAlive.scenario.name>I Am Alive</IAmAlive.scenario.name>
  <IAmAlive.scenario.parts.GameStartDialog.text>You awake in your cryptosleep sarcophagi to the sound of sirens and ripping metal. You barely get to the escape pods before the ship is torn apart. Some time later, you land on this unknown rimworld. \n\nWarning: The enemy will find you soon. Please ready.</IAmAlive.scenario.parts.GameStartDialog.text>
  <IAmAlive.scenario.summary>Choose brave ancient people began to take risks.</IAmAlive.scenario.summary>

</LanguageData>