<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Borg Race (Revisited)</name>
  <packageId>Nolabritt.BorgRaceFork</packageId>
  <author>nolabritt</author>
  <url>https://github.com/baguda/Borg_Race_Revisited</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li><li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</packageId>
      <displayName>HugsLib</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>	
	</li>
    <li>
      <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
      <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/erdelf/AlienRaces/wiki</downloadUrl>
    </li>
	<li>
	<packageId>kentington.saveourship2</packageId>
      <displayName>Save our Ship 2</displayName>
		<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/1909914131</steamWorkshopUrl>
	</li>
    <li>
	<packageId>co.uk.epicguru.ingamewiki</packageId>
      <displayName>In-Game Wiki</displayName>
		<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2113685739</steamWorkshopUrl>
	</li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
	<li>kentington.saveourship2</li>
	<li>co.uk.epicguru.ingamewiki</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>
  A revisiting of Honey Badgers mod, continued by Mlie (the great), for RimWorld 1.1. Using additional assets assimilated from DarkStar’s Patch

Playing as the Borg:
•This mod aims to expand upon the play experience of the Borg faction by overhauling the basic gameplay cycle and integrating the race into the Save our Ship 2 experience. 
•The borg’s behavioral subroutines have been altered to make them less human-like and more borg-like. 
•The economic system of the borg race has been overhauled to require continuous conquest and assimilation of other lifeforms, and to eliminate the need for non-borg-like activities such as farming and trading. 
•The new economic cycle is centered around the assimilation of materials and lifeforms by breaking them down into nanite substrate. 
•Substrate is used by borg to create every borg related item (clothes, food, weapons, buildings, etc.). 
•Organisms deemed suitable for full assimilation (human-like) can be captured and turned into new borg drones.
•New weapons, armors, implants, and buildings have been incorporated to enhance the borg game play experience. 
•Research not needed for the borg as they have the combined knowledge of the collective (and bc its lame). The research tree is used as development road map so check it for updates!  

The Borg faction:
•The borg faction is universally hostile and a force to be feared. 
•They have advanced, powerful gear and are capable of assimilating pawns in the heat of battle.
•Less advanced factions are forced to either retreat or be assimilated if the borg attack!  

To be done
•This is a beta release for play testing and feedback. 
•Balancing is rough but still ongoing (feedback needed)
•Borg faction as default SoS2 space encounter
•Quests replaced with borg-like quests. Including SoS2 space encounters. (help appreciated)
•Code cleaning (fixing the labels, descriptions, and other errors that come with copy-paste coding) 

Future Content Releases:
•Nanoprobes! Borg drones don’t repair, craft, or clean…
•The Unimatrix Queen! Research and logistics pawn
•Economic expansion! Add late game complexity with more buildings to spread out production and more substrates to diversify building.

Special Thanks:
A big thank you to everyone who worked on this mod prior to my revisiting! Even though we didn’t work together directly, I would not have been able to make this version without the hard work and contributions of those who pioneered the project. I don’t know everyone’s name so apologies if I’ve missed anyone.
•Honey Badger (orannjs), Original Author.
•Mlie, the man in black, revived the mod with 1.1 update.
•Thirite, contributor.
•Erdelf, contributor.
•EpicGuru, consultant. 
</description>
</ModMetaData>