<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Egg니드런Fertilized.label>니드런 알 (유정)</Egg니드런Fertilized.label>
  <Egg니드런Fertilized.description>Fertilized 니드런 egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby 니드런. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</Egg니드런Fertilized.description>

  <EggWurmpleFertilized.label>개무소 알 (유정)</EggWurmpleFertilized.label>
  <EggWurmpleFertilized.description>Fertilized wurmple egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby wurmple. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggWurmpleFertilized.description>

  <EggPoochyenaFertilized.label>포챠나 알 (유정)</EggPoochyenaFertilized.label>
  <EggPoochyenaFertilized.description>Fertilized poochyena egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby poochyena. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggPoochyenaFertilized.description>

  <EggTotodileFertilized.label>리아코 알 (유정)</EggTotodileFertilized.label>
  <EggTotodileFertilized.description>Fertilized totodile egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby totodile. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggTotodileFertilized.description>

  <EggChinchouFertilized.label>초라기 알 (유정)</EggChinchouFertilized.label>
  <EggChinchouFertilized.description>Fertilized chinchou egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby chinchou. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggChinchouFertilized.description>

  <EggJolteonFertilized.label>쥬피썬더 알 (유정)</EggJolteonFertilized.label>
  <EggJolteonFertilized.description>Fertilized jolteon egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby eevee. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggJolteonFertilized.description>

  <EggCyndaquilFertilized.label>니드런 알 (유정)</EggCyndaquilFertilized.label>
  <EggCyndaquilFertilized.description>Fertilized cyndaquil egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby cyndaquil. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggCyndaquilFertilized.description>

  <EggFlareonFertilized.label>부스터 알 (유정)</EggFlareonFertilized.label>
  <EggFlareonFertilized.description>Fertilized flareon egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby eevee. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggFlareonFertilized.description>

  <EggChikoritaFertilized.label>치코리타 알 (유정)</EggChikoritaFertilized.label>
  <EggChikoritaFertilized.description>Fertilized chikorita egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby chikorita. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggChikoritaFertilized.description>

  <EggEeveeFertilized.label>이브이 알 (유정)</EggEeveeFertilized.label>
  <EggEeveeFertilized.description>Fertilized eevee egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby eevee. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggEeveeFertilized.description>

  <EggZigzagoonFertilized.label>지그제구리 알 (유정)</EggZigzagoonFertilized.label>
  <EggZigzagoonFertilized.description>Fertilized zigzagoon egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby zigzagoon. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggZigzagoonFertilized.description>

  <EggGastlyFertilized.label>고오스 알 (유정)</EggGastlyFertilized.label>
  <EggGastlyFertilized.description>Fertilized gastly egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby gastly. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggGastlyFertilized.description>

  <EggHaunterFertilized.label>고우스트 알 (유정)</EggHaunterFertilized.label>
  <EggHaunterFertilized.description>Fertilized haunter egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby gastly. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggHaunterFertilized.description>

  <EggMareepFertilized.label>메리프 알 (유정)</EggMareepFertilized.label>
  <EggMareepFertilized.description>Fertilized mareep egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby mareep. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggMareepFertilized.description>

  <EggDoduoFertilized.label>두두 알 (유정)</EggDoduoFertilized.label>
  <EggDoduoFertilized.description>Fertilized doduo egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby doduo. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggDoduoFertilized.description>

  <EggCaterpieFertilized.label>캐터피 알 (유정)</EggCaterpieFertilized.label>
  <EggCaterpieFertilized.description>Fertilized caterpie egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby caterpie. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggCaterpieFertilized.description>

  <EggCharmanderFertilized.label>파이리 알 (유정)</EggCharmanderFertilized.label>
  <EggCharmanderFertilized.description>Fertilized charmander egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby charmander. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggCharmanderFertilized.description>

  <EggSquirtleFertilized.label>꼬부기 알 (유정)</EggSquirtleFertilized.label>
  <EggSquirtleFertilized.description>Fertilized squirtle egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby squirtle. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggSquirtleFertilized.description>

  <EggBulbasaurFertilized.label>이상해씨 알 (유정)</EggBulbasaurFertilized.label>
  <EggBulbasaurFertilized.description>Fertilized bulbasaur egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby bulbasaur. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggBulbasaurFertilized.description>

  <EggPichuFertilized.label>피츄 알 (유정)</EggPichuFertilized.label>
  <EggPichuFertilized.description>Fertilized pichu egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby pichu. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggPichuFertilized.description>

  <EggPikachuFertilized.label>피카츄 알 (유정)</EggPikachuFertilized.label>
  <EggPikachuFertilized.description>Fertilized pikachu egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby pichu. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggPikachuFertilized.description>

  <EggSandshrewFertilized.label>모래두지 알 (유정)</EggSandshrewFertilized.label>
  <EggSandshrewFertilized.description>Fertilized sandshrew egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby sandshrew. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggSandshrewFertilized.description>

  <EggSandslashFertilized.label>고지 알 (유정)</EggSandslashFertilized.label>
  <EggSandslashFertilized.description>Fertilized sandslash egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby sandshrew. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggSandslashFertilized.description>

  <EggDratiniFertilized.label>미뇽 알 (유정)</EggDratiniFertilized.label>
  <EggDratiniFertilized.description>Fertilized dratini egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby dratini. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggDratiniFertilized.description>

  <EggOnyxFertilized.label>롱스톤 알 (유정)</EggOnyxFertilized.label>
  <EggOnyxFertilized.description>Fertilized onyx egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby onyx. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggOnyxFertilized.description>

  <EggEspeonFertilized.label>에브이 알 (유정)</EggEspeonFertilized.label>
  <EggEspeonFertilized.description>Fertilized sandslash egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby eevee. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggEspeonFertilized.description>

  <EggVaporeonFertilized.label>샤미드 알 (유정)</EggVaporeonFertilized.label>
  <EggVaporeonFertilized.description>Fertilized vaporeon egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby eevee. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggVaporeonFertilized.description>

  <EggUmbreonFertilized.label>블래키 알 (유정)</EggUmbreonFertilized.label>
  <EggUmbreonFertilized.description>Fertilized umbreon egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby eevee. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggUmbreonFertilized.description>

  <EggNidorinaNidorinoFertilized.label>니드리나/니드리노 알 (유정)</EggNidorinaNidorinoFertilized.label>
  <EggNidorinaNidorinoFertilized.description>Fertilized 니드리나/니드리노 egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby 니드런. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggNidorinaNidorinoFertilized.description>

  <EggNidokingNidoqueenFertilized.label>니드킹/니드퀸 알 (유정)</EggNidokingNidoqueenFertilized.label>
  <EggNidokingNidoqueenFertilized.description>Fertilized 니드킹/니드퀸 egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby 니드리나/니드리노. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggNidokingNidoqueenFertilized.description>

  <EggTurtwigFertilized.label>모부기 알 (유정)</EggTurtwigFertilized.label>
  <EggTurtwigFertilized.description>Fertilized turtwig egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby turtwig. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggTurtwigFertilized.description>

  <EggIvysaurFertilized.label>이상해풀 알 (유정)</EggIvysaurFertilized.label>
  <EggIvysaurFertilized.description>Fertilized ivysaur egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby bulbasaur. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggIvysaurFertilized.description>

  <EggCharmeleonFertilized.label>파이리 알 (유정)</EggCharmeleonFertilized.label>
  <EggCharmeleonFertilized.description>Fertilized charmeleon egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby charmander. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggCharmeleonFertilized.description>

  <EggWartortleFertilized.label>어니부기 알 (유정)</EggWartortleFertilized.label>
  <EggWartortleFertilized.description>Fertilized wartortle egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby squirtle. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggWartortleFertilized.description>

  <EggAronFertilized.label>가보리 알 (유정)</EggAronFertilized.label>
  <EggAronFertilized.description>Fertilized aron egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby aron. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggAronFertilized.description>

  <EggSphealFertilized.label>대굴레오 알 (유정)</EggSphealFertilized.label>
  <EggSphealFertilized.description>Fertilized spheal egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby spheal. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggSphealFertilized.description>

  <EggShuppetFertilized.label>어둠대신 알 (유정)</EggShuppetFertilized.label>
  <EggShuppetFertilized.description>Fertilized shuppet egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby shuppet. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggShuppetFertilized.description>

  <EggBanetteFertilized.label>다크펫 알 (유정)</EggBanetteFertilized.label>
  <EggBanetteFertilized.description>Fertilized banette egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby shuppet. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggBanetteFertilized.description>

  <EggMegaBanetteFertilized.label>메가 다크펫 알 (유정)</EggMegaBanetteFertilized.label>
  <EggMegaBanetteFertilized.description>Fertilized mega banette egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby banette. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggMegaBanetteFertilized.description>

  <EggLitwickFertilized.label>불켜미 알 (유정)</EggLitwickFertilized.label>
  <EggLitwickFertilized.description>Fertilized litwick egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby litwick. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggLitwickFertilized.description>

  <EggMurkrowFertilized.label>니로우 알 (유정)</EggMurkrowFertilized.label>
  <EggMurkrowFertilized.description>Fertilized murkrow egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby murkrow. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggMurkrowFertilized.description>

  <EggZubatFertilized.label>주뱃 알 (유정)</EggZubatFertilized.label>
  <EggZubatFertilized.description>Fertilized zubat egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby zubat. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggZubatFertilized.description>

  <EggMegaCharizardXFertilized.label>메가 리자몽 x 알 (유정)</EggMegaCharizardXFertilized.label>
  <EggMegaCharizardXFertilized.description>Fertilized mega charizard x egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby charizard. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggMegaCharizardXFertilized.description>

  <EggPumpkabooFertilized.label>호바귀 알 (유정)</EggPumpkabooFertilized.label>
  <EggPumpkabooFertilized.description>Fertilized pumpkaboo egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby pumpkaboo. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggPumpkabooFertilized.description>

  <EggDrifloonFertilized.label>흔들풍손 알 (유정)</EggDrifloonFertilized.label>
  <EggDrifloonFertilized.description>Fertilized drifloon egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby drifloon. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggDrifloonFertilized.description>

  <EggZoruaFertilized.label>조로아 알 (유정)</EggZoruaFertilized.label>
  <EggZoruaFertilized.description>Fertilized zorua egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby zorua. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggZoruaFertilized.description>

  <EggZoroarkFertilized.label>조로아크 알 (유정)</EggZoroarkFertilized.label>
  <EggZoroarkFertilized.description>Fertilized zoroark egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby zorua. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggZoroarkFertilized.description>

  <EggHoundourFertilized.label>델빌 알 (유정)</EggHoundourFertilized.label>
  <EggHoundourFertilized.description>Fertilized houndour egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby houndour. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggHoundourFertilized.description>

  <EggShedinjaFertilized.label>껍질몬 알 (유정)</EggShedinjaFertilized.label>
  <EggShedinjaFertilized.description>Fertilized shedinja egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby nincada. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggShedinjaFertilized.description>

  <EggBellsproutFertilized.label>모다피 알 (유정)</EggBellsproutFertilized.label>
  <EggBellsproutFertilized.description>Fertilized bellsprout egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby bellsprout. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggBellsproutFertilized.description>

  <EggOddishFertilized.label>뚜벅초 알 (유정)</EggOddishFertilized.label>
  <EggOddishFertilized.description>Fertilized oddish egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby oddish. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggOddishFertilized.description>

  <EggCherubiFertilized.label>체리버 알 (유정)</EggCherubiFertilized.label>
  <EggCherubiFertilized.description>Fertilized cherubi egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby cherubi. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggCherubiFertilized.description>

  <EggHoppipFertilized.label>통통코 알 (유정)</EggHoppipFertilized.label>
  <EggHoppipFertilized.description>Fertilized hoppip egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby hoppip. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggHoppipFertilized.description>

  <EggTaurosFertilized.label>켄타로스 알 (유정)</EggTaurosFertilized.label>
  <EggTaurosFertilized.description>Fertilized tauros egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby tauros. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggTaurosFertilized.description>

  <EggMiltankFertilized.label>밀탱크 알 (유정)</EggMiltankFertilized.label>
  <EggMiltankFertilized.description>Fertilized miltank egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby miltank. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggMiltankFertilized.description>

  <EggShuckleFertilized.label>단단지 알 (유정)</EggShuckleFertilized.label>
  <EggShuckleFertilized.description>Fertilized shuckle egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby shuckle. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggShuckleFertilized.description>

  <EggNumelFertilized.label>둔타 알 (유정)</EggNumelFertilized.label>
  <EggNumelFertilized.description>Fertilized numel egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby numel. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggNumelFertilized.description>

  <EggCameruptFertilized.label>폭타 알 (유정)</EggCameruptFertilized.label>
  <EggCameruptFertilized.description>Fertilized camerupt egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby numel. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggCameruptFertilized.description>

  <EggCombeeFertilized.label>세꿀버리 알 (유정)</EggCombeeFertilized.label>
  <EggCombeeFertilized.description>Fertilized combee egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby combee. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggCombeeFertilized.description>

  <EggBayleefFertilized.label>베이리프 알 (유정)</EggBayleefFertilized.label>
  <EggBayleefFertilized.description>Fertilized bayleef egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby chikorita. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggBayleefFertilized.description>

  <EggMeganiumFertilized.label>메가니움 알 (유정)</EggMeganiumFertilized.label>
  <EggMeganiumFertilized.description>Fertilized Meganium egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby chikorita. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggMeganiumFertilized.description>

  <EggVespiquenFertilized.label>비퀸 알 (유정)</EggVespiquenFertilized.label>
  <EggVespiquenFertilized.description>Fertilized vespiquen egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby combee. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggVespiquenFertilized.description>

  <EggCroconawFertilized.label>엘리게이 알 (유정)</EggCroconawFertilized.label>
  <EggCroconawFertilized.description>Fertilized croconaw egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby totodile. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggCroconawFertilized.description>

  <EggFeraligatrFertilized.label>장크로다일 알 (유정)</EggFeraligatrFertilized.label>
  <EggFeraligatrFertilized.description>Fertilized feraligatr egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby totodile. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggFeraligatrFertilized.description>

  <EggCharizardFertilized.label>리자드 알 (유정)</EggCharizardFertilized.label>
  <EggCharizardFertilized.description>Fertilized charizard egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby charmander. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggCharizardFertilized.description>

  <EggPiplupFertilized.label>팽도리 알(유정)</EggPiplupFertilized.label>
  <EggPiplupFertilized.description>Fertilized piplup egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby piplup. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggPiplupFertilized.description>

  <EggPrinplupFertilized.label>팽태자 알 (유정)</EggPrinplupFertilized.label>
  <EggPrinplupFertilized.description>Fertilized prinplup egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby piplup. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggPrinplupFertilized.description>

  <EggEmpoleonFertilized.label>엠페르트 알 (유정)</EggEmpoleonFertilized.label>
  <EggEmpoleonFertilized.description>Fertilized empoleon egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby piplup. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggEmpoleonFertilized.description>

  <EggVenusaurFertilized.label>이상해꽃 알 (유정)</EggVenusaurFertilized.label>
  <EggVenusaurFertilized.description>Fertilized venusaur egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby bulbasaur. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggVenusaurFertilized.description>

  <EggBergmiteFertilized.label>꽁어름 알 (유정)</EggBergmiteFertilized.label>
  <EggBergmiteFertilized.description>Fertilized bergmite egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby bergmite. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggBergmiteFertilized.description>

  <EggGlaceonFertilized.label>글레이시아 알 (유정)</EggGlaceonFertilized.label>
  <EggGlaceonFertilized.description>Fertilized glaceon egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby glaceon. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggGlaceonFertilized.description>

  <EggQuilavaFertilized.label>마그케인 알 (유정)</EggQuilavaFertilized.label>
  <EggQuilavaFertilized.description>Fertilized quilava egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby cyndaquil. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggQuilavaFertilized.description>

  <EggTyphlosionFertilized.label>블레이범 알 (유정)</EggTyphlosionFertilized.label>
  <EggTyphlosionFertilized.description>Fertilized typhlosion egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby cyndaquil. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggTyphlosionFertilized.description>

  <EggBlastoiseFertilized.label>거북왕 알 (유정)</EggBlastoiseFertilized.label>
  <EggBlastoiseFertilized.description>Fertilized blastoise egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby squirtle. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggBlastoiseFertilized.description>

  <EggLaprasFertilized.label>라프라스 알 (유정)</EggLaprasFertilized.label>
  <EggLaprasFertilized.description>Fertilized lapras egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby lapras. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggLaprasFertilized.description>

  <EggSnoruntFertilized.label>눈꼬마 알 (유정)</EggSnoruntFertilized.label>
  <EggSnoruntFertilized.description>Fertilized snorunt egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby snorunt. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggSnoruntFertilized.description>

  <EggGlalieFertilized.label>얼음귀신 알 (유정)</EggGlalieFertilized.label>
  <EggGlalieFertilized.description>Fertilized glalie egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby snorunt. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggGlalieFertilized.description>

  <EggFroslassFertilized.label>눈여아 알 (유정)</EggFroslassFertilized.label>
  <EggFroslassFertilized.description>Fertilized froslass egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby snorunt. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggFroslassFertilized.description>

  <EggSneaselFertilized.label>포푸니 알 (유정)</EggSneaselFertilized.label>
  <EggSneaselFertilized.description>Fertilized sneasel egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby sneasel. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggSneaselFertilized.description>

  <SilkWurmple.label>실크</SilkWurmple.label>
  <SilkWurmple.description>Beautiful and soft silk.</SilkWurmple.description>
  <SilkWurmple.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>Silk</SilkWurmple.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>

  <ElectricWool.label>전기양털</ElectricWool.label>
  <ElectricWool.description>Charged wool from a fluffy pokémon. It feels a little strange if you touch it...</ElectricWool.description>
  <ElectricWool.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>Electric Wool</ElectricWool.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>

  <Honey.label>꿀</Honey.label>
  <Honey.description>Honey from an animal.</Honey.description>


</LanguageData>