<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- CHIKORITA -->

  <Chikorita.label>치코리타</Chikorita.label>
  <Chikorita.description>#152 Chikorita
Leaf Pokémon
Type: Grass

Pokédex entrie: It uses the leaf on its head to determine the temperature and humidity. It loves to sunbathe.

Chikorita is a small, pale green Pokémon with a darker necklace of buds. It has a large head in proportion to the rest of its body with large red eyes that appear to have no pupils. It has four short legs with a single nailed toe on each and a small tail. Its most distinguishing feature is the large leaf on the top of its head, which is usually longer than the rest of its body. Aside from the soothing aroma that wafts from its leaf, Chikorita uses its leaf to determine the temperature and humidity of the surrounding air. Chikorita actively seek out and enjoy the sun's warmth.</Chikorita.description>
  <Chikorita.tools.0.label>Tackle</Chikorita.tools.0.label>
  <Chikorita.tools.1.label>Razor Leaf</Chikorita.tools.1.label>
  <!-- No Leather: Butcher Products -->
  <Chikorita_Meat.label>허브향 고기</Chikorita_Meat.label>
  <Chikorita_Meat.description>허브향 고기</Chikorita_Meat.description>
  <Chikorita_Corpse.label>치코리타 시체</Chikorita_Corpse.label>
  <Chikorita_Corpse.description>치코리타 시체</Chikorita_Corpse.description>


  <!-- BAYLEEF -->

  <Bayleef.label>베이리프</Bayleef.label>
  <Bayleef.description>#153 Bayleef
Leaf Pokémon
Type: Grass

Pokédex entrie: Bayleef's neck is ringed by curled-up leaves. Inside each tubular leaf is a small shoot of a tree. The fragrance of this shoot makes people peppy.

Bayleef resembles a pale yellow sauropod dinosaur or a lizard. A large leaf shaped like a scythe protrudes from its head. Curled leaf-like growths, stated to be buds with small tree shoots inside, sprout in a ring around its neck. It has red eyes, a short, blunt snout, and a short, pointed tail. There is one large toenail on each of its four feet.

The aroma wafting from the leaf-like growths around its neck has a spicy scent, and exhibits various beneficial effects on itself, nearby people, or Pokémon who inhale it. The fragrance has a combination of energizing, stimulating, and healing effects. Bayleef can be rarely found in grasslands.</Bayleef.description>
  <Bayleef.tools.0.label>Body Slam</Bayleef.tools.0.label>
  <Bayleef.tools.1.label>Razor Leaf</Bayleef.tools.1.label>
  <Bayleef.tools.2.label>Magical Leaf</Bayleef.tools.2.label>
  <!-- No Leather: Butcher Products -->
  <!-- Use Meat From: Chikorita -->
  <Bayleef_Corpse.label>베이리프 시체</Bayleef_Corpse.label>
  <Bayleef_Corpse.description>베이리프 시체</Bayleef_Corpse.description>


  <!-- MEGANIUM -->

  <Meganium.label>메가니움</Meganium.label>
  <Meganium.description>#154 Meganium
Herb Pokémon
Type: Grass

Pokédex entrie: The fragrance of Meganium's flower soothes and calms emotions. In battle, this Pokémon gives off more of its becalming scent to blunt the foe's fighting spirit.

Meganium is a pale green, sauropod-like Pokémon with yellow eyes. It has two stamen-like protrusions sprouting from the top of its nose, each tipped with its own anther. These protrusions are shorter on the female. It has four feet, each of which have three toes. Large pink flower petals with a yellow central pattern and white tips encircle its neck. Additionally, it has a short, pointed tail.

It is said that Meganium's petals can release an aroma that can calm aggressive feelings, and its breath has the power to revive dead grass and plants. Its powerful and soothing regenerative powers can even affect those who stand nearby. Meganium tend to be a very docile species and has been portrayed as a peacemaker in the anime. Meganium can rarely be found living in grasslands.</Meganium.description>
  <Meganium.tools.0.label>Solar Beam</Meganium.tools.0.label>
  <Meganium.tools.1.label>Petal Blizzard</Meganium.tools.1.label>
  <Meganium.tools.2.label>Magical Leaf</Meganium.tools.2.label>
  <!-- No Leather: Butcher Products -->
  <!-- Use Meat From: Chikorita -->
  <Meganium_Corpse.label>메가니움 시체</Meganium_Corpse.label>
  <Meganium_Corpse.description>메가니움 시체</Meganium_Corpse.description>


  <!-- BULBASAUR -->

  <Bulbasaur.label>이상해씨</Bulbasaur.label>
  <Bulbasaur.description>#001 Bulbasaur
Seed Pokémon
Type: Grass/Poison

Pokédex entrie: Bulbasaur can be seen napping in bright sunlight. There is a seed on its back. By soaking up the sun's rays, the seed grows progressively larger.

Bulbasaur is a small, quadruped Pokémon that has blue-green skin with darker green patches. It has red eyes with white pupils and scleras. It also has pointed, ear-like structures on top of its head. Its snout is short and blunt, and it has a wide mouth. A pair of small, pointed teeth are visible in the upper jaw when its mouth is open. Each of its thick legs ends with three sharp claws. On its back is a green plant bulb, which is grown from a seed planted there at birth. The bulb provides it with energy through photosynthesis as well as from the nutrient-rich seeds contained within.

As mentioned in the anime, starter Pokémon are raised by Breeders to be distributed to new Trainers. Having been domesticated from birth, Bulbasaur is regarded as both a rare and well-behaved Pokémon. It is known to be extremely loyal, even after long-term abandonment. Bulbasaur has also shown itself to be an excellent caretaker, even having a special technique called the "Bulba-by." To perform this technique, Bulbasaur uses its vines to pick up a young Pokémon and soothingly rocks it in the air. It is found in grasslands and forests throughout the Kanto region. However, due to Bulbasaur's status as starter Pokémon, it is hard to come by in the wild and generally found under the ownership of a Trainer. It has been observed that a Bulbasaur's bulb will flash blue when it is ready to evolve. If it does not want to evolve, it struggles to resist the transformation. Many Bulbasaur gather every year in a hidden garden in Kanto to evolve into Ivysaur in a ceremony led by a Venusaur.</Bulbasaur.description>
  <Bulbasaur.tools.0.label>Tackle</Bulbasaur.tools.0.label>
  <Bulbasaur.tools.1.label>Vine Whip</Bulbasaur.tools.1.label>
  <!-- No Leather: Butcher Products -->
  <!-- Use Meat From: Chikorita -->
  <Bulbasaur_Corpse.label>이상해씨 시체</Bulbasaur_Corpse.label>
  <Bulbasaur_Corpse.description>이상해씨 시체</Bulbasaur_Corpse.description>


  <!-- IVYSAUR -->

  <Ivysaur.label>이상해풀</Ivysaur.label>
  <Ivysaur.description>#002 Ivysaur
Seed Pokémon
Type: Grass/Poison

Pokédex entrie: There is a bud on this Pokémon's back. To support its weight, Ivysaur's legs and trunk grow thick and strong. If it starts spending more time lying in the sunlight, it's a sign that the bud will bloom into a large flower soon.

Ivysaur is a quadruped Pokémon similar to a dinosaur. It has blue-green skin with darker patches. On top of its head are pointed ears with black insides, and it has narrow red eyes. It has a short, rounded snout with a wide mouth. Two pointed teeth protrude from its upper jaw. Each of its feet has three claws on them. The bulb on its back has bloomed into a large pink bud. A short brown trunk surrounded by leafy green fronds supports the bud. The weight of the plant prevents Ivysaur from standing on its hind legs and forces its legs to grow sturdy. When its flower is ready to bloom, it gives off a distinct, strong sweet-smelling aroma and starts swelling. Ivysaur will also start spending more time in sunlight in preparation for its upcoming evolution. Exposure to sunlight adds to the strength of both Ivysaur and its plant. Ivysaur's natural habitat is plains.</Ivysaur.description>
  <Ivysaur.tools.0.label>Vine Whip</Ivysaur.tools.0.label>
  <Ivysaur.tools.1.label>Razor Leaf</Ivysaur.tools.1.label>
  <Ivysaur.tools.2.label>Leech Seed</Ivysaur.tools.2.label>
  <!-- No Leather: Butcher Products -->
  <!-- Use Meat From: Chikorita -->
  <Ivysaur_Corpse.label>이상해풀 시체</Ivysaur_Corpse.label>
  <Ivysaur_Corpse.description>이상해풀 시체</Ivysaur_Corpse.description>


  <!-- VENUSAUR -->

  <Venusaur.label>이상해꽃</Venusaur.label>
  <Venusaur.description>#003 Venusaur
Seed Pokémon
Type: Grass/Poison

Pokédex entrie: There is a large flower on Venusaur's back. The flower is said to take on vivid colors if it gets plenty of nutrition and sunlight. The flower’s aroma soothes the emotions of people.

Venusaur is a squat, quadruped Pokémon with bumpy, blue-green skin. It has small, circular red eyes, a short, blunt snout, and a wide mouth with two pointed teeth in the upper jaw and four in the lower jaw. On top of its head are small, pointed ears with reddish pink insides. It has three clawed toes on each foot. The bud on its back has bloomed in a large pink, white-spotted flower. The flower is supported by a thick, brown trunk surrounded by green fronds. A female Venusaur will have a seed in the center of its flower.

As Mega Venusaur, the flower on its back grows larger and two smaller pink flowers bloom, one on its forehead and one on its rear. The weight of the flower causes its legs to become sturdier in order to support it.[1] Additional leaves with woody stems, which are supported by vines, are grown around the flower. Mega Venusaur also develops dark markings on its forehead below the new flower.

Venusaur uses its flower to catch the sun's rays to convert them into energy, which causes the flower to take on colors that are more vibrant. The flower releases a soothing scent that attracts Pokémon. This scent becomes stronger after a rainy day. In the anime, Venusaur has demonstrated the ability to manipulate nature, release several vines from its back and lead evolution ceremonies for Bulbasaur and Ivysaur. Frenzy Plant was its signature move in the past. This Pokémon is rarely found in the wild but has been known to inhabit grasslands.</Venusaur.description>
  <Venusaur.tools.0.label>Solar Beam</Venusaur.tools.0.label>
  <Venusaur.tools.1.label>Petal Dance</Venusaur.tools.1.label>
  <Venusaur.tools.2.label>Double Edge</Venusaur.tools.2.label>
  <!-- No Leather: Butcher Products -->
  <!-- Use Meat From: Chikorita -->
  <Venusaur_Corpse.label>이상해꽃 시체</Venusaur_Corpse.label>
  <Venusaur_Corpse.description>이상해꽃 시체</Venusaur_Corpse.description>


  <!-- TURTWIG -->

  <Turtwig.label>모부기</Turtwig.label>
  <Turtwig.description>#387 Turtwig
Tiny Leaf Pokémon
Type: Grass

Pokédex entrie: It undertakes photosynthesis with its body, making oxygen. The leaf on its head wilts if it is thirsty.

Turtwig is a small, light green, quadruped Pokémon resembling a turtle or tortoise. Its eyes, feet, and lower jaw are yellow. Its body is covered by a brown shell that is composed of earth. The shell has a thick black stripe and a black rim. On a very healthy Turtwig, the shell should feel moist. A small seedling grows on a brown patch on its head. This seedling will wilt if the Pokémon becomes thirsty. As a plant-based Pokémon, Turtwig usually nourishes itself through photosynthesis. It also drinks water, which hardens its soil-based shell.</Turtwig.description>
  <Turtwig.tools.0.label>Tackle</Turtwig.tools.0.label>
  <Turtwig.tools.1.label>Razor Leaf</Turtwig.tools.1.label>
  <!-- No Leather: Butcher Products -->
  <!-- Use Meat From: Chikorita -->
  <Turtwig_Corpse.label>모부기 시체</Turtwig_Corpse.label>
  <Turtwig_Corpse.description>모부기 시체</Turtwig_Corpse.description>


  <!-- ODDISH -->

  <Oddish.label>뚜벅초</Oddish.label>
  <Oddish.description>#043 Oddish
Weed Pokémon
Type: Grass/Poison

Pokédex entrie: Oddish searches for fertile, nutrient-rich soil, then plants itself. During the daytime, while it is planted, this Pokémon's feet are thought to change shape and become similar to the roots of trees..

Oddish resembles a blue plant bulb with a round body, beady red eyes, and oval, foot-like roots. Five large, green leaves sprout from its head. As demonstrated in the anime, these leaves are prehensile and can be used to scale vertical surfaces and catch light objects.

Known by the scientific name Oddium Wanderus, Oddish lives in grasslands. A nocturnal Pokémon, Oddish buries its sensitive body in the ground during the day to avoid the sun and fool predators. If its leaves are pulled in this state, it will respond by shrieking horribly. It starts to move when its leaves begin absorbing moonlight, which it uses to grow. Oddish will wander up to 1000 feet (300 meters) during the night to scatter its seeds and find a nutrient-rich patch of soil in which to plant itself. The more fertile the earth, the glossier its leaves will be. It is thought that its feet become like tree roots while planted. In the past, Petal Dance was its signature move.</Oddish.description>
  <Oddish.tools.0.label>Absorb</Oddish.tools.0.label>
  <Oddish.tools.1.label>Poison Powder</Oddish.tools.1.label>
  <!-- No Leather: Butcher Products -->
  <!-- Use Meat From: Chikorita -->
  <Oddish_Corpse.label>모부기 시체</Oddish_Corpse.label>
  <Oddish_Corpse.description>모부기 시체</Oddish_Corpse.description>


  <!-- BELLSPROUT -->

  <Bellsprout.label>모다피</Bellsprout.label>
  <Bellsprout.description>#069 Bellsprout
Flower Pokémon
Type: Grass/Poison

Pokédex entrie: Bellsprout's thin and flexible body lets it bend and sway to avoid any attack, however strong it may be. From its mouth, this Pokémon spits a corrosive fluid that melts even iron.

Bellsprout is a plant-based Pokémon with a stem-like brown body. This stem is long, thin and very flexible, making it capable of swerving rapidly to avoid many attacks or moving with blinding speed to capture prey. Its roots resemble feet, and it uses them as such. It will plant these feet in the ground to replenish water, but it is unable to flee while it is rooted. It has one green leaf on each side of its body. Its yellow head is bell-shaped and has what appear to be pink lips at the end. Bellsprout prefers hot and humid places, living in forests.</Bellsprout.description>
  <Bellsprout.tools.0.label>Wrap</Bellsprout.tools.0.label>
  <Bellsprout.tools.1.label>Vine Whip</Bellsprout.tools.1.label>
  <!-- No Leather: Butcher Products -->
  <!-- Use Meat From: Chikorita -->
  <Bellsprout_Corpse.label>모다피 시체</Bellsprout_Corpse.label>
  <Bellsprout_Corpse.description>모다피 시체</Bellsprout_Corpse.description>


  <!-- HOPPIP -->

  <Hoppip.label>통통코</Hoppip.label>
  <Hoppip.description>#187 Hoppip
Cottonweed Pokémon
Type: Grass/Flying

Pokédex entrie: This Pokémon drifts and floats with the wind. If it senses the approach of strong winds, Hoppip links its leaves with other Hoppip to prepare against being blown away.

Hoppip is a round, pink Pokémon with long green leaves growing on top of its head. The leaves on its head have ragged edges, similar to a dandelion. It has big, triangular ears with dark insides and beady yellow eyes that lack pupils. Its arms and legs are stubby, and it has a short tail with a rounded tip. There is a circular yellow pad on the underside of each foot.

Hoppip's body is very light, and it is easily lifted off the ground by winds and will drift in the air. Hoppip can sense approaching strong winds. In order to avoid being blown away, it clusters and links leaves with other Hoppip or grips the ground firmly with its feet. However, it enjoys gentle breezes. Hoppip lives in grasslands, although some also drift through fields, mountains, and even urban environments.</Hoppip.description>
  <Hoppip.tools.0.label>Absorb</Hoppip.tools.0.label>
  <Hoppip.tools.1.label>Fairy Wind</Hoppip.tools.1.label>
  <!-- No Leather: Butcher Products -->
  <!-- Use Meat From: Chikorita -->
  <Hoppip_Corpse.label>통통코 시체</Hoppip_Corpse.label>
  <Hoppip_Corpse.description>통통코 시체</Hoppip_Corpse.description>


  <!-- CHERUBI -->

  <Cherubi.label>체리버</Cherubi.label>
  <Cherubi.description>#420 Cherubi
Cherry Pokémon
Type: Grass

Pokédex entrie: It evolves by sucking the energy out of the small ball where it had been storing nutrients.

Cherubi is a small cherry-like Pokémon with a round, deep-pink body with two stubby feet. It has beady eyes and a purple-red stripe running down part of its face. Cherubi has a short stem with two big, green leaves and a second, much smaller head growing out of it. This second head is vestigial in terms of function, but it contains nutrients that contribute to Cherubi's growth as its initial source of food. As the second head is apparently edible, several Pokémon have been seen trying to pluck it off. When the second head begins to bloom it means Cherubi is close to evolving. It has been known to sun bathe on warm days. When it is about to evolve, the second head starts to wilt. Cherubi mainly photosynthesizes, and it is attracted to honey. Starly is a natural predator of Cherubi.</Cherubi.description>
  <Cherubi.tools.0.label>Leech Seed</Cherubi.tools.0.label>
  <Cherubi.tools.1.label>Magical Leaf</Cherubi.tools.1.label>
  <Cherubi.tools.2.label>Solar Beam</Cherubi.tools.2.label>
  <!-- No Leather: Butcher Products -->
  <!-- Use Meat From: Chikorita -->
  <Cherubi_Corpse.label>체리버 시체</Cherubi_Corpse.label>
  <Cherubi_Corpse.description>체리버 시체</Cherubi_Corpse.description>


</LanguageData>