<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- EEVEE -->

  <Eevee.label>이브이</Eevee.label>
  <Eevee.description>#133 이브이
Evolution Pokémon
Type: Normal

Pokédex entrie: Possessing an unbalanced and unstable genetic makeup, it conceals many possible evolutions.

Eevee is a mammalian, quadruped creature with primarily brown fur. The tip of its bushy tail and its large furry collar are cream-colored. It has short, slender legs with three small toes and a pink paw pad on each foot. Eevee has brown eyes, long pointed ears, and a small black nose. This Pokémon is rarely found in the wild, and is mostly only found in cities and towns. However, Eevee is said to have an irregularly shaped genetic structure that allows it to adapt to many different kinds of environments. Eventually, Eevee may evolve to better suit its surroundings.</Eevee.description>
  <Eevee.tools.0.label>Tackle</Eevee.tools.0.label>
  <Eevee.tools.1.label>Sand Attack</Eevee.tools.1.label>
  <Eevee.tools.2.label>Swift</Eevee.tools.2.label>
  <Eevee_Leather.label>이브이 가죽</Eevee_Leather.label>
  <Eevee_Leather.description>이브이 가죽</Eevee_Leather.description>
  <Eevee_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>이브이 가죽</Eevee_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <Eevee_Meat.label>평범한 고기</Eevee_Meat.label>
  <Eevee_Meat.description>평범한 고기</Eevee_Meat.description>
  <Eevee_Corpse.label>이브이 시체</Eevee_Corpse.label>
  <Eevee_Corpse.description>이브이 시체</Eevee_Corpse.description>


  <!-- ZIGZAGOON -->

  <Zigzagoon.label>지그제구리</Zigzagoon.label>
  <Zigzagoon.description>#263 지그제구리
Tiny Racoon Pokémon
Type: Normal

Pokédex entrie: Zigzagoon restlessly wanders everywhere at all times. This Pokémon does so because it is very curious. It becomes interested in anything that it happens to see.

Zigzagoon is a raccoon-like, quadruped Pokémon with bristly, zigzag-patterned fur. It has stripes formed by alternating layers of cream and brown fur. It has a brown head with spiky ears and a black nose. A black, mask pattern surrounds its brown eyes. The upper half of its mouth is jagged, and when it is open, there are two pointed teeth in its lower jaw. Its feet have three claws and pink paw pads. Its forefeet are cream-colored, but the hind feet are brown. Its brush tail is spiky and bristly.

Zigzagoon is abundantly curious, as it wanders restlessly back and forth while rubbing its nose to the ground in search of something. It rubs its bristly back hair against trees to mark its territory, and plays dead to fool opponents in battle. Zigzagoon is found commonly in grassy fields.</Zigzagoon.description>
  <Zigzagoon.tools.0.label>Headbutt</Zigzagoon.tools.0.label>
  <Zigzagoon.tools.1.label>Pin Missle</Zigzagoon.tools.1.label>
  <Zigzagoon.tools.2.label>Tail Whip</Zigzagoon.tools.2.label>
  <Zigzagoon_Leather.label>지그제구리 가죽</Zigzagoon_Leather.label>
  <Zigzagoon_Leather.description>지그제구리 가죽</Zigzagoon_Leather.description>
  <Zigzagoon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>지그제구리 가죽</Zigzagoon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Eevee -->
  <Zigzagoon_Corpse.label>지그제구리 시체</Zigzagoon_Corpse.label>
  <Zigzagoon_Corpse.description>지그제구리 시체</Zigzagoon_Corpse.description>


  <!-- DODUO -->

  <Doduo.label>두두</Doduo.label>
  <Doduo.description>#084 Doduo
Twin Bird Pokémon
Type: Normal/Flying

Pokédex entrie: The brains in its two heads appear to communicate emotions to each other with telepathic power.

Doduo is a two-headed, bipedal avian Pokémon. Each head has a long sharp beak and two beady black eyes with no discernible sclerae. It has a soft but bristly, down-like covering of brown feathers on its body and both heads. The males of the species have black flexible necks, whereas females have brown necks; both genders have brown coloring on their legs. It has two feet, each with four digits ending in a sharp claw.

Even when sleeping or nourishing itself with food and water, one head is always awake and alert and keeps a keen eye out for enemies. Both heads have an identical brain. However, it is believed that on occasion they may possess different sets of brains. It is also theorized that the two heads communicate with some form of telepathy to be coordinated with one another. Due to its almost non-existent wings, it cannot fly very well but has developed its legs to be a very powerful runner. Reaching speeds of 60 mph (96.5 km/h), it energetically strides across the plains leaving large, 4" (10.6 cm) deep foot prints behind it. Doduo lives in wide open plains, grasslands, and savannahs.</Doduo.description>
  <Doduo.tools.0.label>Uproar</Doduo.tools.0.label>
  <Doduo.tools.1.label>Peck</Doduo.tools.1.label>
  <Doduo.tools.2.label>Fury Attack</Doduo.tools.2.label>
  <Doduo_Leather.label>두두 가죽</Doduo_Leather.label>
  <Doduo_Leather.description>두두 가죽</Doduo_Leather.description>
  <Doduo_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>두두 가죽</Doduo_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Eevee -->
  <Doduo_Corpse.label>두두 시체</Doduo_Corpse.label>
  <Doduo_Corpse.description>두두 시체</Doduo_Corpse.description>


  <!-- MILTANK -->

  <Miltank.label>밀탱크</Miltank.label>
  <Miltank.description>#241 Miltank
Milk Cow Pokémon
Type: Normal

Pokédex entrie: Most people raise it for its milk, but it's quite tough and strong, so it's also well suited for battle.

Miltank is a bipedal, bovine Pokémon, which can only be female. Its body is mostly pink, with a yellow belly and black, angular markings along its back. A black hood-like marking surrounds its face with a pink, triangular mark on its forehead. There are two small horns on top of its head. It has large, blue eyes, a black nose, and a wide mouth, as well as long, black, floppy ears with yellow insides. Miltank has a yellow udder with four pink teats. All four of its limbs end in black, cloven hooves, and its long tail is tipped with a black sphere.</Miltank.description>
  <Miltank.tools.0.label>Body Slam</Miltank.tools.0.label>
  <Miltank.tools.1.label>Zen Headbutt</Miltank.tools.1.label>
  <Miltank.tools.2.label>Wake Up Slap</Miltank.tools.2.label>
  <Miltank_Leather.label>밀탱크 가죽</Miltank_Leather.label>
  <Miltank_Leather.description>밀탱크 가죽</Miltank_Leather.description>
  <Miltank_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>밀탱크 가죽</Miltank_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Eevee -->
  <Miltank_Corpse.label>밀탱크 시체</Miltank_Corpse.label>
  <Miltank_Corpse.description>밀탱크 시체</Miltank_Corpse.description>


  <!-- TAUROS -->

  <Tauros.label>켄타로스</Tauros.label>
  <Tauros.description>#128 Tauros
Wild Bull Pokémon
Type: Normal

Pokédex entrie: This Pokémon is not satisfied unless it is rampaging at all times. If there is no opponent for Tauros to battle, it will charge at thick trees and knock them down to calm itself.

Tauros is a quadruped, bovine Pokémon. It is covered in light brown fur with a thick, darker brown mane around the neck. It has a rounded muzzle with a dark brown nose, and three gray bumps running vertically down its forehead. A pair of curved, gray horns grows from atop its head. Each of its three black tails has a tuft of fur on the end, and there is a single gray hoof on each foot. Tauros is a male-only species with no true female counterpart.

Tauros is a violent, rowdy Pokémon that whips itself into a frenzy using its three tails. Once it starts charging, it is unable to stop or change course until it hits something. It lives and travels in herds on plains and grasslands. It will lock horns with others of its kind, and the herd's protector takes pride in its battle-scarred horns.</Tauros.description>
  <Tauros.tools.0.label>Horn Attack</Tauros.tools.0.label>
  <Tauros.tools.1.label>Thrash</Tauros.tools.1.label>
  <Tauros.tools.2.label>Double Edge</Tauros.tools.2.label>
  <Tauros_Leather.label>켄타로스 가죽</Tauros_Leather.label>
  <Tauros_Leather.description>켄타로스 가죽</Tauros_Leather.description>
  <Tauros_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>켄타로스 가죽</Tauros_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Eevee -->
  <Tauros_Corpse.label>켄타로스 시체</Tauros_Corpse.label>
  <Tauros_Corpse.description>켄타로스 시체</Tauros_Corpse.description>


</LanguageData>