<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- NIDORAN -->

  <Nidoran.label>니드런</Nidoran.label>
  <Nidoran.description>#032 니드런
Poison Pin Pokémon
Type: Poison

Pokédex entrie: The male Nidoran has developed muscles that freely move its ears in any direction. Even the slightest sound does not escape this Pokémon's notice. Nidoran♀ has barbs that secrete a powerful poison. They are thought to have developed as protection for this small-bodied Pokémon. When enraged, it releases a horrible toxin from its horn.

Nidoran♂ is a small, quadruped rodent-like Pokémon. It is pinkish purple with darker spots, and has large, spiny ears with teal insides, oversized front teeth, and red eyes. Its back is covered with three lines of large spines that can release potent poisons if threatened. The center line of spines is taller than the other two. The size of the long, pointed horn on its forehead is indicative of the strength of its venom. Nidoran♂ is an exclusively male Pokémon, Nidoran♀ being its female counterpart.

Nidoran♂ constantly listens for the sounds of approaching enemies with its large ears. Said ears have unique muscles that allow them to be moved in any direction, and even the slightest sound does not escape Nidoran♂'s notice. In order to listen to distant locations, it flaps its ears like wings. When angry, it extends its toxic spikes and charges, stabbing with its horn to inject poison. Nidoran♂ lives in open spaces, such as savannas and plains.</Nidoran.description>
  <Nidoran.tools.0.label>Horn Attack</Nidoran.tools.0.label>
  <Nidoran.tools.1.label>Poison Sting</Nidoran.tools.1.label>
  <Nidoran_Leather.label>니드런 가죽</Nidoran_Leather.label>
  <Nidoran_Leather.description>니드런 가죽</Nidoran_Leather.description>
  <Nidoran_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>니드런 가죽</Nidoran_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <Nidoran_Meat.label>보라색 고기</Nidoran_Meat.label>
  <Nidoran_Meat.description>보라색 고기</Nidoran_Meat.description>
  <Nidoran_Corpse.label>니드런 시체</Nidoran_Corpse.label>
  <Nidoran_Corpse.description>니드런 시체</Nidoran_Corpse.description>


  <!-- 니드리나/니드리노 -->

  <NidorinaNidorino.label>니드리나/니드리노</NidorinaNidorino.label>
  <NidorinaNidorino.description>#030 니드리나/#033 니드리노
Poison Pin Pokémon
Type: Poison

Pokédex entrie: Nidorino has a horn that is harder than a diamond. If it senses a hostile presence, all the barbs on its back bristle up at once, and it challenges the foe with all its might. The female's horn develops slowly. Prefers physical attacks such as clawing and biting.

Nidorina is a quadruped, light-blue Pokémon with darker blue patches. It has red eyes, large, spiny ears, and has two pointed teeth protruding from its upper jaw. It possesses large poison spikes, which it retracts whenever it is with a group and while resting in its burrow. Its paws have three claws each, and it is able to stand on its hind legs. The hind legs are longer and thicker than its forelegs. It has a stubby tail. This is a female only species; the male counterpart is Nidorino.

Nidorina is a gentle Pokémon, known to be a caring mother that chews food for its young. It seems to display close family bonds with others of its kind, and becomes nervous when separated. Nidorina prefers not to fight since its horn grows slowly, but if forced or enraged, it prefers physical attacks such as clawing and biting. It also emits ultrasonic cries to befuddle foes. Nidorina live in burrows at hot savannas and plains.

Nidorino is a light purple, quadruped Pokémon. It has several darker purple spots across its body. It has large, spiny ears with teal insides, narrow black eyes, and a long snout with two pointed teeth protruding from the upper jaw. It has a ridge of toxic spines on its back, and a long, pointed horn on its forehead. The horn is harder than a diamond and capable of secreting poison on impact. Its short legs have three claws on each foot. This is a male only species; the female counterpart is Nidorina.

Nidorino is independent and fierce, often described as violent and easily angered. It uses its ears to check its surroundings. If it senses a hostile presence, all the barbs on its back bristle up at once, and it challenges the foe with all its might. Nidorino live in hot savannas and plains.</NidorinaNidorino.description>
  <NidorinaNidorino.tools.0.label>Toxic Spikes</NidorinaNidorino.tools.0.label>
  <NidorinaNidorino.tools.1.label>Fury Attack</NidorinaNidorino.tools.1.label>
  <NidorinaNidorino.tools.2.label>Poison Fang</NidorinaNidorino.tools.2.label>
  <NidorinaNidorino_Leather.label>니드리나/니드리노 가죽</NidorinaNidorino_Leather.label>
  <NidorinaNidorino_Leather.description>니드리나/니드리노 가죽</NidorinaNidorino_Leather.description>
  <NidorinaNidorino_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>니드리나/니드리노 가죽</NidorinaNidorino_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Nidoran -->
  <NidorinaNidorino_Corpse.label>니드리나/니드리노 시체</NidorinaNidorino_Corpse.label>
  <NidorinaNidorino_Corpse.description>니드리나/니드리노 시체</NidorinaNidorino_Corpse.description>


  <!-- 니드킹/니드퀸 -->

  <NidokingNidoqueen.label>니드킹/니드퀸</NidokingNidoqueen.label>
  <NidokingNidoqueen.description>#032 니드킹/#니드퀸
Drill Pokémon
Type: Poison/Ground

Pokédex entrie: Nidoking's thick tail packs enormously destructive power. With one swing, it can topple a metal transmission tower. Once this Pokémon goes on a rampage, there is no stopping it. Nidoqueen's body is encased in extremely hard scales. It is adept at sending foes flying with harsh tackles. This Pokémon is at its strongest when it is defending its young. 

Nidoking is a large, bipedal, purple Pokémon with distinct reptilian features. It has narrow eyes, large, spiny ears, fur-like tufts on its cheeks, and a short snout filled with pointed teeth. There is a long, venomous horn on its forehead and a ridge of spines down its back. Gray plates cover its chest and belly, and there is a gray rounded spine on each elbow. Each hand was three claws, while foot has only a single hoof-like nail. It has a long, powerful tail. This is a male only species; the female counterpart is Nidoqueen.

It is said that Nidoking's tail is capable of toppling a metal transmission tower. Nidoking uses this tail to smash, constrict, or break the bones of its prey and enemies. The tail can be swung to create distance between it and its foes before Nidoking charges. Its steel-like hide adds to its powerful, rampaging charges. Nidoking lives in grasslands.


Nidoqueen is a large, bipedal blue Pokémon with distinct reptilian features. Its body is encased with extremely hard scales that serve as excellent protection from any attack and stand up when Nidoqueen is excited or provoked. It has a blunt snout, narrow brown eyes, and large ears with brown insides. There is a small horn on its forehead, and single spine on each ear, and there is a line of toxic spikes running down the length of its back. Each hand has three short claws and each foot was two claws. Its lower jaw, the front of its abdomen, and two plates on its chest are cream-colored. It has a thick, powerful tail.

Nidoqueen can be quite fierce and is very protective over its young. This Pokémon is at its strongest when it is defending its young, and will try to seal the entrance to its burrow to protect them. When in contact with foes, it can poison them with the spikes from its back or cause small tremors by slamming the ground. It is also adept at sending foes flying with harsh tackles and it uses its hefty bulk to execute powerful moves. Nidoqueen lives in hot savannas and plains.</NidokingNidoqueen.description>
  <NidokingNidoqueen.tools.0.label>Earth Power</NidokingNidoqueen.tools.0.label>
  <NidokingNidoqueen.tools.1.label>Double Kick</NidokingNidoqueen.tools.1.label>
  <NidokingNidoqueen.tools.2.label>Chip Away</NidokingNidoqueen.tools.2.label>
  <NidokingNidoqueen_Leather.label>니드킹/니드퀸 가죽</NidokingNidoqueen_Leather.label>
  <NidokingNidoqueen_Leather.description>니드킹/니드퀸 가죽</NidokingNidoqueen_Leather.description>
  <NidokingNidoqueen_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>니드킹/니드퀸 가죽</NidokingNidoqueen_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Nidoran -->
  <NidokingNidoqueen_Corpse.label>니드킹/니드퀸 시체</NidokingNidoqueen_Corpse.label>
  <NidokingNidoqueen_Corpse.description>니드킹/니드퀸 시체</NidokingNidoqueen_Corpse.description>


  <!-- ZUBAT -->

  <Zubat.label>주뱃</Zubat.label>
  <Zubat.description>#041 주뱃
Bat Pokémon
Type: Poison/Flying

Pokédex entrie: While flying, it constantly emits ultrasonic waves from its mouth to check its surroundings.

Zubat is a blue, bat-like Pokémon. While it lacks eyes, it has pointed ears with purple insides and a mouth with two sharp teeth on each jaw. A male will have larger fangs than the female. It has purple wing membranes support by two, elongated fingers, and two long, thin, tails.

Zubat lives in abundance in caves. It has evolved to have neither eyes nor nostrils, instead navigating through dark environments with echolocation. As demonstrated in the anime, it will leave its abode at night with a mass of other Zubat in order to seek prey. During the daytime, Zubat sleeps hanging upside down in caves, forests, or under the eaves of old buildings, avoiding sunlight at all costs. Daylight causes Zubat to become unhealthy, and prolonged exposure can even burn its skin. However, captured and trained Zubat have been recorded as being much more tenacious in the daytime, even when directly exposed to sunbeams. .</Zubat.description>
  <Zubat.tools.0.label>Bite</Zubat.tools.0.label>
  <Zubat.tools.1.label>Poison Fang</Zubat.tools.1.label>
  <Zubat_Leather.label>주뱃 가죽</Zubat_Leather.label>
  <Zubat_Leather.description>주뱃 가죽</Zubat_Leather.description>
  <Zubat_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>주뱃 가죽</Zubat_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Nidoran -->
  <Zubat_Corpse.label>주뱃 시체</Zubat_Corpse.label>
  <Zubat_Corpse.description>주뱃 시체</Zubat_Corpse.description>


</LanguageData>