<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- CYNDAQUIL -->

  <Cyndaquil.label>브케인</Cyndaquil.label>
  <Cyndaquil.description>#155 Cyndaquil
Fire Mouse Pokémon
Type: Fire

Pokédex entrie: It usually stays hunched over. If it is angry or surprised, it shoots flames out of its back.

Cyndaquil is a small, bipedal Pokémon with bluish fur on top of its body, and a milky color on the underside. Cyndaquil seems to be a composite of features from the echidna and the shrew. The echidna features are the flames from its back, while its general body shape is shrew-like. Its eyes are often closed and it has a long, thin snout. It lacks claws on its forelimbs, but has a single claw on each hind foot. Cyndaquil is usually timid by nature and often curls into a ball when intimidated. It has four red spots on its back from which its flames erupt. Cyndaquil is capable of defending itself using these flames. The fire grows more powerful as Cyndaquil becomes more angry or defensive. Though rare in the wild, few can be found living on grasslands.</Cyndaquil.description>
  <Cyndaquil.tools.0.label>Tackle</Cyndaquil.tools.0.label>
  <Cyndaquil.tools.1.label>Ember</Cyndaquil.tools.1.label>
  <Cyndaquil_Leather.label>브케인 가죽</Cyndaquil_Leather.label>
  <Cyndaquil_Leather.description>브케인 가죽</Cyndaquil_Leather.description>
  <Cyndaquil_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>브케인 가죽</Cyndaquil_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <Cyndaquil_Meat.label>활활거리는 고기</Cyndaquil_Meat.label>
  <Cyndaquil_Meat.description>활활거리는 고기</Cyndaquil_Meat.description>
  <Cyndaquil_Corpse.label>브케인 시체</Cyndaquil_Corpse.label>
  <Cyndaquil_Corpse.description>브케인 시체</Cyndaquil_Corpse.description>


  <!-- QUILAVA -->

  <Quilava.label>마그케인</Quilava.label>
  <Quilava.description>#156 Quilava
Volcano Pokémon
Type: Fire

Pokédex entrie: Quilava keeps its foes at bay with the intensity of its flames and gusts of superheated air. This Pokémon applies its outstanding nimbleness to dodge attacks even while scorching the foes with flames.

Quilava is a slim quadruped Pokémon. The top half of its body is blue, while the lower half is cream. Its ears are triangular with red insides, and it possesses a rounded nose and red eyes. It has five red spots on its body that can project flames: two in a somewhat exclamation-mark shape on its forehead and three lined up horizontally on its rear. The fire coming from its head and rear can be launched as a flame attack. It also uses gusts of superheated air as a battle technique. Quilava's fur is non-flammable, so it can withstand flame attacks. Quilava tends to be rare in the wild, but can sometimes be found living on grasslands.</Quilava.description>
  <Quilava.tools.0.label>Flame Wheel</Quilava.tools.0.label>
  <Quilava.tools.1.label>Flame Charge</Quilava.tools.1.label>
  <Quilava.tools.2.label>Lava Plume</Quilava.tools.2.label>
  <Quilava_Leather.label>마그케인 가죽</Quilava_Leather.label>
  <Quilava_Leather.description>마그케인 가죽</Quilava_Leather.description>
  <Quilava_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>마그케인 가죽</Quilava_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Cyndaquil -->
  <Quilava_Corpse.label>마그케인 시체</Quilava_Corpse.label>
  <Quilava_Corpse.description>마그케인 시체</Quilava_Corpse.description>


  <!-- TYPHLOSION -->

  <Typhlosion.label>블레이범</Typhlosion.label>
  <Typhlosion.description>#157 Typhlosion
Volcano Pokémon
Type: Fire

Pokédex entrie: Typhlosion obscures itself behind a shimmering heat haze that it creates using its intensely hot flames. This Pokémon creates blazing explosive blasts that burn everything to cinders. 

Typhlosion is a badger-like Pokémon with a bulky yet agile body. Typhlosion is classified as a quadruped, but it is capable of bipedal movement and is frequently depicted standing on its hind legs. When its mouth is open, it shows its thick tongue and sharp canines. It has a short snout and small eyes and ears. Typhlosion's face, underside, arms, and legs are a shade of cream, and its back is dark blue. On Typhlosion’s rear, there is a spiky, coarse fringe of fur. Across the back of its neck, there are several red spots that produce fire in battle. Typhlosion will make anything go up in flames when angered, and generates shimmering heat from its body when it is ready for battle. Though it is rare in the wild, some can be found living on grasslands.</Typhlosion.description>
  <Typhlosion.tools.0.label>Burn Up</Typhlosion.tools.0.label>
  <Typhlosion.tools.1.label>Eruption</Typhlosion.tools.1.label>
  <Typhlosion.tools.2.label>Inferno</Typhlosion.tools.2.label>
  <Typhlosion_Leather.label>블레이범 가죽</Typhlosion_Leather.label>
  <Typhlosion_Leather.description>블레이범 가죽</Typhlosion_Leather.description>
  <Typhlosion_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>블레이범 가죽</Typhlosion_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Cyndaquil -->
  <Typhlosion_Corpse.label>블레이범 시체</Typhlosion_Corpse.label>
  <Typhlosion_Corpse.description>블레이범 시체</Typhlosion_Corpse.description>


  <!-- FLAREON -->

  <Flareon.label>Flareon</Flareon.label>
  <Flareon.description>#136 Flareon
Flame Pokémon
Type: Fire

Pokédex entrie: When it catches prey or finds berries, it breathes fire on them until they're well done, and then it gobbles them up.

Flareon is a mammalian, quadruped Pokémon covered in short, reddish-orange fur. It has long ears, dark eyes, and a small black nose. There are three small toes and a yellow paw pad on each foot. Fluffy yellow fur forms a small tuft on its head, as well as its bushy tail and a mane around its chest and neck. It will fluff out its collar to cool down its high body temperature. This high temperature is caused by its internal flame sac. Flareon stores and heats inhaled air in this sac, and then exhales it as fire. It is an omnivore who roasts either Berries or prey before consumption. Flareon is mostly found in populated areas, and is rarely seen in the wilderness.</Flareon.description>
  <Flareon.tools.0.label>Smog</Flareon.tools.0.label>
  <Flareon.tools.1.label>Ember</Flareon.tools.1.label>
  <Flareon.tools.2.label>Fire Fang</Flareon.tools.2.label>
  <Flareon_Leather.label>부스터 가죽</Flareon_Leather.label>
  <Flareon_Leather.description>부스터 가죽</Flareon_Leather.description>
  <Flareon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>부스터 가죽</Flareon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Cyndaquil -->
  <Flareon_Corpse.label>부스터 시체</Flareon_Corpse.label>
  <Flareon_Corpse.description>부스터 시체</Flareon_Corpse.description>


  <!-- CHARMANDER -->

  <Charmander.label>파이리</Charmander.label>
  <Charmander.description>#004 Charmander
Lizard Pokémon
Type: Fire

Pokédex entrie: The flame that burns at the tip of its tail is an indication of its emotions. The flame wavers when Charmander is enjoying itself. If the Pokémon becomes enraged, the flame burns fiercely.

Charmander is a bipedal, reptilian Pokémon with a primarily orange body. Its underside from the chest down and soles are cream-colored. It has two small fangs visible in its upper jaw and two smaller fangs in its lower jaw. Charmander has blue eyes. Its arms and legs are short with four fingers and three clawed toes. A fire burns at the tip of this Pokémon's slender tail and has blazed there since Charmander's birth. The flame can be used as an indication of Charmander's health and mood, burning brightly when the Pokémon is strong, weakly when it is exhausted, wavering when it is happy, and blazing when it is enraged. It is said that Charmander dies if its flame goes out. However, if the Pokémon is healthy, the flame will continue to burn even if it gets a bit wet and is said to steam in the rain.

Charmander can be found in hot, mountainous areas. However, it is found far more often in the ownership of Trainers. As shown in Pokémon Snap, Charmander exhibits pack behavior, calling others of its species if it finds food.</Charmander.description>
  <Charmander.tools.0.label>Scratch</Charmander.tools.0.label>
  <Charmander.tools.1.label>Ember</Charmander.tools.1.label>
  <Charmander_Leather.label>파이리 가죽</Charmander_Leather.label>
  <Charmander_Leather.description>파이리 가죽</Charmander_Leather.description>
  <Charmander_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>파이리 가죽</Charmander_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Cyndaquil -->
  <Charmander_Corpse.label>파이리 시체</Charmander_Corpse.label>
  <Charmander_Corpse.description>파이리 시체</Charmander_Corpse.description>


  <!-- CHARMELEON -->

  <Charmeleon.label>리자드</Charmeleon.label>
  <Charmeleon.description>#005 Charmeleon
Flame Pokémon
Type: Fire

Pokédex entrie: Charmeleon mercilessly destroys its foes using its sharp claws. If it encounters a strong foe, it turns aggressive. In this excited state, the flame at the tip of its tail flares with a bluish white color.

Charmeleon is a bipedal, reptilian creature. It has bright-red scales and a cream underside. There is a horn-like protrusion on the back of its head, and it has narrow blue eyes and a long snout. It has relatively long arms with three sharp claws. Its short legs have feet with three claws and cream-colored soles. The tip of its long, powerful tail has a flame burning on it. The temperature rises to unbearable levels if Charmeleon swings its tail.

Charmeleon has a vicious nature and will constantly seek out opponents. Strong opponents excite this Pokémon, causing it to spout bluish-white flames that torch its surroundings. However, it will relax once it has won. It is rare in the wild, but it can be found in mountainous areas.</Charmeleon.description>
  <Charmeleon.tools.0.label>Dragon Rage</Charmeleon.tools.0.label>
  <Charmeleon.tools.1.label>Fire Fang</Charmeleon.tools.1.label>
  <Charmeleon.tools.2.label>Flame Thrower</Charmeleon.tools.2.label>
  <Charmeleon_Leather.label>리자드 가죽</Charmeleon_Leather.label>
  <Charmeleon_Leather.description>리자드 가죽</Charmeleon_Leather.description>
  <Charmeleon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>리자드 가죽</Charmeleon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Cyndaquil -->
  <Charmeleon_Corpse.label>리자드 시체</Charmeleon_Corpse.label>
  <Charmeleon_Corpse.description>리자드 시체</Charmeleon_Corpse.description>


  <!-- CHARIZARD -->

  <Charizard.label>리자몽</Charizard.label>
  <Charizard.description>#006 Charizard
Flame Pokémon
Type: Fire/Flying

Pokédex entrie: Charizard flies around the sky in search of powerful opponents. It breathes fire of such great heat that it melts anything. However, it never turns its fiery breath on any opponent weaker than itself. 

Charizard is a draconic, bipedal Pokémon. It is primarily orange with a cream underside from the chest to the tip of its tail, which burns with a sizable flame. Charizard has a long neck, small blue eyes, raised nostrils, and two horn-like structures protruding from the back of its rectangular head. There are two fangs visible in the upper jaw when its mouth is closed. Two large wings with blue-green undersides sprout from its back, and a horn-like appendage juts out from the third joint of each wing. Charizard's arms are short and skinny compared to its robust belly, and each limb has three white claws. It has stocky legs and cream-colored soles under its feet.</Charizard.description>
  <Charizard.tools.0.label>Flare Blitz</Charizard.tools.0.label>
  <Charizard.tools.1.label>Inferno</Charizard.tools.1.label>
  <Charizard.tools.2.label>Dragon Claw</Charizard.tools.2.label>
  <Charizard.tools.3.label>Dragon Claw</Charizard.tools.3.label>
  <Charizard_Leather.label>리자몽 가죽</Charizard_Leather.label>
  <Charizard_Leather.description>리자몽 가죽</Charizard_Leather.description>
  <Charizard_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>리자몽 가죽</Charizard_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Cyndaquil -->
  <Charizard_Corpse.label>리자몽 시체</Charizard_Corpse.label>
  <Charizard_Corpse.description>리자몽 시체</Charizard_Corpse.description>


  <!-- MEGA CHARIZARD X -->

  <MegaCharizardX.label>메가 리자몽 X</MegaCharizardX.label>
  <MegaCharizardX.description>#006 Mega Charizard X
Flame Pokémon
Type: Fire/Dragon

Pokédex entrie: Charizard flies around the sky in search of powerful opponents. It breathes fire of such great heat that it melts anything. However, it never turns its fiery breath on any opponent weaker than itself. 

As Mega Charizard X, its body and legs appear more physically fit, though its arms remain thin. Its skin turns black with a sky blue underside extending from the lower jaw to the tip of the tail. Two spikes with blue tips curve upward from the front and back of each shoulder, while the tips of its horns sharpen, turn blue, and curve slightly upward. Its brow and claws are larger, its snout is shorter, and its eyes are now red with white pupils. It has two small, fin-like spikes under each horn and two more down its lower neck. The lower trims of its wings are divided into large, rounded points and each third joint is adorned with a claw-like spike. Mega Charizard X breathes blue flames out the sides of its mouth, and the flame on its tail now burns blue with increased heat.</MegaCharizardX.description>
  <MegaCharizardX.tools.0.label>Flare Blitz</MegaCharizardX.tools.0.label>
  <MegaCharizardX.tools.1.label>Inferno</MegaCharizardX.tools.1.label>
  <MegaCharizardX.tools.2.label>Dragon Claw</MegaCharizardX.tools.2.label>
  <MegaCharizardX.tools.3.label>Dragon Claw</MegaCharizardX.tools.3.label>
  <MegaCharizardX_Leather.label>메가 리자몽 X 가죽</MegaCharizardX_Leather.label>
  <MegaCharizardX_Leather.description>메가 리자몽 X 가죽</MegaCharizardX_Leather.description>
  <MegaCharizardX_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>메가 리자몽 X 가죽</MegaCharizardX_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Cyndaquil -->
  <MegaCharizardX_Corpse.label>메가 리자몽 X 시체</MegaCharizardX_Corpse.label>
  <MegaCharizardX_Corpse.description>메가 리자몽 X 시체</MegaCharizardX_Corpse.description>


  <!-- NUMEL -->

  <Numel.label>둔타</Numel.label>
  <Numel.description>#322 Numel
Numb Pokémon
Type: Fire/Ground

Pokédex entrie: Numel is extremely dull witted - it doesn't notice being hit. However, it can't stand hunger for even a second. This Pokémon's body is a seething cauldron of boiling magma.

Numel is a yellow, quadruped Pokémon that resembles a Dromedary camel with a volcano-like hump on its back. The hump is green at the very top and fades out into yellow with small green spots. It contains magma of almost 2,200 °F (1,200 °C). A female will have a bigger hump than a male. It has bangs on top of its head, sleepy eyes with brown circles around them, and short, stubby legs.

Numel is a very strong Pokémon, having served humans for many years with its ability to carry heavy loads up to 220 lbs. (100 kg). However, it slows down when wet and cannot stand when it is hungry. Due to its dull wits, it does not notice when it has been hit. Numel lives on volcanic mountains.</Numel.description>
  <Numel.tools.0.label>Magnitude</Numel.tools.0.label>
  <Numel.tools.1.label>Ember</Numel.tools.1.label>
  <Numel_Leather.label>둔타 가죽</Numel_Leather.label>
  <Numel_Leather.description>둔타 가죽</Numel_Leather.description>
  <Numel_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>둔타 가죽</Numel_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Cyndaquil -->
  <Numel_Corpse.label>둔타 시체</Numel_Corpse.label>
  <Numel_Corpse.description>둔타 시체</Numel_Corpse.description>


  <!-- CAMERUPT -->

  <Camerupt.label>폭타</Camerupt.label>
  <Camerupt.description>#323 Camerupt
Eruption Pokémon
Type: Fire/Ground

Pokédex entrie: The humps on Camerupt's back are formed by a transformation of its bones. They sometimes blast out molten magma. This Pokémon apparently erupts often when it is enraged.

Camerupt is a quadruped Pokémon that resembles a Bactrian camel. It has two gray volcanoes on its back. The two volcanoes on a female's back are bigger than those on a male. It also has a stout body with red shaggy fur and three blue ring-shaped markings on both sides. It has bangs on top of its head, droopy ears, and a tan furless muzzle.

As Mega Camerupt, the humps on its back have transformed into one large and very active volcano. Its fur expands and grows to a point where only its hooves can be seen, and its ears and the tufts on its head grow thicker and longer, standing on end. It gains a gray M on the front of its face and loses the three blue rings on its body. Magma is constantly bubbling up from within its body. It has a deep hatred of water or any moisture, and has an explosive personality and a short temper. The volcano on its back erupts constantly in an effort to intimidate its foes.[1]

Its body contains amounts of molten lava of 18,000 °F (10,000 °C), which erupts out of its humps if the Pokémon is angered. As shown in the anime, it can become uncontrollably angry when it is struck in the face. It lives in the craters of volcanoes.</Camerupt.description>
  <Camerupt.tools.0.label>Earth Power</Camerupt.tools.0.label>
  <Camerupt.tools.1.label>Lava Plume</Camerupt.tools.1.label>
  <Camerupt.tools.2.label>Eruption</Camerupt.tools.2.label>
  <Camerupt_Leather.label>폭타 가죽</Camerupt_Leather.label>
  <Camerupt_Leather.description>폭타 가죽</Camerupt_Leather.description>
  <Camerupt_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>폭타 가죽</Camerupt_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Cyndaquil -->
  <Camerupt_Corpse.label>폭타 시체</Camerupt_Corpse.label>
  <Camerupt_Corpse.description>폭타 시체</Camerupt_Corpse.description>


</LanguageData>