<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- WURMPLE -->

  <Wurmple.label>개무소</Wurmple.label>
  <Wurmple.description>#265 Wurmple
Worm Pokémon
Type: Bug

Pokédex entrie: Using the spikes on its rear end, Wurmple peels the bark off trees and feeds on the sap that oozes out. This Pokémon's feet are tipped with suction pads that allow it to cling to glass without slipping.

Wurmple is a small, caterpillar-like Pokémon. Its body is mainly red with a cream underside and face. It has large yellow eyes with dark pupils. It has one sharp yellow stinger on its head and two of them on its rear. It has a tall, erect, red spine behind its forehead and a similar, smaller spine behind that. It has small spikes running down the top portions of its body and five pairs of stubby white limbs.

Wurmple has suction pads at the tips of its feet, which allow it to cling to glass or tree branches without slipping. It can spit a white silk that turns gooey when exposed to the air. It can release poison from its tail spikes, which can weaken and poison foes. Wurmple lives in forests. It eats leaves and pulls bark off trees to feed on the sap. Taillow, Swellow, and Starly are natural predators of Wurmple.</Wurmple.description>
  <Wurmple.tools.0.label>String Shot</Wurmple.tools.0.label>
  <Wurmple.tools.1.label>Bug Bite</Wurmple.tools.1.label>
  <Wurmple_Leather.label>개무소 가죽</Wurmple_Leather.label>
  <Wurmple_Leather.description>개무소 가죽</Wurmple_Leather.description>
  <Wurmple_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>개무소 가죽</Wurmple_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <Wurmple_Meat.label>벌레 고기</Wurmple_Meat.label>
  <Wurmple_Meat.description>벌레 고기</Wurmple_Meat.description>
  <Wurmple_Corpse.label>개무소 시체</Wurmple_Corpse.label>
  <Wurmple_Corpse.description>개무소 시체</Wurmple_Corpse.description>


  <!-- CATERPIE -->

  <Caterpie.label>캐터피</Caterpie.label>
  <Caterpie.description>#010 Caterpie
Worm Pokémon
Type: Bug

Pokédex entrie: Caterpie has a voracious appetite. It can devour leaves bigger than its body right before your eyes. From its antenna, this Pokémon releases a terrifically strong odor.

Caterpie is a Pokémon that resembles a green caterpillar. There are yellow ring-shaped markings down the sides of its body, which resemble its eyes and are meant to scare off predators. Its most notable characteristic is the bright red antenna (osmeterium) on its head, which releases a stench to repel predators. Despite these features and its camouflage in green foliage, Caterpie is often preyed upon by Flying-type Pokémon. Its feet are tipped with suction cups, permitting this Pokémon to scale most surfaces with minimal effort.

Caterpie will shed its skin many times before finally cocooning itself in thick silk. It can also spit this silk in order to entangle foes as seen in the anime. Its has a voracious appetite, which causes it to eat leaves larger than itself. According to Pokémon Adventures, its favorite food is the Vermilion flower. Caterpie lives in forests.</Caterpie.description>
  <Caterpie.tools.0.label>String Shot</Caterpie.tools.0.label>
  <Caterpie.tools.1.label>Bug Bite</Caterpie.tools.1.label>
  <Caterpie_Leather.label>캐터피 가죽</Caterpie_Leather.label>
  <Caterpie_Leather.description>캐터피 가죽</Caterpie_Leather.description>
  <Caterpie_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>캐터피 가죽</Caterpie_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Wurmple -->
  <Caterpie_Corpse.label>캐터피 시체</Caterpie_Corpse.label>
  <Caterpie_Corpse.description>캐터피 시체</Caterpie_Corpse.description>


  <!-- SHEDINJA -->

  <Shedinja.label>껍질몬</Shedinja.label>
  <Shedinja.description>#292 Shedinja
Pokémon
Type: Bug/Ghost

Pokédex entrie: Shedinja’s hard body doesn’t move—not even a twitch. In fact, its body appears to be merely a hollow shell. It is believed that this Pokémon will steal the spirit of anyone peering into its hollow body from its back.

Shedinja is a Pokémon based on a cicada's shed exoskeleton. Most of its body is light brown, but the abdomen is gray. It has four protrusions on its underside instead of legs; the top pair is brown, while the lower is gray. There are round protrusions on the side of its head with narrow slits for eyes. Two lines encircle its abdomen and a white halo floats above its head. On its back is a pair of tattered wings divided into three wingtips. A hole between its wings reveals that its body completely hollow and dark, as it possesses no internal organs. It is said that looking into this empty space will steal one's spirit. Its shell is very hard, which gives it strong defense but renders it incapable of movement. It does not breathe and floats without moving its wings. It lives in forests.</Shedinja.description>
  <Shedinja.tools.0.label>Shadow Sneak</Shedinja.tools.0.label>
  <Shedinja.tools.1.label>Confuse Ray</Shedinja.tools.1.label>
  <Shedinja.tools.2.label>Phantom Force</Shedinja.tools.2.label>
  <Shedinja_Leather.label>껍질몬 가죽</Shedinja_Leather.label>
  <Shedinja_Leather.description>껍질몬 가죽</Shedinja_Leather.description>
  <Shedinja_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>껍질몬 가죽</Shedinja_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Wurmple -->
  <Shedinja_Corpse.label>껍질몬 시체</Shedinja_Corpse.label>
  <Shedinja_Corpse.description>껍질몬 시체</Shedinja_Corpse.description>


  <!-- COMBEE -->

  <Combee.label>세꿀버리</Combee.label>
  <Combee.description>#415 Combee
Tiny Bee Pokémon
Type: Bug/Flying

Pokédex entrie: The trio is together from birth. It constantly gathers honey from flowers to please Vespiquen.

Combee is a small insectoid Pokémon that resembles three pieces of orange, hexagonal honeycomb stuck together. Each hexagon has a round yellow face. The bottom-center face is the main thinker of the three, and it is also the only one "bee" to have a full abdomen. The top two hexagons have a single antenna and a wing connected to an orange-colored joint. A female Combee has a red spot on the forehead of its lower face.

Combee can fly with its two wings as long as the top two "bees" co-ordinate their flapping. It is mostly sociable among their own kind. It is generally harmless; it flees when threatened. A Combee will almost always be found collecting honey wherever they can. The gathered honey has multiple purposes, though it's usually consumed. When it is not gathering honey, it sleeps or protects its queen. The former is done by creating a hive along with other Combee, locking together into a "wall" to feel safe in larger numbers. It is very suggestible and will never defy the orders of its queen. When a Vespiquen feels threatened, its subject Combee will not think twice about risking its life to protect the queen, then attacking and even killing the threat in an aggressive manner. It commonly lives in caves and hollow trees of forests and other natural, secluded areas with their queen.</Combee.description>
  <Combee.tools.0.label>Gust</Combee.tools.0.label>
  <Combee.tools.1.label>Sweet Scent</Combee.tools.1.label>
  <Combee_Leather.label>세꿀버리 가죽</Combee_Leather.label>
  <Combee_Leather.description>세꿀버리 가죽</Combee_Leather.description>
  <Combee_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>세꿀버리 가죽</Combee_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Wurmple -->
  <Combee_Corpse.label>세꿀버리 시체</Combee_Corpse.label>
  <Combee_Corpse.description>세꿀버리 시체</Combee_Corpse.description>


  <!-- VESPIQUEN -->

  <Vespiquen.label>비퀸</Vespiquen.label>
  <Vespiquen.description>#416 Vespiquen
Beehive Pokémon
Type: Bug/Flying

Pokédex entrie: The trio is together from birth. It constantly gathers honey from flowers to please Vespiquen.

Vespiquen is a bee-like Pokémon with yellow and black striped abdomen resembling an elegant ballroom gown. Underneath the expansive abdomen are honeycomb-like cells that serve as a nest for baby Combee. However, it appears to have a slender, more insect-like abdomen in the centermost cell, which is inconspicuous as the ‘dress’ usually obstructs the view of it. Vespiquen has black, skinny arms with two orange claws and flies with a pair of relatively small wings on its back. Its yellow upper body is a nearly perfect sphere and its waist is black and slender. A curved line on its back between its shoulders separates its thorax and waist. Vespiquen's orange face has intimidating red eyes, oversized, yellow, protruding mandibles, and a red gem on its forehead. The top portion of its head is similar to a headpiece with yellow and black horn-like projections, resembling a hairstyle historically favored by early medieval-period English queens. Vespiquen is a female-only species.

Vespiquen is a queen of a hive of Combee, controlling it and protecting it, as well as giving birth to young Combee. A Vespiquen is far more powerful than its followers, and will only take action if its Combee are unable to protect the hive. If outsiders prove themselves to it by defending its hive, it may repay these acts of kindness with a reward. It feeds on flowers to make honey. It then uses it to bring up other Combee. Being a queen, it can command other Combee in order to use Attack Order, Defend Order, and Heal Order, her signature moves.</Vespiquen.description>
  <Vespiquen.tools.0.label>Fury Cutter</Vespiquen.tools.0.label>
  <Vespiquen.tools.1.label>Fell Stinger</Vespiquen.tools.1.label>
  <Vespiquen.tools.2.label>Air Slash</Vespiquen.tools.2.label>
  <Vespiquen_Leather.label>비퀸 가죽</Vespiquen_Leather.label>
  <Vespiquen_Leather.description>비퀸 가죽</Vespiquen_Leather.description>
  <Vespiquen_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>비퀸 가죽</Vespiquen_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Wurmple -->
  <Vespiquen_Corpse.label>비퀸 시체</Vespiquen_Corpse.label>
  <Vespiquen_Corpse.description>비퀸 시체</Vespiquen_Corpse.description>


  <!-- SHUCKLE -->

  <Shuckle.label>단단지</Shuckle.label>
  <Shuckle.description>#213 Shuckle
Mold Pokémon
Type: Bug/Rock

Pokédex entrie: Shuckle quietly hides itself under rocks, keeping its body concealed inside its hard shell while eating berries it has stored away. The berries mix with its body fluids to become a juice.

Shuckle is a Pokémon that resembles a small turtle. Its body is yellow and appears soft. Until they are in use, Shuckle's limbs appear limp. It is encased in a very hard red shell that has many holes in it. The holes in its shell are rimmed with white. Rather than actively hunting and foraging for food like most other Pokémon, it collects Berries and stores them in its shell. The Berries inside are liquefied and fermented while they decompose by Shuckle's digestive juices, which it then consumes. Its digestive juices are also used to dissolve rocks so Shuckle can hide under them. It can be found in the mountains.</Shuckle.description>
  <Shuckle.tools.0.label>Struggle Bug</Shuckle.tools.0.label>
  <Shuckle.tools.1.label>Stone Edge</Shuckle.tools.1.label>
  <Shuckle.tools.2.label>Sticky Web</Shuckle.tools.2.label>
  <Shuckle_Leather.label>단단지 가죽</Shuckle_Leather.label>
  <Shuckle_Leather.description>단단지 가죽</Shuckle_Leather.description>
  <Shuckle_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>단단지 가죽</Shuckle_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Wurmple -->
  <Shuckle_Corpse.label>단단지 시체</Shuckle_Corpse.label>
  <Shuckle_Corpse.description>단단지 시체</Shuckle_Corpse.description>


</LanguageData>