<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- SPHEAL -->

  <Spheal.label>데굴레오</Spheal.label>
  <Spheal.description>#363 Spheal
Clap Pokémon
Type: Ice/Water

Pokédex entrie: Spheal is much faster rolling than walking to get around. When groups of this Pokémon eat, they all clap at once to show their pleasure. Because of this, their mealtimes are noisy.

Spheal is a chubby, spherical, seal-like Pokémon with a short, flat tail. Its plushy fur is light blue with several white spots of various sizes on its back. This covering of fluffy fur protects Spheal from the cold. It has black, circular eyes, small tusks protruding from its upper jaw, and small, rounded ears. Its stubby flippers and its underside are both beige. When happy or cheerful, such as when eating in a group, this Pokémon will clap its fins. Because its body is poorly shaped for swimming and can only walk slowly, it moves primarily by rolling across ice floes. It can even coat itself in ice while rolling to use its former signature move, Ice Ball. This Pokémon lives in and around the sea.</Spheal.description>
  <Spheal.tools.0.label>Water Gun</Spheal.tools.0.label>
  <Spheal.tools.1.label>Powder Snow</Spheal.tools.1.label>
  <Spheal_Leather.label>대굴레오 가죽</Spheal_Leather.label>
  <Spheal_Leather.description>대굴레오 가죽</Spheal_Leather.description>
  <Spheal_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>대굴레오 가죽</Spheal_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <Spheal_Meat.label>얼어붙은 고기</Spheal_Meat.label>
  <Spheal_Meat.description>얼어붙은 고기</Spheal_Meat.description>
  <Spheal_Corpse.label>대굴레오 시체</Spheal_Corpse.label>
  <Spheal_Corpse.description>대굴레오 시체</Spheal_Corpse.description>


  <!-- GLACEON -->

  <Glaceon.label>글레이시아</Glaceon.label>
  <Glaceon.description>#471 Glaceon
Fresh Snow Pokémon
Type: Ice

Pokédex entrie: By controlling its body heat, it can freeze the atmosphere around it to make a diamond-dust flurry.

Glaceon is a quadruped, mammalian creature covered in light-blue fur that can be frozen into sharp quills. It has long, pointed ears, dark eyes, and a small nose. Glaceon has two dark blue, rhombus-shaped markings on its back, and the tip of its tail and feet are the same shade of blue. With the crest on its forehead and the two teal dangles hanging from its ears, it appears to be wearing a teal ushanka or trapper's hat.

This Pokémon is able to create small ice crystals around it by controlling its body temperature. It is capable of freezing its fur into sharp needle-like icicles, used to tackle its prey. It can drop its body temperature below -75 degrees Fahrenheit. Glaceon is usually found in urban areas under the care of humans. It is rarely found in the wild.</Glaceon.description>
  <Glaceon.tools.0.label>Icy Wind</Glaceon.tools.0.label>
  <Glaceon.tools.1.label>Ice Fang</Glaceon.tools.1.label>
  <Glaceon.tools.2.label>Blizzard</Glaceon.tools.2.label>
  <Glaceon_Leather.label>글레이시아 가죽</Glaceon_Leather.label>
  <Glaceon_Leather.description>글레이시아 가죽</Glaceon_Leather.description>
  <Glaceon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>글레이시아 가죽</Glaceon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Spheal -->
  <Glaceon_Corpse.label>글레이시아 시체</Glaceon_Corpse.label>
  <Glaceon_Corpse.description>글레이시아 시체</Glaceon_Corpse.description>


  <!-- BERGMITE -->

  <Bergmite.label>꽁어름</Bergmite.label>
  <Bergmite.description>#712 Bergmite
Ice Chunk Pokémon
Type: Ice

Pokédex entrie: Using air of -150 degrees Fahrenheit, they freeze opponents solid. They live in herds above the snow line on mountains.

Bergmite is a small, quadruped Pokémon resembling a small, round ice chunk. Its upper half is slightly transparent, while its lower half is a solid white. It has yellow eyes, lined in purple, and two horn-like protrusion on its scalp. There is another smaller protrusion on its back end, which resembles a tail. It has four stubby, conical legs.

Bergmite can summon air of -150 degrees Fahrenheit to freeze its opponents solid. It lives with others of its kind on the tops of mountains, though Bergmite can also be found on the back of its evolved form, Avalugg.</Bergmite.description>
  <Bergmite.tools.0.label>Avalanche</Bergmite.tools.0.label>
  <Bergmite.tools.1.label>Powder Snow</Bergmite.tools.1.label>
  <Bergmite_Leather.label>꽁어름 가죽</Bergmite_Leather.label>
  <Bergmite_Leather.description>꽁어름 가죽</Bergmite_Leather.description>
  <Bergmite_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>꽁어름 가죽</Bergmite_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Spheal -->
  <Bergmite_Corpse.label>꽁어름 시체</Bergmite_Corpse.label>
  <Bergmite_Corpse.description>꽁어름 시체</Bergmite_Corpse.description>


  <!-- SNORUNT -->

  <Snorunt.label>눈꼬마</Snorunt.label>
  <Snorunt.description>#361 Snorunt
Snow Hat Pokémon
Type: Ice

Pokédex entrie: Snorunt live in regions with heavy snowfall. In seasons without snow, such as spring and summer, this Pokémon steals away to live quietly among stalactites and stalagmites deep in caverns.

Snorunt is a small, black Pokémon with an ovoid body. It has circular, light blue eyes, wide teeth, and spherical hands and feet that lack digits. It is covered with a yellow cloak that gives it a triangular outline. The coat is rimmed with an orange stripe and has three orange diamond markings on the back. Well-adapted to life in colder climates, it subsists on snow and ice and can survive temperatures as low as -150 degrees Fahrenheit. Snorunt is also a social creature, living and traveling with other Snorunt in groups of five. It can be found in caves, particularly when the outside weather lacks snow. Additionally, it has been known to visit human dwellings.</Snorunt.description>
  <Snorunt.tools.0.label>Powder Snow</Snorunt.tools.0.label>
  <Snorunt.tools.1.label>Headbutt</Snorunt.tools.1.label>
  <Snorunt_Leather.label>눈꼬마 가죽</Snorunt_Leather.label>
  <Snorunt_Leather.description>눈꼬마 가죽</Snorunt_Leather.description>
  <Snorunt_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>눈꼬마 가죽</Snorunt_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Spheal -->
  <Snorunt_Corpse.label>눈꼬마 시체</Snorunt_Corpse.label>
  <Snorunt_Corpse.description>눈꼬마 시체</Snorunt_Corpse.description>


  <!-- GLALIE -->

  <Glalie.label>얼음귀신</Glalie.label>
  <Glalie.description>#362 Galie
Face Pokémon
Type: Ice

Pokédex entrie: Its actual body is a rock that isn't particularly hard. Glalie absorbs moisture from the air and drapes itself in an armor of ice.

Glalie is a spherical Pokémon that consists of a black rock core covered by ice. The icy covering has several holes and spaces across this Pokémon’s body. Blue eyes and a mouth with flat teeth are visible through three of these holes. There are two large, black, conical horns on either side of Glalie's head.

Mega Glalie's jaw is dislocated because of the overwhelming energy, causing its mouth to extend to the length of its face. The lower jaw is all black except for two light-blue, conical, icy spikes. The pupils in Mega Glalie's eyes are now red instead of black. The horns on top Mega Glalie's head have been partially turned into ice, with the addition of a third horn on its forehead.

Glalie's icy body is actually rock that is not particularly hard. It does not melt, and it can control ice by instantly freezing moisture in the air into any desirable shape. This ability is used to drape itself in ice armor and freeze its prey, which it then consumes whole. It prefers consuming Pokémon like Vanillite that are already frozen though. It can be found in caves. Mega Glalie can spill endless blizzards from its broken mouth, though it gets irritated by the fact that it can no longer consume its prey.</Glalie.description>
  <Glalie.tools.0.label>Freeze Dry</Glalie.tools.0.label>
  <Glalie.tools.1.label>Ice Shard</Glalie.tools.1.label>
  <Glalie.tools.2.label>Ice Fang</Glalie.tools.2.label>
  <Glalie_Leather.label>얼음귀신 가죽</Glalie_Leather.label>
  <Glalie_Leather.description>얼음귀신 가죽</Glalie_Leather.description>
  <Glalie_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>얼음귀신 가죽</Glalie_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Spheal -->
  <Glalie_Corpse.label>얼음귀신 시체</Glalie_Corpse.label>
  <Glalie_Corpse.description>얼음귀신 시체</Glalie_Corpse.description>


  <!-- FROSLASS -->

  <Froslass.label>눈여아</Froslass.label>
  <Froslass.description>#478 Froslass
Snow Land Pokémon
Type: Ice/Ghost

Pokédex entrie: When it finds humans or Pokémon it likes, it freezes them and takes them to its chilly den, where they become decorations.

Froslass is a humanoid Pokémon with a hollow torso that resembles a kimono. It wears a red band around its waist, reminiscent of an Obi. Its body lacks feet and it floats in the air like its counterpart, Glalie. Its arms are connected to the sides of its head, and flare at the wrists. The flared portion has dappled, light blue coloration. Its hands consist of three small fingers. Froslass's head is shaped similar to a sideways water droplet, and is topped with two ice crystals that resemble horns. Its head has several holes on it, resembling a mask. Through two of these holes, crystal blue eyes with yellow sclera can be seen. It also has a mouth below this "mask".

Froslass lives in snowy areas and has the ability to freeze foes with its -58 degrees Fahrenheit breath. It is thought to display its victims secretly after freezing them. As evidenced in the anime, it can create illusions to manipulate others. Froslass is a female only species, and is said in legends to be the spirit of a woman who was lost in the mountains.</Froslass.description>
  <Froslass.tools.0.label>Ominous Wind</Froslass.tools.0.label>
  <Froslass.tools.1.label>Ice Shard</Froslass.tools.1.label>
  <Froslass.tools.2.label>Shadow Ball</Froslass.tools.2.label>
  <Froslass_Leather.label>눈여아 가죽</Froslass_Leather.label>
  <Froslass_Leather.description>눈여아 가죽</Froslass_Leather.description>
  <Froslass_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>눈여아 가죽</Froslass_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Spheal -->
  <Froslass_Corpse.label>눈여아 시체</Froslass_Corpse.label>
  <Froslass_Corpse.description>눈여아 시체</Froslass_Corpse.description>


</LanguageData>