<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- GASTLY -->

  <Gastly.label>고오스</Gastly.label>
  <Gastly.description>#092 Gastly
Gas Pokémon
Type: Ghost/Poison

Pokédex entrie: Poisonous gas comprises 95% of its body. It's said that the remaining 5% is made up of the souls of those who died from the gas.

Gastly has no true form, due to 95% of its body being poisonous gas. However, it consistently appears as a black, spherical Pokémon surrounded by a purple haze. It has a wide, pink mouth with two visible fangs. Though its eyes seem to extend past its round body, visible eyelids surround them. The toxic gas surrounding the main body can induce fainting and suffocation, and is capable of enshrouding an Indian elephant within two seconds. Because it is mostly gas, Gastly will dwindle away when exposed to strong winds.

The anime suggests that Gastly has a playful personality, often frightening and playing pranks on people for fun. However, it has shown a willingness to preserve or pass on the memories of departed humans. It has further been shown changing form and creating illusions, and it is capable of phasing through solid objects and forming tangible hands out of its gasses. The anime has shown Gastly living in old, dilapidated buildings, but it can also be found in caves.</Gastly.description>
  <Gastly.tools.0.label>Spite</Gastly.tools.0.label>
  <Gastly.tools.1.label>Lick</Gastly.tools.1.label>
  <Gastly_Leather.label>고오스 가죽</Gastly_Leather.label>
  <Gastly_Leather.description>고오스 가죽</Gastly_Leather.description>
  <Gastly_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>고오스 가죽</Gastly_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <Gastly_Meat.label>둥실거리는 고기</Gastly_Meat.label>
  <Gastly_Meat.description>둥실거리는 고기</Gastly_Meat.description>
  <Gastly_Corpse.label>고오스 시체</Gastly_Corpse.label>
  <Gastly_Corpse.description>고오스 시체</Gastly_Corpse.description>


  <!-- HAUNTER -->

  <Haunter.label>고우스트</Haunter.label>
  <Haunter.description>#093 Haunter
Gas Pokémon
Type: Ghost/Poison

Pokédex entrie: It strikes at humans from total darkness. Those licked by its cold tongue grow weaker with each passing day until they die.

Haunter is a purple Pokémon with a gaseous body. It has a round head with a pair of disembodied hands. Each hand has three pointed fingers. Its head is flanked by three large, spiked protrusions on either side, and its eyes are large and triangular with small pupils. The gases composing its head curve down to form several pointed teeth framing a pink mouth and a long tongue. Its body tapers into a jagged tail.

Haunter hides in very dark places, where it plots to take the life of the next living thing that comes near it. It silently stalks its victim and steals its life force with a lick from its gaseous tongue, which inflicts convulsions that persists until the victim dies. It has the ability to float through solid walls. Despite its predatory nature, it has been known to entertain and prank people in the anime. Additionally, it has even been shown to feel intense loyalty to a deceased Trainer. Haunter lives in dark, abandoned caves.</Haunter.description>
  <Haunter.tools.0.label>Night Shade</Haunter.tools.0.label>
  <Haunter.tools.1.label>Lick</Haunter.tools.1.label>
  <Haunter.tools.2.label>Dream Eater</Haunter.tools.2.label>
  <Haunter_Leather.label>고우스트 가죽</Haunter_Leather.label>
  <Haunter_Leather.description>고우스트 가죽</Haunter_Leather.description>
  <Haunter_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>고우스트 가죽</Haunter_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Gastly -->
  <Haunter_Corpse.label>고우스트 시체</Haunter_Corpse.label>
  <Haunter_Corpse.description>고우스트 시체</Haunter_Corpse.description>


  <!-- LITWICK -->

  <Litwick.label>불켜미</Litwick.label>
  <Litwick.description>#607 Litwick
Candle Pokémon
Type:

Pokédex entrie: Litwick shines a light that absorbs the life energy of people and Pokémon, which becomes the fuel that it burns.

Litwick is a small, candle-like Pokémon with a purple flame atop its head, which is powered by life energy that it absorbs. Its body and two stubby arms are made primarily out of white wax. The folded, melted wax lays over its right eye, and leaves only the bright yellow left eye visible. It has a small smile under a protruding upper lip. Litwick pretends to guide people and Pokémon around by illuminating darkened areas. However, it is actually sucking away their life energy and leading them to the Ghost World. In the anime, the flame is shown to grow as it continually absorbs life energy.</Litwick.description>
  <Litwick.tools.0.label>Smog</Litwick.tools.0.label>
  <Litwick.tools.1.label>Ember</Litwick.tools.1.label>
  <Litwick_Leather.label>불켜미 가죽</Litwick_Leather.label>
  <Litwick_Leather.description>불켜미 가죽</Litwick_Leather.description>
  <Litwick_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>불켜미 가죽</Litwick_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Gastly -->
  <Litwick_Corpse.label>불켜미 시체</Litwick_Corpse.label>
  <Litwick_Corpse.description>불켜미 시체</Litwick_Corpse.description>


  <!-- PUMPKABOO -->

  <Pumpkaboo.label>호바귀</Pumpkaboo.label>
  <Pumpkaboo.description>#710 Pumpkaboo
Pumpkin Pokémon
Type: Ghost/Grass

Pokédex entrie: It is said to carry wandering spirits to the place where they belong so they can move on.

Pumpkaboo is a bipedal Pokémon that resembles a pinkish pumpkin. It comes in four different sizes: small, average, large, and super sized. The pumpkin body has a pair of circular holes carved out of its rind that resemble eyes. The ghostly body that lives in the pumpkin is black with a pointy collar, yellowish eyes with no visible pupils, a pair of fangs, curved ears and a curled stem. Pumpkaboo can release light from the holes on its body, making it similar to a flashlight.

The spirit residing in the pumpkin is trapped in this world. Pumpkaboo can carry wandering spirits to where they belong, so they can move on. It and its evolution Gourgeist are the only known Pokémon that can learn Trick-or-Treat.</Pumpkaboo.description>
  <Pumpkaboo.tools.0.label>Trick or Treat</Pumpkaboo.tools.0.label>
  <Pumpkaboo.tools.1.label>Leech Seed</Pumpkaboo.tools.1.label>
  <Pumpkaboo.tools.2.label>Shadow Ball</Pumpkaboo.tools.2.label>
  <Pumpkaboo_Leather.label>호바귀 가죽</Pumpkaboo_Leather.label>
  <Pumpkaboo_Leather.description>호바귀 가죽</Pumpkaboo_Leather.description>
  <Pumpkaboo_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>호바귀 가죽</Pumpkaboo_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Gastly -->
  <Pumpkaboo_Corpse.label>호바귀 시체</Pumpkaboo_Corpse.label>
  <Pumpkaboo_Corpse.description>호바귀 시체</Pumpkaboo_Corpse.description>


  <!-- SHUPPET -->

  <Shuppet.label>어둠대신</Shuppet.label>
  <Shuppet.description>#353 Shuppet
Puppet Pokémon
Type: Ghost

Pokédex entrie: It eats up emotions like malice, jealousy, and resentment, so some people are grateful for its presence.

Shuppet is a spherical Pokémon that appears to be covered by a gray cloth. Black rings surround its multicolored eyes, which have light blue sclera, dark blue irises, and yellow pupils. Extending from the top of its head is a long, pointed horn. The horn collects the negative emotions of people, on which this Pokémon feeds. The emotions it feeds on include anger, jealousy, and envy, so some people are grateful for its presence. A nocturnal Pokémon, it will appear in swarms beneath the eaves of houses with negative people. It is most commonly found in cities and other urban settings.</Shuppet.description>
  <Shuppet.tools.0.label>Night Shade</Shuppet.tools.0.label>
  <Shuppet.tools.1.label>Shadow Sneak</Shuppet.tools.1.label>
  <Shuppet_Leather.label>어둠대신 가죽</Shuppet_Leather.label>
  <Shuppet_Leather.description>어둠대신 가죽</Shuppet_Leather.description>
  <Shuppet_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>어둠대신 가죽</Shuppet_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Gastly -->
  <Shuppet_Corpse.label>어둠대신 시체</Shuppet_Corpse.label>
  <Shuppet_Corpse.description>어둠대신 시체</Shuppet_Corpse.description>


  <!-- BANETTE -->

  <Banette.label>다크펫</Banette.label>
  <Banette.description>#354 Banette
Marionette Pokémon
Type: Ghost

Pokédex entrie: It's a stuffed toy that was thrown away and became possessed, ever searching for the one who threw it away so it can exact its revenge.

Banette is a dark gray, doll-like Pokémon that is possessed by pure hatred. It has three short spikes on its head and a long zigzagging ribbon trailing off the back of its head. A zipper acts as its mouth, and it has purplish-pink eyes with slit pupils. Its long, flat arms have three-fingered hands, while its legs are short and stubby. It has a yellow, brush-like tail.

As Mega Banette, this Pokémon gains several additional zippers: one running diagonally across its face, one on each hand and another on its body. The first zipper runs from its left eye to the tip of its central spike. The other three are all unzipped, revealing parts of Mega Banette's cursed purple body. Its three long purple fingers and body revealing two pointed, purple legs are visible. Its zigzagging ribbon becomes somewhat erect, and now has two zipper rings around it and a short zipper on the tip. It gains four further spikes: one on the top and bottom of each hand and one on each hip. However, it loses its brush-like tail.

Being driven to life by a powerful grudge, it keeps its life force safely in its body by the means of its zipped up mouth. If unzipped, it would lose its energy. It lays curses on others by using its body as a voodoo doll and sticking pins into itself. It lives in garbage dumps and dark alleys, where it searches for the person that threw it away before it became a Pokémon. It is said that treating it with enough care will satisfy its grudge and will turn it back into a stuffed toy. When it Mega Evolves, it is filled with so much power and vindictiveness it cannot help cursing its Trainer.</Banette.description>
  <Banette.tools.0.label>Phantom Force</Banette.tools.0.label>
  <Banette.tools.1.label>Will O Wisp</Banette.tools.1.label>
  <Banette.tools.2.label>Shadow Ball</Banette.tools.2.label>
  <Banette_Leather.label>다크펫 가죽</Banette_Leather.label>
  <Banette_Leather.description>다크펫 가죽</Banette_Leather.description>
  <Banette_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>다크펫 가죽</Banette_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Gastly -->
  <Banette_Corpse.label>다크펫 시체</Banette_Corpse.label>
  <Banette_Corpse.description>다크펫 시체</Banette_Corpse.description>


  <!-- MEGA BANETTE -->

  <MegaBanette.label>메가 다크펫</MegaBanette.label>
  <MegaBanette.description>#354 Mega Banette
Marionette Pokémon
Type: Ghost

Pokédex entrie: Mega Evolution increases its vindictiveness, and the cursing power that was held back by its zipper comes spilling out. Extraordinary energy amplifies its cursing power to such an extent that it can't help but curse its own Trainer.

Banette is a dark gray, doll-like Pokémon that is possessed by pure hatred. It has three short spikes on its head and a long zigzagging ribbon trailing off the back of its head. A zipper acts as its mouth, and it has purplish-pink eyes with slit pupils. Its long, flat arms have three-fingered hands, while its legs are short and stubby. It has a yellow, brush-like tail.

As Mega Banette, this Pokémon gains several additional zippers: one running diagonally across its face, one on each hand and another on its body. The first zipper runs from its left eye to the tip of its central spike. The other three are all unzipped, revealing parts of Mega Banette's cursed purple body. Its three long purple fingers and body revealing two pointed, purple legs are visible. Its zigzagging ribbon becomes somewhat erect, and now has two zipper rings around it and a short zipper on the tip. It gains four further spikes: one on the top and bottom of each hand and one on each hip. However, it loses its brush-like tail.

Being driven to life by a powerful grudge, it keeps its life force safely in its body by the means of its zipped up mouth. If unzipped, it would lose its energy. It lays curses on others by using its body as a voodoo doll and sticking pins into itself. It lives in garbage dumps and dark alleys, where it searches for the person that threw it away before it became a Pokémon. It is said that treating it with enough care will satisfy its grudge and will turn it back into a stuffed toy. When it Mega Evolves, it is filled with so much power and vindictiveness it cannot help cursing its Trainer.</MegaBanette.description>
  <MegaBanette.tools.0.label>Phantom Force</MegaBanette.tools.0.label>
  <MegaBanette.tools.1.label>Curse</MegaBanette.tools.1.label>
  <MegaBanette.tools.2.label>Grudge</MegaBanette.tools.2.label>
  <MegaBanette_Leather.label>메가 다크펫 가죽</MegaBanette_Leather.label>
  <MegaBanette_Leather.description>메가 다크펫 가죽</MegaBanette_Leather.description>
  <MegaBanette_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>메가 다크펫 가죽</MegaBanette_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Gastly -->
  <MegaBanette_Corpse.label>메가 다크펫 시체</MegaBanette_Corpse.label>
  <MegaBanette_Corpse.description>메가 다크펫 시체</MegaBanette_Corpse.description>


  <!-- DRIFLOON -->

  <Drifloon.label>흔들풍손</Drifloon.label>
  <Drifloon.description>#354 Drifloon
Balloon Pokémon
Type: Ghost/Flying

Pokédex entrie: Stories go that it grabs the hands of small children and drags them away to the afterlife. It dislikes heavy children.

Drifloon has a spherical, purple body with two stringy arms that have yellow, heart-shaped hands on the ends of them. At the base of its body is a frayed protrusion that resembles the tied end of a balloon. In the very center of its body is a yellow tape-like "X", which contains its small mouth in the very center. Located on either side of the "X" are its small, black eyes. A white mass of fluff that resembles a cloud sits on top of Drifloon's head.

Due to its aimless drifting, this species is known as "Signpost for Wandering Spirits". It has been known to steal children that mistake it for a regular balloon. However, due to its light weight, it can be resisted easily and is often pulled around. Although created by lost spirits of Pokémon and people, it can be friendly and helpful. It prefers to reside in damp, humid locations and can expand or shrink to express its feelings.</Drifloon.description>
  <Drifloon.tools.0.label>Gust</Drifloon.tools.0.label>
  <Drifloon.tools.1.label>Ominous Wind</Drifloon.tools.1.label>
  <Drifloon_Leather.label>흔들풍손 가죽</Drifloon_Leather.label>
  <Drifloon_Leather.description>흔들풍손 가죽</Drifloon_Leather.description>
  <Drifloon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>흔들풍손 가죽</Drifloon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Gastly -->
  <Drifloon_Corpse.label>흔들풍손 시체</Drifloon_Corpse.label>
  <Drifloon_Corpse.description>흔들풍손 시체</Drifloon_Corpse.description>


</LanguageData>