<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- SANDSHREW -->

  <Sandshrew.label>모래두지</Sandshrew.label>
  <Sandshrew.description>#027 Sandshrew
Mouse Pokémon
Type: Ground

Pokédex entrie: It usually makes its home in deserts and arid zones, where rain does not fall. It digs holes to catch Bug-type Pokémon.

Sandshrew is a bipedal mammalian Pokémon, but runs on all fours in the anime. Its brick-patterned yellow hide is dry, tough, blends in with desert sand, and protects its soft white underbelly and muzzle. Sandshrew has blue, almond-shaped eyes, a pointed snout, and triangular ears with white insides. Its tail is thick and conical. It has two long claws on each foot and three sharp claws on its forepaws, which are used to burrow.

Sandshrew spends much of its time hidden underground in deep burrows. It only emerges to lunge and drag in passing Bug-type Pokémon. Sandshrew can quickly curl into a tight ball to protect itself from great falls and opponents, but may also throw sand at attackers. While its body can efficiently absorb water to facilitate life in the desert, Sandshrew has been found in caves as well. If it is too wet, Sandshrew dries itself out by lying near a volcano.</Sandshrew.description>
  <Sandshrew.tools.0.label>Rapid Spin</Sandshrew.tools.0.label>
  <Sandshrew.tools.1.label>Sand Tomb</Sandshrew.tools.1.label>
  <Sandshrew.tools.2.label>Scratch</Sandshrew.tools.2.label>
  <Sandshrew_Leather.label>모래두지 가죽</Sandshrew_Leather.label>
  <Sandshrew_Leather.description>모래두지 가죽</Sandshrew_Leather.description>
  <Sandshrew_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>모래두지 가죽</Sandshrew_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <Sandshrew_Meat.label>빳빳한 고기</Sandshrew_Meat.label>
  <Sandshrew_Meat.description>빳빳한 고기</Sandshrew_Meat.description>
  <Sandshrew_Corpse.label>모래두지 시체</Sandshrew_Corpse.label>
  <Sandshrew_Corpse.description>모래두지 시체</Sandshrew_Corpse.description>


  <!-- SANDSLASH -->

  <Sandslash.label>고지</Sandslash.label>
  <Sandslash.description>#028 Sandslash
Mouse Pokémon
Type: Ground

Pokédex entrie: If it digs at an incredible pace, it may snap off its spikes and claws. They grow back in a day.

Sandslash is a bipedal, ground dwelling pholidote Pokémon. Although Sandslash is usually bipedal, it can run on all fours. Most of its underside is light yellow with a white underbelly. It has a narrow muzzle, almond-shaped blue eyes, and a thick tail. Its back is mostly covered in sharp, brown quills formed from its tough, dry hide. It has two large claws on its paws and feet. These claws are its primary weapons, and are used for slashing. They can also be used for burrowing. Its claws and spikes can both break off and are shed regularly, but grow back quickly. It can curl into a large ball to protect its white underbelly. In this position, it can roll to attack or escape and protect itself from heatstroke. Sandslash is also adept at climbing trees, and is prone to ambush its enemies from above. Sandslash can mostly be found in deserts.</Sandslash.description>
  <Sandslash.tools.0.label>Earthquake</Sandslash.tools.0.label>
  <Sandslash.tools.1.label>Crush Claw</Sandslash.tools.1.label>
  <Sandslash.tools.2.label>Sandstorm</Sandslash.tools.2.label>
  <Sandslash_Leather.label>고지 가죽</Sandslash_Leather.label>
  <Sandslash_Leather.description>고지 가죽</Sandslash_Leather.description>
  <Sandslash_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>고지 가죽</Sandslash_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Sandshrew -->
  <Sandslash_Corpse.label>고지 시체</Sandslash_Corpse.label>
  <Sandslash_Corpse.description>고지 시체</Sandslash_Corpse.description>


</LanguageData>