<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- JOLTEON -->

  <Jolteon.label>쥬피썬더</Jolteon.label>
  <Jolteon.description>#135 Jolteon
Lightning Pokémon
Type: Electric

Pokédex entrie: Every hair on its body starts to stand sharply on end if it becomes charged with electricity.

Jolteon is a quadruped, mammalian Pokémon. It is covered in yellow fur with a spiky fringe around its tail and a white ruff around its neck. Its ears are large and pointed, and its eyes and small nose are black. It has slender legs and small paws, each with three toes and a pink paw pad. In addition to the ability to become sharp like needles, Jolteon's fur also amplifies the electrical charges produced by its cells. It can also store and generate negative ions in its fur, which create a sparking noise.</Jolteon.description>
  <Jolteon.tools.0.label>Discharge</Jolteon.tools.0.label>
  <Jolteon.tools.1.label>Thunder Fang</Jolteon.tools.1.label>
  <Jolteon.tools.2.label>Volt Switch</Jolteon.tools.2.label>
  <Jolteon_Leather.label>쥬피썬더 가죽</Jolteon_Leather.label>
  <Jolteon_Leather.description>쥬피썬더 가죽</Jolteon_Leather.description>
  <Jolteon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>쥬피썬더 가죽</Jolteon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <Jolteon_Meat.label>충전 된 고기</Jolteon_Meat.label>
  <Jolteon_Meat.description>충전 된 고기</Jolteon_Meat.description>
  <Jolteon_Corpse.label>쥬피썬더 시체</Jolteon_Corpse.label>
  <Jolteon_Corpse.description>쥬피썬더 시체</Jolteon_Corpse.description>


  <!-- MAREEP -->

  <Mareep.label>메리프</Mareep.label>
  <Mareep.description>#179 Mareep
Wool Pokémon
Type: Electric

Pokédex entrie: When cold weather increases static electricity, its wool doubles in size and the tip of its tail glows slightly.

Mareep is a sheep-like Pokémon with fluffy cream-colored wool covering its entire body, as well as a curly tuft of wool in the middle of its head. Its head is blue, and it has black eyes. Its four feet are blue and have two digits on each foot, and it appears to be on tiptoe at all times. Its conical ears and tail have a yellow-and-black striped pattern. Mareep has an orange sphere at the end of its tail, which acts like a small light bulb. This sphere glows brighter the more electricity it has.

Mareep's wool, which grows continuously, stores electricity, rubbing together and building a static charge. Its volume increases when it builds up with electricity. Touching the wool when it is charged will result in a static shock. During the summer, the fleece is shed, but it grows back in a week. Air is also stored in its fur, which allows it to stay cool during summer and warm during winter. It tends to avoid battle in the wild and has a mild disposition. Mareep is most often found in grassy fields, though it can also be found in farms where its wool is used in high-quality clothing.</Mareep.description>
  <Mareep.tools.0.label>Cotton Spore</Mareep.tools.0.label>
  <Mareep.tools.1.label>Thunder Shock</Mareep.tools.1.label>
  <Mareep_Leather.label>메리프 가죽</Mareep_Leather.label>
  <Mareep_Leather.description>메리프 가죽</Mareep_Leather.description>
  <Mareep_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>메리프 가죽</Mareep_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Jolteon -->
  <Mareep_Corpse.label>메리프 시체</Mareep_Corpse.label>
  <Mareep_Corpse.description>메리프 시체</Mareep_Corpse.description>


  <!-- PICHU -->

  <Pichu.label>피츄</Pichu.label>
  <Pichu.description>#172 Pichu
Tiny Mouse Pokémon
Type: Electric

Pokédex entrie: It plays with others by touching tails and setting off sparks. This appears to be a test of courage.

Pichu is a small, ground-dwelling rodent Pokémon with pale yellow fur. Its eartips, collar, and tail are black and angular. Pichu's pink cheek pouches can store small amounts of electricity, and its tiny nose looks like a dot. Pichu is classified as a quadruped, but it can walk easily on its hind legs.

Pichu is a social Pokémon known for its playful and mischievous demeanor. It is usually found in groups and often touch tails with other Pichu as a show of courage, creating a shower of sparks that can make them cry. It is inept at storing electricity, and may discharge if amused, startled, or subjected to shock. However, it cannot discharge without being shocked itself. Charging up is more easily done on days of dryness or with thunderclouds. The crackling of static electricity generated by Pichu is audible. It can zap an adult human, but will surprise itself if it does. Pichu primarily lives in the forest, though it has also been depicted to thrive in urban areas.</Pichu.description>
  <Pichu.tools.0.label>Thunder Shock</Pichu.tools.0.label>
  <Pichu.tools.1.label>Sweet Kiss</Pichu.tools.1.label>
  <Pichu_Leather.label>피츄 가죽</Pichu_Leather.label>
  <Pichu_Leather.description>피츄 가죽</Pichu_Leather.description>
  <Pichu_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>피츄 가죽</Pichu_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Jolteon -->
  <Pichu_Corpse.label>피츄 시체</Pichu_Corpse.label>
  <Pichu_Corpse.description>피츄 시체</Pichu_Corpse.description>


  <!-- PIKACHU -->

  <Pikachu.label>피카츄</Pikachu.label>
  <Pikachu.description>#025 Pikachu
Mouse Pokémon
Type: Electric

Pokédex entrie: It stores electricity in the electric sacs on its cheeks. When it releases pent-up energy in a burst, the electric power is equal to a lightning bolt.

Pikachu is a short, chubby rodent Pokémon. It is covered in yellow fur with two horizontal brown stripes on its back. It has a small mouth, long, pointed ears with black tips, brown eyes, and the two red circles on its cheeks contain pouches for electricity storage. It has short forearms with five fingers on each paw, and its feet each have three toes. At the base of its lightning bolt-shaped tail is patch of brown fur at the base. A female will have a V-shaped notch at the end of its tail, which looks like the top of a heart. It is classified as a quadruped, but it has been known to stand and walk on its hind legs.

The anime has shown that wild Pikachu live in groups in forested areas. Pikachu communicate amongst themselves using squeaks and tail-shaking as friendly gestures. Electricity can be used to receive and send messages with each other, as well as other Electric Pokémon species. It raises its tail to check its surroundings, and is occasionally struck by lightning in this position. When groups grow, they can inadvertently cause lightning storms. Pikachu is found foraging for berries it roasts with electricity to make them tender enough to eat. A sure sign that Pikachu inhabits a location is patches of burnt grass. It has been observed eating and sometimes destroying telephone poles, wires, and other electronic equipment.

Pikachu charges itself while sleeping overnight, though stress and a lack of sleep can affect this. It is able to release electric discharges of varying intensity. Pikachu has been known to build up energy in its glands, and will need to discharge to avoid complications. It is also able to release energy through its tail, which acts as a grounding rod, as well as recharging fellow Pikachu with electric shocks. Pikachu can also electrify itself to use its signature move Volt Tackle.</Pikachu.description>
  <Pikachu.tools.0.label>Thunder Bolt</Pikachu.tools.0.label>
  <Pikachu.tools.1.label>Spark</Pikachu.tools.1.label>
  <Pikachu.tools.2.label>Electro Ball</Pikachu.tools.2.label>
  <Pikachu_Leather.label>피카츄 가죽</Pikachu_Leather.label>
  <Pikachu_Leather.description>피카츄 가죽</Pikachu_Leather.description>
  <Pikachu_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>피카츄 가죽</Pikachu_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Jolteon -->
  <Pikachu_Corpse.label>피카츄 시체</Pikachu_Corpse.label>
  <Pikachu_Corpse.description>피카츄 시체</Pikachu_Corpse.description>


</LanguageData>