<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- POOCHYENA -->

  <Poochyena.label>포챠나</Poochyena.label>
  <Poochyena.description>#261 Poochyena
Bite Pokémon
Type: Dark

Pokédex entrie: At first sight, Poochyena takes a bite at anything that moves. This Pokémon chases after prey until the victim becomes exhausted. However, it may turn tail if the prey strikes back.

Poochyena is a quadruped Pokémon similar in appearance to hyenas and canines. Its body is primarily gray with a black face and throat, paws, and belly. Its eyes are red with yellow sclerae, and it has a red nose. Its lower jaw has two pointed teeth sticking out. The fur at the base of its tail is rumpled and shaggy. Poochyena has gray paw pads on its three-toed paws.

Poochyena has a very keen sense of smell, allowing it to find and chase its prey with ease. It takes a bite at anything that moves, and makes the hair on its tail bristle out to try to intimidate its foes. Known for its tenacious nature, it chases after prey until the victim becomes exhausted. If its prey strikes back, it may turn tail. It is omnivorous and will eat anything. This Pokémon lives in grasslands and forests.</Poochyena.description>
  <Poochyena.tools.0.label>Assurance</Poochyena.tools.0.label>
  <Poochyena.tools.1.label>Bite</Poochyena.tools.1.label>
  <Poochyena.tools.2.label>Howl</Poochyena.tools.2.label>
  <Poochyena_Leather.label>포챠나 가죽</Poochyena_Leather.label>
  <Poochyena_Leather.description>포챠나 가죽</Poochyena_Leather.description>
  <Poochyena_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>포챠나 가죽</Poochyena_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <Poochyena_Meat.label>그림자 고기</Poochyena_Meat.label>
  <Poochyena_Meat.description>그림자 고기</Poochyena_Meat.description>
  <Poochyena_Corpse.label>포챠나 시체</Poochyena_Corpse.label>
  <Poochyena_Corpse.description>포챠나 시체</Poochyena_Corpse.description>


  <!-- UMBREON -->

  <Umbreon.label>블래키</Umbreon.label>
  <Umbreon.description>#197 Umbreon
Moonlight Pokémon
Type: Dark

Pokédex entrie: When exposed to the moon's aura, the rings on its body glow faintly and it gains a mysterious power.

Umbreon has a sleek black body with four slender legs and crimson eyes. There are two pairs of pointed teeth visible when its mouth is open, one in the upper jaw and one in the lower. It has long pointed ears and a bushy tail, each with a yellow band around them. Its forehead and legs have yellow rings on them. Its yellow markings glow at night and strike fear into anyone nearby. It hides in the darkness while waiting for its opponents, and its yellow rings glow when it leaps to attack. It is also capable of spraying a poisonous sweat whenever it gets agitated. This Pokémon is rare in the wild, and is more often found in urban areas under the care of people.</Umbreon.description>
  <Umbreon.tools.0.label>Moonlight</Umbreon.tools.0.label>
  <Umbreon.tools.1.label>Pursuit</Umbreon.tools.1.label>
  <Umbreon.tools.2.label>Feint Attack</Umbreon.tools.2.label>
  <Umbreon_Leather.label>블래키 가죽</Umbreon_Leather.label>
  <Umbreon_Leather.description>블래키 가죽</Umbreon_Leather.description>
  <Umbreon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>블래키 가죽</Umbreon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Poochyena -->
  <Umbreon_Corpse.label>블래키 시체</Umbreon_Corpse.label>
  <Umbreon_Corpse.description>블래키 시체</Umbreon_Corpse.description>


  <!-- ZORUA -->

  <Zorua.label>조로아</Zorua.label>
  <Zorua.description>#570 Zorua
Tricky Fox Pokémon
Type: Dark

Pokédex entrie: It changes into the forms of others to surprise them. Apparently, it often transforms into a silent child.

Zorua is a slate gray, fox-like Pokémon with red and black accents. Its ears are triangular with dark insides, and it has a large tuft of fur tipped with red on top of its head. It has greenish blue eyes with red eyelids. There are circular, red markings above the eyes that resemble eyebrows. Its muzzle is short and tapered with two small fangs seen in the upper jaw when its mouth is open. Zorua possesses a ruff of black fur around its neck and four short limbs tipped with red. Its tail is short and bushy. Zorua can change its physical appearance, though this transformation is merely an illusion as it keeps its own type and moves.</Zorua.description>
  <Zorua.tools.0.label>Fury Swipes</Zorua.tools.0.label>
  <Zorua.tools.1.label>Feint Attack</Zorua.tools.1.label>
  <Zorua.tools.2.label>Scratch</Zorua.tools.2.label>
  <Zorua_Leather.label>조로아 가죽</Zorua_Leather.label>
  <Zorua_Leather.description>조로아 가죽</Zorua_Leather.description>
  <Zorua_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>조로아 가죽</Zorua_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Poochyena -->
  <Zorua_Corpse.label>조로아 시체</Zorua_Corpse.label>
  <Zorua_Corpse.description>조로아 시체</Zorua_Corpse.description>


  <!-- ZOROARK -->

  <Zoroark.label>조로아크</Zoroark.label>
  <Zoroark.description>#571 Zoroark
Illusion Fox Pokémon
Type: Dark

Pokédex entrie: It doesn't just transform itself—it also has the power to make hundreds of people see its illusions.

Zoroark is a bipedal, gray-brown, fox-like Pokémon with crimson and black accents. It has a pointed snout and ears with red insides. It also has some red rimming its eyes and mouth. It has a large, red, voluminous mane with black tips, which somewhat resembles a ponytail, as a teal bangle down its length separates a mass of the mane from the lower portion. It has a black ruff on its upper body, pointed at the shoulders from which its arms extend. Its upper arms are thin, whereas its lower arms, while still slim, are bulkier. The arms have spiky extensions of fur at the elbows, and it has red claws on its hands and feet. Zoroark's eyes are red-rimmed with light blue irises.

Zoroark can create illusions that are indistinguishable from reality, deluding many people simultaneously. It can even create illusory landscapes in the forests where it dwells, to hide its territory and protect its den. However, Zoroark is incapable of physically changing itself into another form; it is merely capable of casting illusions. When a Zoroark takes the form of a human, it is capable of human speech. It can make convincing illusions of attacks, and these illusions are extremely realistic, enough to fool even cameras and make one believe they're being physically affected, though the illusion does not have any direct physical effect.</Zoroark.description>
  <Zoroark.tools.0.label>Night Slash</Zoroark.tools.0.label>
  <Zoroark.tools.1.label>Night Daze</Zoroark.tools.1.label>
  <Zoroark.tools.2.label>Hone Claws</Zoroark.tools.2.label>
  <Zoroark_Leather.label>조로아크 가죽</Zoroark_Leather.label>
  <Zoroark_Leather.description>조로아크 가죽</Zoroark_Leather.description>
  <Zoroark_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>조로아크 가죽</Zoroark_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Poochyena -->
  <Zoroark_Corpse.label>조로아크 시체</Zoroark_Corpse.label>
  <Zoroark_Corpse.description>조로아크 시체</Zoroark_Corpse.description>


  <!-- HOUNDOUR -->

  <Houndour.label>델빌</Houndour.label>
  <Houndour.description>#228 Houndour
Dark Pokémon
Type: Dark/Fire

Pokédex entrie: Houndour hunt as a coordinated pack. They communicate with each other using a variety of cries to corner their prey. This Pokémon's remarkable teamwork is unparalleled.

Houndour is a quadruped, canine Pokémon with short, black fur and a red underbelly and muzzle. Its ears and tail are both short and pointed. Two fangs protrude from its upper jaw, and its triangular nose is black. There are white bands on its ankles, and rib-like ridges on its back. Houndour appears to have a simplistic, stylized skull on its forehead with the eye orbits creating eyebrow patterning above its actual eyes. It also has circular, red paw pads on each of its three-toed paws.

Houndour is an intelligent Pokémon that forms packs to hunt for prey, and shows unparalleled teamwork. As seen in the anime, it will not abandon a sick pack member. It communicates using various barks and howls. Barks are used to determine the location of a pack member during a hunt, while howls are used as declaration of ownership over a territory. They are known to be loyal and obedient to their Trainers. Houndour can typically be found around rough terrain.</Houndour.description>
  <Houndour.tools.0.label>Bite</Houndour.tools.0.label>
  <Houndour.tools.1.label>Fire Fang</Houndour.tools.1.label>
  <Houndour.tools.2.label>Smog</Houndour.tools.2.label>
  <Houndour_Leather.label>델빌 가축</Houndour_Leather.label>
  <Houndour_Leather.description>델빌 가축</Houndour_Leather.description>
  <Houndour_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>델빌 가축</Houndour_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Poochyena -->
  <Houndour_Corpse.label>델빌 시체</Houndour_Corpse.label>
  <Houndour_Corpse.description>델빌 시체</Houndour_Corpse.description>


  <!-- MURKROW -->

  <Murkrow.label>니로우</Murkrow.label>
  <Murkrow.description>#198 Murkrow
Darkness Pokémon
Type: Dark/Flying

Pokédex entrie: It appears near travelers to lure them into deep forests. It is said to carry misfortune.

Murkrow is an avian Pokémon with black feathers. Its crooked, yellow beak and the three, feathery tufts on its head resemble a witch's nose and hat respectively. The feathery crest is smaller on the female than on the male. It has semi-circular, red eyes with white sclerae and pupils and a spiky collar of feathers around its neck. The shaggy feathers on its tail resemble the end of a broom, and there is a thin, red band at the base of the tail. Its yellow feet have four toes, three facing forward and one backward.

Murkrow has a fondness for anything sparkly, and it will go as far as fighting with other Pokémon, such as Meowth or Gabite, in order to gain their stashes. Whenever it is chased, it loses the attacker by leading it down dark mountain trails, and sometimes it does this to travelers as a mean spirited prank. Its thieving and nocturnal nature has led it to become representative of misfortune. It is possible to train a Murkrow to repeat words, as seen under Team Rocket's ownership. Murkrow usually live in flocks amongst forests or swamps.</Murkrow.description>
  <Murkrow.tools.0.label>Astonish</Murkrow.tools.0.label>
  <Murkrow.tools.1.label>Peck</Murkrow.tools.1.label>
  <Murkrow.tools.2.label>Night Shade</Murkrow.tools.2.label>
  <Murkrow_Leather.label>니로우 가죽</Murkrow_Leather.label>
  <Murkrow_Leather.description>니로우 가죽</Murkrow_Leather.description>
  <Murkrow_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>니로우 가죽</Murkrow_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Poochyena -->
  <Murkrow_Corpse.label>니로우 시체</Murkrow_Corpse.label>
  <Murkrow_Corpse.description>니로우 시체</Murkrow_Corpse.description>


  <!-- SNEASEL -->

  <Sneasel.label>포푸니</Sneasel.label>
  <Sneasel.description>#215 Umbreon
Sharp Claw Pokémon
Type: Dark/Ice

Pokédex entrie: Its paws conceal sharp claws. If attacked, it suddenly extends the claws and startles its enemy.

Sneasel is a bipedal Pokémon that resembles both cats and weasels. It is primarily bluish black with three bright red feathers for its tail and a single one on its left ear. The ear feather is shorter on the female than on the male. The other ear is short and pointed, and it has narrow red eyes. On its forehead and chest are yellow, oval markings. It has red eyes with black eyelash-like markings on the edges. It has long limbs with two large, retractable claws on its hands and feet.

Sneasel is a notoriously vicious Pokémon, which is perfectly capable of using its claws to do substantial damage. The claws are also used for climbing trees in its forest home. Sneasel steals eggs from unattended Pidgey nests. Sneasel has been known to form pairs to hunt. One will lure the parents away from the nest, while the other steals the eggs. Its former signature move, Beat Up, allows it to call on its teammates to attack its opponent.</Sneasel.description>
  <Sneasel.tools.0.label>Icy Wind</Sneasel.tools.0.label>
  <Sneasel.tools.1.label>Metal Claw</Sneasel.tools.1.label>
  <Sneasel.tools.2.label>Feint Attack</Sneasel.tools.2.label>
  <Sneasel_Leather.label>포푸니 가죽</Sneasel_Leather.label>
  <Sneasel_Leather.description>포푸니 가죽</Sneasel_Leather.description>
  <Sneasel_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>포푸니 가죽</Sneasel_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Poochyena -->
  <Sneasel_Corpse.label>포푸니 시체</Sneasel_Corpse.label>
  <Sneasel_Corpse.description>포푸니 시체</Sneasel_Corpse.description>


</LanguageData>