<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- TOTODILE -->

  <Totodile.label>리아코</Totodile.label>
  <Totodile.description>#158 Totodile
Big Jaw Pokémon
Type: Water

Pokédex entrie: It is small but rough and tough. It won't hesitate to take a bite out of anything that moves.

Totodile resembles a bipedal, blue crocodile with red spines on its back and tail. The spine on its back is larger with additional ridges. Totodile's head is large, with ridges above its eyes. Much of the head's size is composed of Totodile's snout and strong jaws. There are two visible teeth on the tip of its upper jaw, and two rows of three teeth on each side of its lower jaw. On its chest is a yellow, somewhat V-shaped pattern that extends to its arms with a line bisecting the pattern. Totodile has five sharp claws and three toes. Its eyes are red and surrounded by a dark blue or black pattern. Totodile tends to be playful by nature, and has a habit of biting anything it sees, including its Trainer. In the wild, Totodile prefers to live along the edges of bodies of water.</Totodile.description>
  <Totodile.tools.0.label>Tackle</Totodile.tools.0.label>
  <Totodile.tools.1.label>Water Gun</Totodile.tools.1.label>
  <Totodile_Leather.label>리아코 가죽</Totodile_Leather.label>
  <Totodile_Leather.description>리아코 가죽</Totodile_Leather.description>
  <Totodile_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>리아코 가죽</Totodile_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <Totodile_Meat.label>촉촉한 고기</Totodile_Meat.label>
  <Totodile_Meat.description>촉촉한 고기</Totodile_Meat.description>
  <Totodile_Corpse.label>리아코 시체</Totodile_Corpse.label>
  <Totodile_Corpse.description>리아코 시체</Totodile_Corpse.description>


  <!-- CROCONAW -->

  <Croconaw.label>엘리게이</Croconaw.label>
  <Croconaw.description>#159 Croconaw
Big Jaw Pokémon
Type: Water

Pokédex entrie: If it loses a fang, a new one grows back in its place. There are always 48 fangs lining its mouth.

Croconaw is a medium-sized, bipedal, crocodilian Pokémon with a blue and yellow body. Croconaw has three clusters of red spikes on its body: one with three points on its head like a crest, one with two points on its back, and a diamond-shaped spike on its tail. Black markings surround its red eyes. Its lower jaw is yellow and pronounced, and its chest has an asymmetrical, yellow pattern resembling a spotted animal skin. Although Croconaw has been described as always having forty-eight fangs lining its mouth, only six are discernible with four visible when the mouth is closed. It is capable of regrowing lost fangs. Its teeth are positioned like barbed fishing hooks and are impossible to pull out with ordinary strength. Croconaw can rarely be found near water.</Croconaw.description>
  <Croconaw.tools.0.label>Ice Bite</Croconaw.tools.0.label>
  <Croconaw.tools.1.label>Bite</Croconaw.tools.1.label>
  <Croconaw.tools.2.label>Crunch</Croconaw.tools.2.label>
  <Croconaw_Leather.label>엘리게이 가죽</Croconaw_Leather.label>
  <Croconaw_Leather.description>엘리게이 가죽</Croconaw_Leather.description>
  <Croconaw_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>엘리게이 가죽</Croconaw_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Totodile -->
  <Croconaw_Corpse.label>엘리게이 시체</Croconaw_Corpse.label>
  <Croconaw_Corpse.description>엘리게이 시체</Croconaw_Corpse.description>


  <!-- FERALIGATR -->

  <Feraligatr.label>장크로다일</Feraligatr.label>
  <Feraligatr.description>#160 Feraligatr
Big Jaw Pokémon
Type: Water

Pokédex entrie: Feraligatr intimidates its foes by opening its huge mouth. In battle, it will kick the ground hard with its thick and powerful hind legs to charge at the foe at an incredible speed.

Feraligatr is a bulky, bipedal crocodilian Pokémon that is primarily blue with accents of red and yellow. A notable feature of Feraligatr is its large, powerful jaws that are able to bite and lock down on opponents. Three pointed teeth are visible when Feraligatr closes its mouth, two from the lower jaw and one from the upper. Feraligatr intimidates its foes by opening its huge mouth. Feraligatr has three sets of spikes on its body: one on its head, one on its back, and one near the tip of its tail. The one on its back appears particularly prominent, due to its size and the bulk of Feraligatr’s shoulders. It has a bisected, V-shaped yellow pattern between its thighs. Feraligatr also has large scales on its arms, tail, and legs. When hunting or fighting, Feraligatr is agile and fast, due to its powerful hind legs that are used to kick the ground hard and charge. Feraligatr can rarely be found living near water.</Feraligatr.description>
  <Feraligatr.tools.0.label>Aqua Tail</Feraligatr.tools.0.label>
  <Feraligatr.tools.1.label>Bite</Feraligatr.tools.1.label>
  <Feraligatr.tools.2.label>Crunch</Feraligatr.tools.2.label>
  <Feraligatr_Leather.label>장크로다일 가죽</Feraligatr_Leather.label>
  <Feraligatr_Leather.description>장크로다일 가죽</Feraligatr_Leather.description>
  <Feraligatr_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>장크로다일 가죽</Feraligatr_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Totodile -->
  <Feraligatr_Corpse.label>장크로다일 시체</Feraligatr_Corpse.label>
  <Feraligatr_Corpse.description>장크로다일 시체</Feraligatr_Corpse.description>


  <!-- PIPLUP -->

  <Piplup.label>팽도리</Piplup.label>
  <Piplup.description>#393 Piplup
Penguin Pokémon
Type: Water

Pokédex entrie: Because it is very proud, it hates accepting food from people. Its thick down guards it from the cold.

Piplup is a light-blue, penguin-like Pokémon, which is covered in thick down to insulate against the cold. It has a dark blue head with a primarily white face and a short, yellow beak. The dark blue feathers on its head extend down its back and around its neck, which causes it to appear to be wearing a cape. There are two white ovals on its chest and a small, light-blue marking resembles a crown above its beak. It has flipper-like arms and yellow feet with three toes each.

Piplup has a strong sense of self-pride. Because of its pride, it has a hard time accepting food from humans and bonding with its caretakers. It will even puff out its chest after it falls down, which it often does due to its poor walking abilities. However, it is a skilled swimmer that can dive for over ten minutes in order to hunt. It has also been shown to fly short distances in the anime. It lives along the seashore in colder climates.</Piplup.description>
  <Piplup.tools.0.label>Pound</Piplup.tools.0.label>
  <Piplup.tools.1.label>Bubble</Piplup.tools.1.label>
  <Piplup_Leather.label>팽도리 가죽</Piplup_Leather.label>
  <Piplup_Leather.description>팽도리 가죽</Piplup_Leather.description>
  <Piplup_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>팽도리 가죽</Piplup_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Totodile -->
  <Piplup_Corpse.label>팽도리 시체</Piplup_Corpse.label>
  <Piplup_Corpse.description>팽도리 시체</Piplup_Corpse.description>


  <!-- PRINPLUP -->

  <Prinplup.label>팽태자</Prinplup.label>
  <Prinplup.description>#394 Prinplup
Penguin Pokémon
Type: Water

Pokédex entrie: Because every Prinplup considers itself to be the most important, they can never form a group.

Prinplup is a blue, penguin-like Pokémon. It is mostly dark blue with light blue facial markings, wing tips, and lower body. Its eyes are blue and it has a short yellow beak with a small point above it. Two large, yellow ridges extend from its beak over the back of its head and meet just above the nape of its neck. On its body are four large, white spots that resemble buttons. Instead of arms, it has long, flipper-like wings that are capable of knocking over and snapping trees. It has short legs with yellow, three-toed feet. Prinplup has a high sense of self-pride, which prevents it from forming groups of its own kind. This Pokémon can be found in icy waters, where it hunts for prey.</Prinplup.description>
  <Prinplup.tools.0.label>Peck</Prinplup.tools.0.label>
  <Prinplup.tools.1.label>Bubble</Prinplup.tools.1.label>
  <Prinplup.tools.2.label>Bubble Beam</Prinplup.tools.2.label>
  <Prinplup_Leather.label>팽태자 가죽</Prinplup_Leather.label>
  <Prinplup_Leather.description>팽태자 가죽</Prinplup_Leather.description>
  <Prinplup_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>팽태자 가죽</Prinplup_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Totodile -->
  <Prinplup_Corpse.label>팽태자 시체</Prinplup_Corpse.label>
  <Prinplup_Corpse.description>팽태자 시체</Prinplup_Corpse.description>


  <!-- EMPOLEON -->

  <Empoleon.label>엠페르트</Empoleon.label>
  <Empoleon.description>#395 Empoleon
Emperor Pokémon
Type: Water/Steel

Pokédex entrie: The three horns that extend from its beak attest to its power. The leader has the biggest horns.

Empoleon is a pale green, sauropod-like Pokémon with yellow eyes. It has two stamen-like protrusions sprouting from the top of its nose, each tipped with its own anther. These protrusions are shorter on the female. It has four feet, each of which have three toes. Large pink flower petals with a yellow central pattern and white tips encircle its neck. Additionally, it has a short, pointed tail.

Empoleon is a large, navy blue, penguin-like Pokémon. It has a wide, yellow beak that extends upward into three pointed horns that form a trident-shaped crest bracketing blue eyes. Large horns are a symbol of leadership and strength for Empoleon. There is a blue marking resembling a crown over its eyes and a white, lacy marking running down its chest. A blue, fin-like projection forms a collar around its throat and runs down the length of its chest and belly. On its back are two raised, gold bumps and a second blue fin that forms its tail. Its yellow feet are webbed with three toes each and its feathers form ruffs above its feet. It has wide, flipper-like wings rimmed with blue along the tips, and three golden claws. The edges of these wings can slice through ice floes, and this Pokémon will use them to attack anyone or anything that damages its pride.</Empoleon.description>
  <Empoleon.tools.0.label>Hydro Pump</Empoleon.tools.0.label>
  <Empoleon.tools.1.label>Drill Peck</Empoleon.tools.1.label>
  <Empoleon.tools.2.label>Whirlpool</Empoleon.tools.2.label>
  <Empoleon_Leather.label>엠페르트 가죽</Empoleon_Leather.label>
  <Empoleon_Leather.description>엠페르트 가죽</Empoleon_Leather.description>
  <Empoleon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>엠페르트 가죽</Empoleon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Totodile -->
  <Empoleon_Corpse.label>엠페르트 시체</Empoleon_Corpse.label>
  <Empoleon_Corpse.description>엠페르트 시체</Empoleon_Corpse.description>


  <!-- CHINCHOU -->

  <Chinchou.label>초라기</Chinchou.label>
  <Chinchou.description>#170 Chinchou
Angler Pokémon
Type: Water/Electric

Pokédex entrie: Chinchou lets loose positive and negative electrical charges from its two antennas to make its prey faint. This Pokémon flashes its electric lights to exchange signals with others.

Chinchou is a small, round, blue fish-like Pokémon with a pair of tiny white fins and two small blue feet. Chinchou's eyes have unique pupils that are shaped like plus signs. It has two antennae that are positioned on its rear like two tails. There is a yellow teardrop-shaped orb at the end of each antenna.

Its antennae were once fins. The electricity-generating cells in these antennae create so much electrical power that they even make Chinchou tingle slightly. Chinchou charges up its electric attacks by absorbing energy through its two antennae, and flashes its electric lights to exchange signals with others or claim turf. These antennae also glow softly which lure in prey, which it stuns with its antennae before attacking. Chinchou tends to lurk on the dark ocean floors, rarely ever coming up to the surface. However, it has demonstrated the ability to walk on land.</Chinchou.description>
  <Chinchou.tools.0.label>Thunder Wave</Chinchou.tools.0.label>
  <Chinchou.tools.1.label>Bubble</Chinchou.tools.1.label>
  <Chinchou.tools.2.label>Electro Ball</Chinchou.tools.2.label>
  <Chinchou_Leather.label>초라기 가죽</Chinchou_Leather.label>
  <Chinchou_Leather.description>초라기 가죽</Chinchou_Leather.description>
  <Chinchou_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>초라기 가죽</Chinchou_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Totodile -->
  <Chinchou_Corpse.label>초라기 시체</Chinchou_Corpse.label>
  <Chinchou_Corpse.description>초라기 시체</Chinchou_Corpse.description>


  <!-- SQUIRTLE -->

  <Squirtle.label>꼬부기</Squirtle.label>
  <Squirtle.description>#007 Squirtle
Tiny Turtle Pokémon
Type: Water

Pokédex entrie: Shoots water at prey while in the water. Withdraws into its shell when in danger.

Squirtle is a small Pokémon that resembles a light blue turtle. While it typically walks on its two short legs, it has been shown to run on all fours in Super Smash Bros. Brawl. It has large eyes and a slightly hooked upper lip. Each of its hands and feet has three pointed digits. The end of its long tail curls inward. Its body is encased by a tough shell that forms and hardens after birth. This shell is brown on the top, pale yellow on the bottom, and has a thick white ridge between the two halves.

Squirtle's shell is a useful tool. It can withdraw into the shell for protection or for sleeping, and its grooved, rounded shape helps to reduce water resistance when this Pokémon swims. Squirtle can spray foamy water from its mouth with great accuracy. In the past, Skull Bash was its signature move. Squirtle is scarce in the wild, although it can be found around small ponds and lakes. The anime has shown that it can be found living on secluded islands with other members of its evolutionary line.</Squirtle.description>
  <Squirtle.tools.0.label>Tackle</Squirtle.tools.0.label>
  <Squirtle.tools.1.label>Bubble</Squirtle.tools.1.label>
  <Squirtle_Leather.label>꼬부기 가죽</Squirtle_Leather.label>
  <Squirtle_Leather.description>꼬부기 가죽</Squirtle_Leather.description>
  <Squirtle_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>꼬부기 가죽</Squirtle_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Totodile -->
  <Squirtle_Corpse.label>꼬부기 시체</Squirtle_Corpse.label>
  <Squirtle_Corpse.description>꼬부기 시체</Squirtle_Corpse.description>


  <!-- WARTORTLE -->

  <Wartortle.label>어니부기</Wartortle.label>
  <Wartortle.description>#008 Wartortle
Turtle Pokémon
Type: Water

Pokédex entrie: It is said to live 10,000 years. Its furry tail is popular as a symbol of longevity.

Wartortle is a bipedal, indigo Pokémon similar to a turtle. It has brown eyes, a dark blue streak on each cheek, and two sharp teeth protruding from its upper jaw. It has three clawed fingers and pointed toes. Pale blue fur covers its long ears and tail. A brown shell with a pale yellow underside encases its body. A thick, white rim separates the upper and lower halves of the shell. As Wartortle grows old, its tail fur will darken, and it may have algae growing on its shell. The shell may also carry scars from past battles.

To maintain balance while swimming at high speeds, Wartortle moves its furry ears and tail. It can use the fur to store air for extended underwater diving. Its tail is a popular symbol of longevity, making it popular with the elderly. It hides in water when hunting and emerges to surprise its prey. In the past, Skull Bash was its signature move. The anime has shown that Wartortle can be found living in colonies on islands, but its preferred habitat seems to be freshwater ponds and lakes.</Wartortle.description>
  <Wartortle.tools.0.label>Aqua Tail</Wartortle.tools.0.label>
  <Wartortle.tools.1.label>Water Pulse</Wartortle.tools.1.label>
  <Wartortle.tools.2.label>Bubble</Wartortle.tools.2.label>
  <Wartortle_Leather.label>어니부기 가죽</Wartortle_Leather.label>
  <Wartortle_Leather.description>어니부기 가죽</Wartortle_Leather.description>
  <Wartortle_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>어니부기 가죽</Wartortle_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Totodile -->
  <Wartortle_Corpse.label>어니부기 시체</Wartortle_Corpse.label>
  <Wartortle_Corpse.description>어니부기 시체</Wartortle_Corpse.description>


  <!-- BLASTOISE -->

  <Blastoise.label>거북왕</Blastoise.label>
  <Blastoise.description>#009 Blastoise
Shellfish Pokémon
Type: Water

Pokédex entrie: Blastoise has water spouts that protrude from its shell. The water spouts are very accurate. They can shoot bullets of water with enough accuracy to strike empty cans from a distance of over 160 feet.

Blastoise is a large, bipedal turtle-like Pokémon. Its body is blue and is mostly hidden by its tough, brown shell. This shell has a pale yellow underside and a white ridge encircling its arms and separating the upper and lower halves. Two powerful water cannons reside in the top sides of its shell. These cannons can be extended or withdrawn and can be used to assist in high-speed charges. Blastoise's head has triangular ears that are black on the inside, small brown eyes, and a cream-colored lower jaw. Its arms are thick and striated with three claws on each hand. Its feet have three claws on the front and one on the back. It has a stubby tail.

The powerful cannons on this Pokémon's back are capable of producing water blasts that can pierce steel and concrete. Blastoise deliberately makes itself heavy to withstand these powerful blasts, and it will crush its opponents with its bulk. It has two former signature moves, Skull Bash and Hydro Cannon. The anime has shown that Blastoise can take the role of a leader in large groups of Squirtle and Wartortle. Its preferred habitat seems to be freshwater ponds and lakes.</Blastoise.description>
  <Blastoise.tools.0.label>Bubble Beam</Blastoise.tools.0.label>
  <Blastoise.tools.1.label>Hydro Pump</Blastoise.tools.1.label>
  <Blastoise.tools.2.label>Bite</Blastoise.tools.2.label>
  <Blastoise_Leather.label>거북왕 가죽</Blastoise_Leather.label>
  <Blastoise_Leather.description>거북왕 가죽</Blastoise_Leather.description>
  <Blastoise_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>거북왕 가죽</Blastoise_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Totodile -->
  <Blastoise_Corpse.label>거북왕 시체</Blastoise_Corpse.label>
  <Blastoise_Corpse.description>거북왕 시체</Blastoise_Corpse.description>


  <!-- VAPOREON -->

  <Vaporeon.label>샤미드</Vaporeon.label>
  <Vaporeon.description>#134 Vaporeon
Bubble Jet Pokémon
Type: Water

Pokédex entrie: It prefers beautiful shores. With cells similar to water molecules, it could melt in water.

Vaporeon is a composite creature sharing physical traits of aquatic and land animals. It is a quadruped with three small toes on each foot and dark blue paw pads on the hind feet. Vaporeon's body is light blue with a dark blue marking around its head and a ridge down its back. This Pokémon has a split tailfin that has been mistaken for a mermaid's in the past. It has a white ruff around its neck, and three fins around its head made of cream-colored webbing. It is said that rain will come within a few hours if Vaporeon's fins begin to vibrate.

Vaporeon is mostly found in urban settings. under the ownership of a Trainer. It is rarely seen in the wild, but in that occasion, it prefers clean freshwater lakes. It has developed gills to become better suited to an aquatic lifestyle. Vaporeon's cell composition being similar to water allows it to melt into the water by using Acid Armor. This ability enables Vaporeon to remain camouflaged while swimming and ambush its prey, fish Pokémon.</Vaporeon.description>
  <Vaporeon.tools.0.label>Aqua Ring</Vaporeon.tools.0.label>
  <Vaporeon.tools.1.label>Water Pulse</Vaporeon.tools.1.label>
  <Vaporeon.tools.2.label>Muddy Water</Vaporeon.tools.2.label>
  <Vaporeon_Leather.label>샤미드 가죽</Vaporeon_Leather.label>
  <Vaporeon_Leather.description>샤미드 가죽</Vaporeon_Leather.description>
  <Vaporeon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>샤미드 가죽</Vaporeon_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Totodile -->
  <Vaporeon_Corpse.label>샤미드 시체</Vaporeon_Corpse.label>
  <Vaporeon_Corpse.description>샤미드 시체</Vaporeon_Corpse.description>


  <!-- LAPRAS -->

  <Lapras.label>라프라스</Lapras.label>
  <Lapras.description>#131 Lapras
Transport Pokémon
Type: Water/Ice

Pokédex entrie: 	Its high intelligence enables it to understand human speech. It likes to ferry people on its back.

Lapras is a large sea creature that resembles a plesiosaur. It has a spotted, blue hide with a cream underside. Its neck is long, and it has large black eyes. There is a short horn in the middle of its forehead and curled ears placed farther back on its head. It has four flippers with the foremost pair being larger than the hind. On its back is a heavy, gray shell covered in blunt knobs.

Lapras is a gentle, helpful Pokémon that enjoys ferrying people across bodies of water. In the past, its docility made it an easy target for hunters, and it was driven to near-extinction. Recent protection efforts have seen Lapras become overabundant, which is now affecting the fish Pokémon numbers in some areas. An intelligent Pokémon, it is able to understand human speech. Lapras have been known to travel in large pods across the seas, spanning both polar and tropical areas. To keep in touch with other of its kind, it sings enchanting melodies. In the anime it was shown that Lapras is able to develop psychic abilities such as telepathy.</Lapras.description>
  <Lapras.tools.0.label>Ice Beam</Lapras.tools.0.label>
  <Lapras.tools.1.label>Hydro Pump</Lapras.tools.1.label>
  <Lapras.tools.2.label>Sheer Cold</Lapras.tools.2.label>
  <Lapras_Leather.label>라프리스 가죽</Lapras_Leather.label>
  <Lapras_Leather.description>라프리스 가죽</Lapras_Leather.description>
  <Lapras_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>라프리스 가죽</Lapras_Leather.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
  <!-- Use Meat From: Totodile -->
  <Lapras_Corpse.label>라프리스 시체</Lapras_Corpse.label>
  <Lapras_Corpse.description>라프리스 시체</Lapras_Corpse.description>


</LanguageData>