<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
  <IncidentDef>
    <defName>SZ_YearBeastApproach</defName>
    <label>Nian beast attack! (It is recommended to click on the beast and view its detailed introduction)</label>
    <category>ThreatBig</category>
    <targetTags>
      <li>Map_PlayerHome</li>
    </targetTags>
    <workerClass>AncientChineseBeast.IncidentWorker_YearBeastApproach</workerClass>
    <baseChance>0</baseChance>
    <letterLabel>The Nian Beast is coming! (It is recommended to click on the beast and view its detailed introduction)</letterLabel>
    <letterText>A Nian Beast created by the genetic engineering of the Celestial Soldier Machine Race has appeared near the colony! It has a pair of sharp horns and a tiger-like body. What is even more troublesome is its thick protection. It needs to be dealt with as soon as possible, otherwise the ecological chain of the colony will be completely destroyed by it!</letterText>
    <letterDef>ThreatBig</letterDef>
  </IncidentDef>

  <IncidentDef>
    <defName>SZ_BeastApproach</defName>
    <label>The beast is coming! (It is recommended to click on the beast and view its detailed introduction)</label>
    <category>ThreatBig</category>
    <targetTags>
      <li>Map_PlayerHome</li>
    </targetTags>
    <workerClass>AncientChineseBeast.IncidentWorker_BeastApproach</workerClass>
    <modExtensions>
      <li Class="AncientChineseBeast.DefModExtension_Beasts">
        <beasts>
          <li>
            <pawn>SZ_QiongQi</pawn>
            <label>穷奇！(Pauper)</label>
            <text>没想到这种只存在于山海经中的凶兽竟然真的出现在了边缘世界上！据可靠情报透露，穷奇有着一对极其敏锐的双眼，如果放任它肆虐不管的话，我们的殖民地最终也只会成为它的囊中之物！\n\nUnexpectedly, such fierce beasts only exist in the classics of mountains and seas actually appear in the marginal world! According to reliable information, Ponzi has a pair of extremely sharp eyes. If we let it go unchecked, our colony will eventually become its bag!            </text>
          </li>
          <li>
            <pawn>SZ_MingShe</pawn>
            <label>鸣蛇！(Ming Snake)</label>
            <text>造成华夏据点多处发生旱灾的凶兽——鸣蛇已经出现在了我们的殖民地！为了保卫我们的庄稼能够顺利生长，我们有必要迅速找到应对它的方法并将它送去见阎王老爷。\n\nThe vicious beast that caused droughts in many parts of the Chinese colony——Snake has appeared in our colony! In order to protect our crops from growing smoothly, we must quickly find a way to deal with it and send it to Lord Hades.</text>
          </li>
        </beasts>
      </li>
    </modExtensions>
    <baseChance>0</baseChance>
    <letterDef>ThreatBig</letterDef>
  </IncidentDef>

  <IncidentDef>
    <defName>SZ_BeastApproachTunnel</defName>
    <label>The beast is coming! (It is recommended to click on the beast and view its detailed introduction)</label>
    <category>ThreatBig</category>
    <targetTags>
      <li>Map_PlayerHome</li>
    </targetTags>
    <workerClass>AncientChineseBeast.IncidentWorker_TunnelBeastApproach</workerClass>
    <modExtensions>
      <li Class="AncientChineseBeast.DefModExtension_Beasts">
        <beasts>
          <li>
            <pawn>SZ_SeXie</pawn>
            <label>色邪(Sex Evil)</label>
            <text>色邪，这种有着蝎子特征的人形凶兽总算是在我们面前露出了它的真容，据说它是华夏据点在基因凶兽里遇到的最难缠的对手，除了有各种特殊能力外，还可以进行形态转换，我们一定要小心了！\n\nSexie, this kind of humanoid beast with scorpion characteristics finally revealed its true face in front of us. It is said that it is the most difficult opponent encountered by the Huaxia colony among the genetic beasts. In addition to having various special abilities , you can also perform form transformation, we must be careful!</text>
          </li>
        </beasts>
      </li>
    </modExtensions>
    <baseChance>0</baseChance>
    <letterDef>ThreatBig</letterDef>
  </IncidentDef>
</Defs>