<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Ben Lubar's Android Tiers Patches</name>
	<author>Ben Lubar</author>
	<packageId>me.lubar.AndroidTiersPatches</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description><![CDATA[A collection of small patches for Android Tiers and related mods.

XML Patches (always active):

- Surrogate androids can be researched as soon as T1 androids are unlocked. Research that comes off of SX androids has been modified to have additional requirements.
- You can build the android parts workbench immediately after researching basic robotics, just like the other two workbenches.
- Adds a replacement voice synthesizer (in all three tiers of replacement part) for androids.
- The Civil Androids and Android Insurrection factions show up properly in the faction list at world generation.
- Civil Androids now requires a "classic" ideoligion, the same requirement as Civil Outlander Union.
- Android Insurrection now requires a Supremicist Raider ideoligion, and has a Kriminul culture, the same as Pirate Gang.
- Simple minded (the trait tier 1 androids have) now blocks Vanilla Social Interactions Expanded inspirations.

Harmony Patches (enabled by default, toggleable in settings):

- Android flesh counts as a space suit for Save Our Ship 2. (Note that this does not prevent frostbite from space.)
- Androids cannot get cancer and other human chronic diseases (if another mod tries to give them the disease).
- Basic androids cannot be targeted for conversion rituals (default) OR basic androids have the faction's primary ideoligion.
- Removes the Recreation need meter from basic androids that don't use it.

Supports, but does not require the following mods:

- Rimworld - Ideology (Official DLC)
- Android Tiers - Gynoids Reborn
- Save Our Ship 2
- Vanilla Social Interactions Expanded
]]></description>
	<url>https://git.lubar.me/rimworld-mods/android-tiers-patches</url>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</packageId>
			<displayName>HugsLib</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/UnlimitedHugs/RimworldHugsLib/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Atlas.AndroidTiers</packageId>
			<displayName>Android Tiers</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/Atla55/Android-Tiers-Core/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/1386412863</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
		<li>Atlas.AndroidTiers</li>
		<li>Winterbloom.ATGynoids</li>
		<li>kentington.saveourship2</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VanillaSocialInteractionsExpanded</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
