<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
     <NaiJiuHigh.label>Milk wine synergistic</NaiJiuHigh.label>
     <NaiJiuHigh.description>Milk wine is clear in color, sweet in taste, and has no odor. Because alcohol and dairy products are mixed in the production process, the colonists can get good health benefits after enjoying the milk wine. The colonists will feel full and energetic It will also be better, and at the same time, blood circulation will be improved. \n\nBecause the milk wine has a lower alcohol concentration, colonists are less likely to get drunk, become irritable and prone to fights, and are less affected by consciousness.</NaiJiuHigh.description>
     <NaiJiuHigh.labelNoun>Intoxicated</NaiJiuHigh.labelNoun>
     <NaiJiuHigh.stages.0.label>Slightly drunk</NaiJiuHigh.stages.0.label>
     <NaiJiuHigh.stages.1.label>Slightly drunk</NaiJiuHigh.stages.1.label>
     <NaiJiuHigh.stages.2.label>Revel</NaiJiuHigh.stages.2.label>
     <NaiJiuHigh.stages.3.label>Drunk</NaiJiuHigh.stages.3.label>
     <NaiJiuHigh.stages.4.label>Fragment</NaiJiuHigh.stages.4.label>

     <ShenZhouJiuAddiction.label>China alcohol addiction</ShenZhouJiuAddiction.label>
    <ShenZhouJiuAddiction.description>Excessive consumption of Shenzhou alcohol may cause colonists to develop addiction and dependence on Shenzhou alcohol. Although compared with beer and other alcohol, the raw materials used in the brewing of Shenzhou alcohol are less harmful to the nerves, but this is not It means that the colonists' addiction to Chinese alcohol is a good thing. \n\nIf the supply of alcohol products (including beer and Chinese alcohol) is lacking, colonists will have withdrawal reactions, and the brain will return to normal after a period of time, so that the problem of addiction can be fundamentally solved Of course, it will take longer for the colonists to get rid of their dependence on Shenzhou liquor.</ShenZhouJiuAddiction.description>

    <ShenZhouJiuTolerance.label>Shenzhou alcohol tolerance</ShenZhouJiuTolerance.label>
    <ShenZhouJiuTolerance.description>The colonists were produced by drinking Shenzhou liquor. The more severe the tolerance, the more Shenzhou liquor needed to obtain the same effect. \n\nFortunately, the negative effects of the raw materials of Shenzhou liquor are very small, so this tolerance dissipates quickly.</ShenZhouJiuTolerance.description>



</LanguageData>