<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
    <name>Trainers, Serum, and AI Crafting</name>
    <author>Noromyx</author>
	<packageId>Noromyx.TrainersSerumAICrafting</packageId>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.3</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <description>
This is an update to Malkav73's mod, Neurotrainer Etc. Crafting: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1578693166
	
With this mod you'll be able to craft Neurotrainers, Psytrainers, mechanite serums, and AI cores.
	
	
!!!WARNING!!! This mod only supports Rimworld version 1.3.
	
I've made some pretty extensive changes to the original mod to bring it more in line with the impact it has on the game. My goal was to make it less "cheaty" and make it something you had to sink a balanced amount of time and resources into to obtain these very valuable items. Below is a complete list of changes I've made.
		
All obtainable Psytrainers have been added to the crafting table.
		
Modified the Neurotrainer research project:
	Tech Level: Industrial > Spacer
	Requirements: Electricity > Hi-Tech Research Bench w/ Multianalyzer
		
Added research projects for:
	Psytrainers with the same requirements as Neurotrainers. Requires first researching Neurotrainers.
	Mechanite Serums with the same requirements as Neurotrainers, research cost increased 1200 > 2500 and tech level increased Spacer > Ultratech. Requires first researching Neurotrainers.
	Artificial Intelligence Cores with the same requirements as Neurotrainers, research cost increased 1200 > 3000 and tech level increased Spacer > Ultratech. Requires first researching Neurotrainers.
		
Neurotrainer Crafting Station build costs changed:
	60 Wood, 50 Steel > 75 Steel, 15 Gold, 3 Component, 1 Advanced Component
		
Neurotrainers base recipe changed from:
	Effect: ButcherFlesh > Smith (so you wont see blood flying when crafting these things?)
	Recipe: 10 Silver, 2 Gold, 65 Steel, 10 Plasteel, 1 Uranium, 1 Glitterworld Medicine > 25 Steel, 10 Plasteel, 10 Devilstrand, 50 Silver, 2 Advanced Components
		
Trainers and serums now have a separate recipe. Serum recipe is now: 100 Plasteel, 75 Silver, 50 Gold, 25 Uranium, 20 Devilstrand, 5 Advanced Components
    </description>
</ModMetaData>