<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

  <!-- Research Tab --> 
  <ResearchTabDef>
    <defName>Autoinjectors</defName>
    <label>Autoinjectors</label>
  </ResearchTabDef>


  <!-- Research Projects -->
  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>Distilation</defName>
    <label>drug extraction</label>
    <description>Use the drug lab to derive extracts from various drugs. Used primarily for medical applications.</description>
    <baseCost>400</baseCost>
    <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
    <tab>Autoinjectors</tab>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>DrugProduction</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchViewX>0.00</researchViewX>
    <researchViewY>1.40</researchViewY>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>Autoinjection</defName>
    <label>autoinjection</label>
    <description>Create Autoinjection devices. Allows creation of intravenous(IV) autoinjection and hand-held autoinjection devices. IV autoinjectors automatically administer a dose of the drug after a condition is met. Hand-held autoinjectors apply a more refined form a given drug, meaning they typically last longer and have lesser negative effects.</description>
    <baseCost>600</baseCost>
    <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
    <tab>Autoinjectors</tab>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>Distilation</li>
      <li>Prosthetics</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchViewX>1.00</researchViewX>
    <researchViewY>0.70</researchViewY>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>AdvAutoinjection</defName>
    <label>advanced autoinjection</label>
    <description>Create IV autoinjectors which contain the medical form of a given drug, the same form as the drug as the hand-held autoinjectors, meaning more potency with less negative effects. Common technology on Glitterworlds, where nearly everybody is fitted with at least a single advanced autoinjector, and getting them replaced is as common as a dentist visit or a routine check-up.</description>
    <baseCost>600</baseCost>
    <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
    <tab>Autoinjectors</tab>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>Autoinjection</li>
      <li>Bionics</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchViewX>2.00</researchViewX>
    <researchViewY>0.70</researchViewY>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>Prevent</defName>
    <label>medical drugs</label>
    <description>Allows the extraction of active ingredients from Penoxycyline in order to create autoinjectors. The drug lasts signicantly longer in it's injected form. Penoxycyline can only be made into hand-held autoinjectors. Only requires a single Penoxycyline to create the extract.</description>
    <baseCost>600</baseCost>
    <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
    <tab>Autoinjectors</tab>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>Distilation</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchViewX>1.00</researchViewX>
    <researchViewY>2.10</researchViewY>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>Morphine</defName>
    <label>morphine</label>
    <description>Allows the creation of morphine extract from psychite tea for use in autoinjectors. Greatly reduces pain and increases mood significantly, but users get tired slightly faster. Is under extreme demand due to it's medical application, leading to it having more value than the work required to create it would have one imagine.</description>
    <baseCost>600</baseCost>
    <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
    <tab>Autoinjectors</tab>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>Distilation</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchViewX>1.00</researchViewX>
    <researchViewY>2.80</researchViewY>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>Social</defName>
    <label>social drugs</label>
    <description>Allows the extraction of the active ingredients from Ambrosia, Beer and Smokeleaf in order to create autoinjectors. All are engineered to provide effects for a longer period of time, with less of a hit to manipulation, movement speed and conciousness. Can be made into both hand-held and IV autoinjectors.</description>
    <baseCost>400</baseCost>
    <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
    <tab>Autoinjectors</tab>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>Distilation</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchViewX>2.00</researchViewX>
    <researchViewY>2.10</researchViewY>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>Hard</defName>
    <label>hard drugs</label>
    <description>Allows the extraction of the active ingredients from Flake and Yayo in order to create autoinjectors. All are engineered to provide effects for a longer period of time, with less of a hit to manipulation, movement speed and conciousness. Can be made into both hand-held and IV autoinjectors.</description>
    <baseCost>400</baseCost>
    <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
    <tab>Autoinjectors</tab>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>PsychiteRefining</li>
      <li>Distilation</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchViewX>3.00</researchViewX>
    <researchViewY>2.10</researchViewY>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>Work</defName>
    <label>work related drugs</label>
    <description>Allows extraction of the active ingredients out of drugs used by people in arduous professions to increase proformance, namely Wake Up and Go-Juice. Both can be made into hand-held, IV and advanced IV autoinjectors.</description>
    <baseCost>400</baseCost>
    <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
    <tab>Autoinjectors</tab>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>Distilation</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchViewX>2.00</researchViewX>
    <researchViewY>2.80</researchViewY>
  </ResearchProjectDef>
</Defs>