<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="SoftWarmBeds.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <modNameReadable>Soft Warm Beds</modNameReadable>
    <modIdentifier>JPT_SoftWarmBeds</modIdentifier>
    <!--<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1713295858</linkUrl>-->
    <linkUrl>https://ko-fi.com/jptrrs</linkUrl>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="SoftWarmBeds.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>SoftWarmBeds_1_0_6</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.0.6</assemblyVersion>
    <content>Check out the new options panel (Options > Mod Settings), where you can customize the beds' color scheme to your liking!|Also, notice the beddings' category has been changed to &lt;i&gt;Apparel&lt;/i&gt;, for compatibility purposes.|The full change log is on our Steam Workshop page.</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="SoftWarmBeds.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>SoftWarmBeds_2_0_0</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>2.0.0</assemblyVersion>
    <content>&lt;b&gt;Your beds have just been improved!&lt;/b&gt;|- The code for the bed insulation properties has been revised to overcome a RimWorld quirk. Now it will also affect your pawn's "Slept in Cold/Heat" thoughts, just like it was supposed to.|- You can now copy &amp; paste beddings settings from one bed to another.|- &lt;i&gt;Hospitality&lt;/i&gt; is no longer required!|- Improved performance &amp; compatibility with other mods.|You can find the full change log on our Steam Workshop page.|(NOTE: Due to the changes, loading a saved game for the first time with the development mode activated might produce some red errors on the log window. They are harmless, please just ignore them.)</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="SoftWarmBeds.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>SoftWarmBeds_2_5</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>2.5</assemblyVersion>
    <content>
      &lt;b&gt;A new feature was added to the mod settings!&lt;/b&gt;
      |img:MiyuriMode|caption:You can now choose to have your beds manually unmade by a colonist, instead of the bedding just popping out when you command it to unmake. It works just like other game objects with and on/off switch. 

To activate this, open the mod settings panel (Options > Mod Settings) and select &lt;i&gt;Require a colonist to unmake beds&lt;/i&gt;.
      |Other improvements on this version:
      |- The rest effectiveness for the Animal Bed was adjusted so it doesn't get too powerful once the textile softness bonus is applied.
      |- The report window for a sleeping pawn takes the bed into account for the min/max comfortable temperature calculation once again (it was missing on RW 1.1).
    </content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>  
  
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="SoftWarmBeds.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>SoftWarmBeds_2_6</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>2.6.1</assemblyVersion>
	<content>
      &lt;b&gt;I want your opinion!&lt;/b&gt;
      |I'm conducting a survey on what textile materials added by other mods turn up with a weird softness value. This information could help us improve the formula that generates it. If you use a mod that adds textiles and its softness number feels odd to you, drop me a line! Just follow the link above or look for the discussion on our steam page.
	  |Thank you!

      |&lt;b&gt;Improvements on this version:&lt;/b&gt;
	  |- New languages added: Italian &amp; Chinese (courtesy of Sergio di Napoli &amp; leafzxg respectively).
	  |- Improved performance on Hospitality integration (courtesy of Lannan).
	  |- Animal Beds now provide cold insulation to your pets, same as bedrolls.
	  |- Fixed error when adding beds to caravans.
	  |- Updated load order rules for various mods.
    </content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="SoftWarmBeds.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>SoftWarmBeds_2_7</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>2.7</assemblyVersion>
    <content>&lt;b&gt;Improved integration with Vanilla Factions Expanded - Vikings!&lt;/b&gt;
    |img:../Textures/Things/Beddings/FurBeddingSingle,../Textures/Things/Beddings/FurBeddingDouble
    |If you're playing with that mod, we have some news for you. Now the fur beds will also require the use of separate beddings for them to achieve their full potential!
    |The new &lt;b&gt;Fur Beddings&lt;/b&gt; can be made at the &lt;i&gt;Crafting Spot&lt;/i&gt; or the &lt;i&gt;Tailoring Bech&lt;/i&gt; just like the regular ones. They require more material to be produced, but become available before the regular beddings, alongside the fur beds themselves (unless you're also using &lt;i&gt;Vanilla Furniture Expanded&lt;/i&gt;, in which case they will require the research of &lt;i&gt;Basic Furniture&lt;/i&gt;). Thanks to JupiterLily for this awesome addition!
    |This version also includes new translations for Spanish and Russian (courtesy of Chivalry Dark &amp; Stalin).
    |Enjoy!
    |img:Ko-fi|caption:Making mods is fun, mantaining them takes a lot of work! If you like what we did here, please consider supporting us with a cup of coffee. Follow the link above or go to ko-fi.com/jptrrs. Thank you!
    </content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

</Defs>