<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>[KIR]Extra Mechanoid Units and Equipment</name>
  <author>Kirby23590</author>
  <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>Kirby.ExtraMechanoidsUnits</packageId>
  <description>Sooo you fought Centipedes, Scythers, Lancers and Pikemen. 
  
  But you felt like it's not enough variety 
  or is just boring to have the same mechs over and over?
  
  What if you wanted the a mech with a ranged weapon with deadly melee 
  or give the lancers and pikemen a automatic blaster and a mini inferno cannon?
  
  Or maybe it's missing lil mechs that explode when you destroy them?
  Now with this mod you'll have new 6 mechanoid units!
  And it will also give the lancers and pikeman a new extra weapon!
  
  &lt;size=24&gt;Mechanoid Types:&lt;/size&gt;
  
  -- Tick: Fast, small mechanoids that explode in death that can start fires.
  
  -- Ratite: Small fast biped but weak mechanoids who can use cover.
  
  -- Prowler: Very fast melee mechanoids resembling large feline predators.
  
  -- Jaeger: Melee or Ranged mechanoids with a melee blade, also uses cover.
  
  -- Hoplite: Very durable ranged mechanoids that use powerful medium range weapons.
  
  -- Dragoon: Very frail snipers that are equipped with a powerful long-ranged weapon.
  
  
  &lt;size=24&gt;Mechanoid Weapons:&lt;/size&gt;
  
  -- Mini-charge blaster: Only used by Ratites, not very damaaging but it has a high-fire rate.
  
  -- Inferno mini-launcher: A smaller inferno cannon with a smaller blast radius, used by Pikemen.
  
  -- Hoplite charge blaster: Obviously used by Hoplites. Fires 5 shots in burst.
  
  -- Bolter: A powerful slug-thrower that can pierce armor, used by Hoplites.
  
  -- Riveter: Very inaccurate but has a high-fire rate and fire 5 shots in short bursts, used by Jaegers.
  
  -- Jaeger smoke launcher: Fires a single smoke grenade that can prevent turrets from locking on.
  
  -- Dragoon rail lance: A very powerful ranged weapon used by dragoons, has extreme range but has a long cooldown.
  
  &lt;size=20&gt;And two useable weapons for your soldiers!&lt;/size&gt;
  
  -- Assault charge blaster: Used by lancers, and fires 4 shots in burst. But can be used by human hands and made in Fabrication Benches.
  
  -- Charge scatterer: A short-ranged powerful weapon used by Hoplites and Jaegers. Also can be made in Fabrication Benches and used by your soldiers.
  </description>
  
</ModMetaData>