<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>Ultima Core</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>Bowen.Ultima.Core</modIdentifier>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>Core_1_3_1_8</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.1.8</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
          img:images/UNews|caption:
|

This update:

  * Several items have been removed from Core as they are now (and have been) moved to Britannia Construction Co. and the Artisan's Guild.
    Items affected include the Ornate column, street lamp, all floors, walls and the display counter.
  * Goblins and Gwani should no longer spawn with most of the traits from A Rimworld of Magic as neither race is supposed to posses any affinity for magic and most of the fighter traits are not appropriate for them. 
	
Incompatibility / Known Issues:
  * Gwani seems to be spawning with antique armor.  Bad Gwani!  
  
In Development:
  Gargoyles
  Bestiary

Currently Planned/Considering:
  Apothecary
  Cult of Runes
  Cult of Truth
  The Blue Boar (Food and Drink)
  More Factions
	
RimWorlds of Ultima Discord: https://discord.gg/pgSbHce
1 Cor 13
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>Core_1_3_1_7</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.1.7</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
          img:images/UNews|caption:
|
I'm going to be moving content that is not specifically shared among factions to new mods at the end of Oct.  The mods are Britannia Construction Co. and Artisan's Guild. 

Items affected include the Ornate column, street lamp, all floors and the display counter.

This update:

  * Updated trapper caravan.  They should no longer deal with human skin (Medieval Overhaul) or alien leathers (O21 Toolbox).
  * Basic gargoyles are in.  Quite a bit of work to do still before their faction is ready but some of you should no longer see errors about missing textures etc.
	
Incompatibility / Known Issues:
  * Gwani seems to be spawning with antique armor.  Bad Gwani!  
  * Antique armor doesn't yield resources when salvaged. 
  
In Development:
  Gargoyles
  Bestiary

Currently Planned/Considering:
  Apothecary
  Cult of Runes
  Cult of Truth
  The Blue Boar (Food and Drink)
  More Factions
	
RimWorlds of Ultima Discord: https://discord.gg/pgSbHce
1 Cor 13
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>Core_1_3_1_6</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.1.6</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
          img:images/UNews|caption:
|
I'm going to be moving content that is not specifically shared among factions to a new mod.  The Britannia Construction Co.  This will be all floors, walls and buildings. (Apparel is meant to be shared so it will be staying in core.)

BCC will focuses mainly on structures and floors or items of a similiar nature. I will go through a similiar process with the Artisan's Guild now in development. 

There will be a transition period of at least several weeks where this content will remain in Core to give time for everyone to get the new mod if they want to use that content. 

This update:

  * Added apparel: Winter coat
  * Updated support for Rimworld of Magic 
  * New Trapper's Caravan (selling mostly leathers including hides from Medieval Overhaul)
  * Probably some other stuff.  
	
Incompatibility / Known Issues:
  * Gwani seems to be spawning with antique armor.  Bad Gwani!  
  * Antique armor doesn't yield resources when salvaged. 
  
In Development:
  Artisan's Guild
  Gargoyles
  Bestiary

Currently Planned/Considering:
  Apothecary
  Cult of Runes
  Cult of Truth
  The Blue Boar (Food and Drink)
  More Factions
	
RimWorlds of Ultima Discord: https://discord.gg/pgSbHce
1 Cor 13
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>Core_1_3_1_5</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.1.5</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
          img:images/UNews|caption:
|
This update:

  * Added 8 colored 'fine' carpets under the fine carpet dropdown.
  * Removed defaultfaction from some base pawns.  Should fix the wall of red Core gives when you don't have a particular faction installed. :P
	
Incompatibility / Known Issues:
  *	Roloo's Dual Wield mod.  It's not a hard compatibility issue but I do plan on adding shields at some point and it would be weird if you had a shield and a weapon in the off hand. (Shields will count as apparel)
  * Gwani seems to be spawning with antique armor.  Bad Gwani!  
  * Antique armor doesn't yield resources when salvaged. 
  
In Development:
  EXOTICS!
  Gargoyles
  Bestiary

Currently Planned/Considering:
  Apothecary
  Artisan's Guild
  Cult of Runes
  Cult of Truth
  The Blue Boar (Food and Drink)
  More Factions
	
RimWorlds of Ultima Discord: https://discord.gg/pgSbHce
1 Cor 13
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>Core_1_3_1_4</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.1.4</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
          img:images/UNews|caption:
|
This update:

  * All new caravans for factions.  (Probably needs tweaking, feedback appeciated)
  * Updated art for Gwani.
  * Goblins and Gwani now have their own starting scenarios. 
	
Incompatibility / Known Issues:
  *	Roloo's Dual Wield mod.  It's not a hard compatibility issue but I do plan on adding shields at some point and it would be weird if you had a shield and a weapon in the off hand. (Shields will count as apparel)
  * Gwani seems to be spawning with antique armor.  Bad Gwani!  
  * Antique armor is not salvagable. 
  
In Development:
  Gargoyles
  Bestiary

Currently Planned/Considering:
  Apothecary
  Artisan's Guild
  Cult of Runes
  Cult of Truth
  The Blue Boar (Food and Drink)
  More Factions
	
RimWorlds of Ultima Discord: https://discord.gg/pgSbHce
1 Cor 13
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>Core_1_3_1_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.1.3</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
          img:images/UNews|caption:
|
This update:

  * Race compatibility with Lord of the Rims. 
	Renamed some leather Defs to share with LotR so there's no overlap. They were identical otherwise anyway. 
	Ultima races will share meat types with their LotR counterparts. (Unfortunately, they still have separate corpses.)
  * Moved settlement namer for the Fellowship to CORE (it was in Britannia.. DOH!)
  * Support for the new faction of Buccaneer's Den.
  * Minor tweaks to the merchant dress.
	
Known Incompatibility
	I'm going to go ahead and declare Roloo's Dual Wield mod as incompatible.  It's not a hard compatibility issue but I do plan on adding shields at some point and it would be weird if you had a shield and a weapon in the off hand. (Shields will count as apparel)

RimWorlds of Ultima Discord: https://discord.gg/pgSbHce
1 Cor 13
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>Core_1_3_1_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.1.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
          img:images/UNews|caption:
|
This update:

  * Fixed a typo in the research Defs that will probably require some of you to redo the research projects to unlock content.  Sorry about that. 
  * Bunch of behind the scenes stuff for additional factions.
  * Added primitive straw and pelt beds for all of your comfy neolithic sleeping needs.  
  * The Ornate Column is now a column style.  I'm leaving the original object in for awhile in case it's being used in current games but I will probably remove it eventually. 
  * Gwanifur should now be available. Where does that come from I wonder? 
  * Fixed some compatibility issues with Medieval Overhaul

RimWorlds of Ultima Discord: https://discord.gg/pgSbHce
1 Cor 13
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>


	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>Core_1_3_1_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.1.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
          img:images/UNews|caption:
|
This update:

  * JecsTools users will see the return of racial bonuses for Elves, Dwarves and Hobbits. 
  * Added new Meme - The Triad of Inner Strength (guess what I'm working on now?) :)
  * Added apparel Monk Robe and Monk Hood.
  * Probably a few other things I can't entirely recall.

  Known Issue: The Ornate Column is not satisfying Royalty throne room requirements despite the patch.  I'm hoping to make it a style of standard columns for better compatibility.

RimWorlds of Ultima Discord: https://discord.gg/pgSbHce
1 Cor 13
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>Core_1_3_1_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
          img:images/UNews|caption:
|
This update: I'm beginning to make some changes to CORE now that Ultima: ARMOURY is out and updates to other mods.
|
  * Guard Armor will no longer be craftable in CORE. Guards (from Britannia) will use plate armor and tabards from Armoury.
  * The magic bow is no longer craftable.  This is in preparation for moving it to another mod. (It shouldn't be craftable anyway)
  * Added Britannic Culture w/ Virtues of the Avatar Meme. WIP This is mainly for the Factions: Britannia mod but may be expanded
    Right now it still requires some hands on tweaking. ie Relics, titles, events etc  
  * Elves, dwarves and bobbits should play nicer with the style station. 
  * New civilian clothes for Factions
  * Visible content in CORE is now locked behind light weight research projects.

  Known Issue: The Ornate Column is not satisfying Royalty throne room requirements despite the patch.  I'm hoping to make it a style of standard columns for better compatibility.

RimWorlds of Ultima Discord: https://discord.gg/pgSbHce
1 Cor 13
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>