<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Defs>
	<XenotypeDef>
		<defName>RBM_Minotaur</defName>
		<label>minotaur</label>
		<!-- Desc -->
		<description>The ancient origins of the minotaur are shrouded in mystery, helped not by their hostility towards humans. Man once reared minotaur as they did cattle — branding them with hot irons and enslaving them as labourers or cannon fodder. Today, minotaur civilisations are typically found as far away from humans as possible. An exception to this rule are the "guardians": minotaur bred and sworn to protect the monarchy of mentally superior but physically inferior xenos. \n\nMinotaurs are generally characterised by their short tempers and inability to comprehend the lofty concepts that other xenos do. They go into heat every Aprimay, are able to digest plant matter with ease and celebrate every victory with a bellowing moo.</description>
		<descriptionShort>Standing at a staggering height, the ancient minotaur are known for their ability to thrive in even the most bitter corners of the world thanks to their imposing might, hardy stomachs and cloven hooves. Their characteristically short temper and general sturdiness can make them a formidable foe on the battlefield.</descriptionShort>
		<!-- Stats -->
		<iconPath>UI/XenotypeIcons/MinotaurBull</iconPath>
		<inheritable>true</inheritable>
		<nameMaker>NamerPersonMinotaur_Male</nameMaker>
		<nameMakerFemale>NamerPersonMinotaur_Female</nameMakerFemale>
		<chanceToUseNameMaker>69</chanceToUseNameMaker> <!-- Nice -->
		<combatPowerFactor>1.3</combatPowerFactor>
		<genes>
			<!-- Ability -->
			<li>RBM_BovineTemper</li>
			<!-- Cosmetic -->
			<li>RBM_BovineHead</li>
			<li>RBM_BovineEars</li>
			<li>RBM_BovineHorns</li>
			<li>RBM_BovineVoice</li>
			<li>RBM_UnguligradeLegs</li>
			<li>RBM_EstrousCycle</li>
			<li>RBM_RuminantStomach</li>
			<li>RBM_Herculean</li>
			<!-- Skins -->
			<li>RBM_EarthySkin</li>
			<li>Skin_InkBlack</li>
			<li>Skin_SlateGray</li>
			<li>Skin_LightGray</li>
			<li>Skin_SheerWhite</li>
			<li>Skin_Orange</li>
			<!-- Skills -->
			<li>AptitudePoor_Intellectual</li>
			<li>AptitudePoor_Social</li>
			<!-- Optional -->
			<li>RBM_PeriodicLactation</li>
		</genes>
	</XenotypeDef>
</Defs>