<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>Progressive Recipies</name>
    <author>XiaNight</author>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.4</li>
    </supportedVersions>

    <loadAfter>
        <li>VanillaExpanded.VARME</li>
    </loadAfter>

    <packageId>XiaNight.Progressive.Recipies</packageId>
    <description>
        Adds recipes for crafting items progressively.

        Don't you hate when you upgrade all your pawn's armor, say from flak armor to recon armor, you need to spend a lot of time crafting the recon armor, and then the flak armor is no use; it doesn't even have enough market value.
        say no more, this mod adds recipes with little additional materials that make you available to craft upgraded armor from lower tier armors, and no armor/materials/time are wasted.

        This mod adds recipies that helps you upgrade armors, this mod won't remove existing recipies, so you can still make armors directly from raw materials.

        Vanilla Armor Expanded supported!

        -- Recipies:

        - Upgrade to Flak Helmet
        Ingredients: Simple Helmet x1, Plasteel x10, Component x2
        Required Research: FlakArmor

        - Upgrade to Recon Helmet
        Ingredients: Flak Helmet x1, Plasteel x20, Advanced Component x1
        Required Research: ReconArmor

        - Upgrade to Recon Armor
        Ingredients: Flak Jacket x1, Flak Armor x1, PLasteel x80, Advanced Component x3, Uranium x10
        Required Research: ReconArmor

        - Upgrade to Marine Helmet
        Ingredients: Recon Helmet x1, Plasteel x10
        Required Research: MarineArmor
        
        - Upgrade to Marine Armor
        Ingredients: Recon Armor x1, Plasteel x20, Advanced Component x1, Uranium x 10
        Required Research: MarineArmor

        -- Vanilla Armor Expanded Recipies

        - Upgrade to Trooper Helmet
        Ingredients: Flak Helmet x1, Plasteel x15, Advanced Component x1
        Required Research: TrooperArmor

        - Upgrade to Trooper Armor
        Ingredients: Flak Jacket x1, Flak Armor x1, PLasteel x65, Advanced Component x2, Uranium x5
        Required Research: TrooperArmor

        - Upgrade to Siege Breaker Helmet
        Ingredients: Trooper Helmet x1, Plasteel x20, Component x1
        Required Research: SiegebreakerArmor

        - Upgrade to Siege Breaker Armor
        Ingredients: Trooper Armor x1, Plasteel x95, Advanced Component x4, Uranium x 35
        Required Research: SiegebreakerArmor

    </description>
</ModMetaData>