<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<TipSetDef>
		<defName>BDP_Tips</defName>
		<tips>
			<li>While other people tends to left spent lizion cells on the ground, your colonists will put the ejected casing in ther inventory.</li>
			<li>Cryogenic lizion gives pawns frostbites, harm plants and extinguish fires, but they're harmless against anything else.</li>
			<li>Overcharged cells are inaccurate and they damage cells beyong repair, but they pack some real punch.</li>
		</tips>
	</TipSetDef>

	<!--
	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>BDP_LizionProduction</defName>
		<label>lizion production</label>
		<priority>50</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>false</needsOpportunity>
		<helpText></helpText>
		<highlightTags>
			<li>BDGW_RailRearm</li>
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>
-->

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>BDP_LizionProduction</defName>
		<label>lizion production</label>
		<priority>50</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>false</needsOpportunity>
		<helpText>In order to produce lizion, you'll need air inlets and lizion extractors, connected with air pipes and preferably a buffer air tank. Air inlets needs clear space to operate, or their efficiency decreases. Steam geyser intakes are another solution that're fast and not space consuming, but their availbility are restricted just like other steam geyser using buildings.\n\nLizion produced from refineries can be stored in tanks for other uses or used to fill cells into actual ammo using fillers.</helpText>
		<highlightTags>
			<li>BDGW_RailRearm</li>
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>BDP_LizionCells</defName>
		<label>lizion cells</label>
		<priority>50</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>false</needsOpportunity>
		<helpText>Most plasma weapons accept standarized lizion cells as ammo. Empty cells are produced at fabrication bench, and they need to be inserted into a lizion cell filler in order to become usable.\n\nCell-using plasma weapons eject empty cells ready to be refilled again. The quality, remaining durability and the nature of the weapon will affect the chances cells being ejected undamaged, with less powerful weapons being more cell-efficient.\n\nOvercharged cells are always damaged in the firing process.</helpText>
		<highlightTags>
			<li>BDGW_RailRearm</li>
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>BDP_LizionBackpack</defName>
		<label>lizion tank backpack</label>
		<priority>50</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>false</needsOpportunity>
		<helpText>The lizion tank backpack is a versatile piece of equipment, colonists will automatcally fill them at cell fillers if their backpack is not full.\n\nApart from the built in lizion deflector, it also comes with several abilities useful in combat.\n\nAnother function the backpack has is feeding handheld plasma weapons, toggled when holding a suitable weapon and pressing siphon mode gizmo. If not working, try press the reconnect button. Weapons using tanked gas can only fire standard plasma bolts due to standarized pressure, but they don't need to reload until tank is depleted.</helpText>
		<highlightTags>
			<li>BDGW_RailRearm</li>
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>BDP_LizionShield</defName>
		<label>lizion deflector</label>
		<priority>50</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>false</needsOpportunity>
		<helpText>The lizion deflector, or shield for short, will mitigate any heat damage using stored gas, depending on the amount of damage. They have a chance of malfunction depending on its quality, leaking at most 50% damage past.\n\nThe shield may also spray a small amount of lizion at the user when he/she is on fire or suffering heatstrokes. The amount of lizion spent depends on fire size and heatstroke severity.</helpText>
		<highlightTags>
			<li>BDGW_RailRearm</li>
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>BDP_LizionExtinguisher</defName>
		<label>lizion fire extinguisher</label>
		<priority>50</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>false</needsOpportunity>
		<helpText>Extinguishers are fire fighting equipments fueled by liquid lizion. Your colonists will try to refill them from fillers if selected drop logic permits. You can also change how it's automatic dropping behavior should behave.</helpText>
		<highlightTags>
			<li>BDGW_RailRearm</li>
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>
</Defs>
