<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
<name>PRF-More Machines (v1.4)</name>
<packageId>Daemon976.PRFMoreMachinesV2</packageId>
<author>Daemon976</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.mod</li>
		<li>spdskatr.projectrimfactory</li>
		<li>Adventurer.ExpandWoodwork</li>
		<li>Argon.VMEu</li>
		<li>MrKociak.MoreArchotechStuffandThingsReupload</li>
		<li>vanillaexpanded.helixiengas</li>
		<li>vanillaexpanded.vchemfuele</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<incompatibleWith>
		<li>PRF.Materials</li>
	</incompatibleWith>
  <description>This mod adds some additional machines to Project RimFactory Revived (version 2.50+) that are direct upgrades to core workbenches, plus a few mod bonus machines.

Adds:

Drug Synthesizer - A fully automated system capable of synthesizing anything the drug lab can create.

CNC Machining System - A fully automated upgrade from the manual Machining Table.

CNC Fabrication System - A fully automated advanced fabrication system designed for mass-production.

Textile Factory - Tired of slaving over a hot sewing machine? Build this and let it do all the tailoring for you!

Lumber Mill (Req. Expanded Woodworking) - Look Ma, no splinters! Let this device process all your wood for you.

Plasma Furnace - A variant of the PRF-Materials Plasma Furnace that doesn't require PRF-Materials

Materials Refinery - A variant of the PRF-Materials Materials Refinery that doesn't require PRF-Materials

Stone Fabricator - A variant of the PRF-Materials Stone Fabricator that doesn't require PRF-Materials

Archotech Assembler - (Req. More Archotech Garbage) An automated factory created by slapping a lot of Archotech Fragments onto a PRF machine base which miraculously creates a working factory.

Includes Helixien and Chemfuel powered variants of some machines if you have VHGE and/or VHCE.

   </description>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>spdskatr.projectrimfactory</packageId>
      <displayName>Project RimFactory Revived</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2033979700</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>
