<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
	<kathanon.TableRange.SearchRange.title>Max distance to walk to table</kathanon.TableRange.SearchRange.title>
	<kathanon.TableRange.SearchRange.desc>When a pawn is deciding to eat, what is the maximum (straight-line) distance they will walk to find a table? Individual tables can override this.</kathanon.TableRange.SearchRange.desc>
	<kathanon.TableRange.IndividualRange.title>Per-table setting</kathanon.TableRange.IndividualRange.title>
	<kathanon.TableRange.IndividualRange.desc>Allow setting maximum range for individual tables.</kathanon.TableRange.IndividualRange.desc>
	<kathanon.TableRange.DisplayRange.title>Display use area</kathanon.TableRange.DisplayRange.title>
	<kathanon.TableRange.DisplayRange.desc>When placing a table, display the area that pawns can use that table from.</kathanon.TableRange.DisplayRange.desc>
	<kathanon.TableRange.RangeToAll.title>Display area for all chairs</kathanon.TableRange.RangeToAll.title>
	<kathanon.TableRange.RangeToAll.desc>When displaying the use area, use the area from within all chairs of the table are reachable - i.e. the maximum area from where pawns can use the table if all seats are free. 
Otherwise, the area from where any of the chairs are reachable is used - i.e. the area from where pawns can use the table unless all seats are taken.</kathanon.TableRange.RangeToAll.desc>
	<kathanon.TableRange.UseChairs.title>Use any existing chairs</kathanon.TableRange.UseChairs.title>
	<kathanon.TableRange.UseChairs.desc>When displaying the use area, if there are any chairs or blueprints for chairs already placed, only the area for the placed chairs will be shown. If disabled, all potential chair spots will always be used.</kathanon.TableRange.UseChairs.desc>
	<kathanon.TableRange.Selected.title>Display area for selected</kathanon.TableRange.Selected.title>
	<kathanon.TableRange.Selected.desc>Also display the use area when an already placed table is selected.</kathanon.TableRange.Selected.desc>
	<kathanon.TableRange.Merge.title>Display selected area merged</kathanon.TableRange.Merge.title>
	<kathanon.TableRange.Merge.desc>When displaying the use area of multiple selected tables, display the combined range instead of each individual. Holding control (or control) inverts this setting.</kathanon.TableRange.Merge.desc>

    <kathanon.TableRange.UseRange>Set Range</kathanon.TableRange.UseRange>
	<kathanon.TableRange.UseRange.tip>Set a specific maximum range that pawns will use this table from, overriding the global value.</kathanon.TableRange.UseRange.tip>
</LanguageData>