<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
 
  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>ThermalsuitArmorPrototypes</defName>
    <label>Basic chemical trials</label>
    <description>Iron Accord technology operates on increasingly complex, harder-to-produce chemicals. Their tech-trees are described as "backwards".
 Among the simplest, evaporative agents and exothermic reactions can heat up or cool down the user inside a thermal suit with the flick of a few dials.
 Understanding these base-level chemical applications opens a path to more interesting applications...</description>
    <baseCost>2000</baseCost>
    <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
    <researchViewX>4.00</researchViewX>
    <researchViewY>4.10</researchViewY>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>PowerArmorPrototypes</defName>
    <label>Intermediate biochem-steroid trials</label>
    <description>MFAS-armors use a series of pulleys and levers to trade speed for strength, ultimately allowing a man to wear his weight in metal.
 The suit itself is simple, but building and sustaining the strength to wear it isn't, especially with a chronic shortage of organic resources.
 Childhood growth hormones ('Controlled' hypertrophy) and biochemical food supplements (Endothermic bacteria and oil decomposers) get the job done, with unpleasant side effects.
 This unlocks the Gamma-tier and Beta-tier armors as well as their respective steroid treatments.
 Further understanding could discover the secrets of their elite Alpha units...</description>
    <baseCost>4000</baseCost>
    <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>ThermalsuitArmorPrototypes</li>
    </prerequisites>	
    <researchViewX>4.00</researchViewX>
    <researchViewY>4.10</researchViewY>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>EVAArmorPrototypes</defName>
    <label>Advanced ferrochemical trials</label>
    <description>At first glance, the use of soft citadel steel seems insane for armor use. It's soft and performs fairly poorly for it's weight.
 However, the suits and broken machines you studied have been here for a thousand years, with no signs of rust or corrosion.
 The patterns are difficult to properly manufacture, but the concepts are simply escalation. Citadel steel will stand forever, in space or on earth.
 This unlocks the infamous Alpha MFAS, and functional EVA-suits.</description>
    <baseCost>6000</baseCost>
    <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>PowerArmorPrototypes</li>
    </prerequisites>	
    <researchViewX>5</researchViewX>
    <researchViewY>4.10</researchViewY>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

</Defs>
