<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Area Rugs 2.0</name>
  <author>TheGoofyOne</author>
	<url>about:blank</url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.0</li>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>TheGoofyOne.AreaRugs</packageId>
  <description>Area Rugs 2.0
  
Area Rugs 2.0
  
Version 2.6

This mod adds to RimWorld:

Square rugs (1x1 to 7x7 tiles)
Hall runners (1x2 to 1x7 tiles)
Wide Hall runners (2x3 to 2x8 tiles)
Rectangle rugs (2x3 to 6x8 tiles)
Big Rectangle Rugs (6X10, 8X10, 10X12)
Circular rugs with and without the Rimworld logo. 1x1 to 7x7 tiles
Footprint Door Mats in 1X1, 1X2, and 1X3. Do NOT clean.
Rim Rug 3X5 
Round Fancy Rug 3X3
Beer 30 Rug 3X5
Eye Of Ra Rug 3X5
Lady Rug 3X5 
Puzzle Rug 3X5
Persian Rug 4X6 
Egyptian Rug 4X6
Prayer Rug 2X3
Play Mat 3X5
Vanilla Bear Rugs 4X4 
Thrumbo Rug 4X4 
Megasloth Rug 4X4
Muffalo Rug 4X4

NOTES/CHANGES to VANILLA:

Butchering Megasloth, Grizzly Bears, Polar Bears, and Muffalo now also produces a skin for carpetmaking.
Butchering Thrumbos does not produce a horn anymore but a Thrumbo Skin usable to make a Thrumbo Rug which has the head with the horn on it. You can remove the horn still with a new process at the Rug Making Table.

Mod will most likely not work with other mods that may edit what happens when butchering the animals that make rugs. Example - My Taxidermy MOD - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1750874483

Works with Save Our Ship 2.

Add/Remove notes: Safe to add. If you remove 1.0 and add 2.0 then load an old save two things will happen. You will loose dyed cloth and two rugs, the simple and frilly rugs. You will get erros on your first load but no more errors when you save and load again. 99% of the DEFs were not changed from 1.0 to 2.0.


Version 1.0 - Released and still up on steam.
Version 2.0 - Revamped and removed dyed cloth and 3D Bear Rugs while adding a few more rugs and pulling some lame ones.
Version 2.1 - Added 2X runners and Prayer Rug
Version 2.2 - Added Play Mat
Version 2.3 - Fixed a couple issues causing log errors, nothing more.
Version 2.4 - Fixed an issue in work speed stats causing log errors.
Version 2.5 - Changed Animal rugs from 4X4 to 3X3 due to users comments.
Version 2.6 - Re-Wrote MOD to use XPATH patching as it still was overwriting animal defs and causing Muffalo issues.

</description>
</ModMetaData>