<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Roo's Satyr Xenotype</name>
	<author>Rooboid, Zelan</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>Rooboid.Satyr</packageId>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VanillaTraitsExpanded</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VAPPE</li>
		<li>Owlchemist.GiddyUp</li>
		<li>Rooboid.Minotaur</li>
		<li>Rooboid.Faun</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</packageId>
			<displayName>Biotech</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1826140/RimWorld__Biotech/?curator_clanid=25160263</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1826140/RimWorld__Biotech/?curator_clanid=25160263</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<description>This mod welcomes the silver-tongued and musical satyr xenotype to the Rim! These flirtatious bards have a penchant for causing mischief, but make up for their uncouth ways with their impressive musical abilities and impressive skill with a bow.

&lt;size=25&gt;• Features&lt;/size&gt;

• 6 new genes and 1 new trait that make up the Satyr xenotype.
• 40+ Satyr backstories to go with various new pawn types.
• 15 new beards.
• 7 unlockable musical abilities.
• 4 musical weapons that passively increase artistic skill.
• And more!

&lt;size=25&gt;• For More…&lt;/size&gt;

If you’re looking for more features, check out Roo’s Satyr and Faun Xenotypes Expanded, which fleshes out the two xenotypes with factions, apparel, hairstyles and more. For more information on mod compatibilities, bugs or plans for the future, please visit my steam workshop page or receive behind-the-scenes updates on my patreon: https://www.patreon.com/Rooboid

&lt;size=25&gt;• Credits&lt;/size&gt;

All credits can be found in the mod's 'About' folder.
A special thanks to my patrons for making this mod possible and keeping me sane:
Britton McGrane, Brandon Pollastri, Eric Celmer, Johnsilker, دانيال أيفان مولار مارتينز, Clement C, Alexandra Milan, John Hamilton, Lau Rosenkilde Birk, Thomas, Shaelyn Rivers-Green, SpaceMarines1, Daedalus, Greg Bunger, D-Train, Dodo, Prince Gerald S and Bardest	</description>
</ModMetaData>