<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
<ScenarioDef>
	
	<defName>CRYST_SCENARIO_DEF</defName>
	<label>&lt;color=#B967FF&gt;&lt;size=16&gt;New Age Of Crystal&lt;/size&gt;&lt;/color&gt;</label>
<description>          &lt;color=#B967FF&gt;A short rumble ago&lt;/color&gt; you -a beautiful, gigantic, gorgeous, and lovely crystal- found yourself nestled safely under a thousand tons of delicious rock, happily munching away on a vein of rare, double yum-yum minerals. Unbeknownst to you "Eh-lee-mans" found their way into your feeding tunnels. 
	
The biggest thief you know is the "Eh-lee-man"; he takes your rock and does *weird* things with it, he takes your minerals and stranges them up too! Today it seems he's even decided to take you! While you were busy brunching those sneaky-soft ehleemans snuck up on you and hit you with something you've never sensed before and you lost yourself in a coal dark blackness for a long rumble.

Next thing you stone you're in a large metal cavern being bathed in an unusally steady fluctuation of electromagnetic radiation. There's a large amount of heat present and a refreshing carbon soot is beginning to stain your upper reaches. Through a thick panel of silicon dioxide set into one side of the steel warren you sense an avalanche of different ehleemans and other assorted soft-lattices.

You sense one of the ehleemans skid to a stop infront of the SiO₂ panel and wack one of their meaty stalactites into the wall opposite before wheeling around and slapping it again against the wall next to your viewing panel. Vibrations rattle and you're flung to the side of the strange cavern as the panicing ehleemans raise out of view and are replaced by a cold void.</description>
	<scenario>
		
		<summary>You are hungry, hungry Crystosentient jettisoned from a burning space ship onto an extremely edible rimworld.</summary>
		<playerFaction>
			<def>PlayerFaction</def>
			<factionDef>CRYST_FACTION_PLAYER_DEF</factionDef>
		</playerFaction>
		<parts>
			<li Class="ScenPart_ConfigPage_ConfigureStartingPawns">
				<def>ConfigPage_ConfigureStartingPawns</def>
				<pawnCount>1</pawnCount>
				<pawnChoiceCount>10</pawnChoiceCount>
			</li>
			<li Class="ScenPart_PlayerPawnsArriveMethod">
				<def>PlayerPawnsArriveMethod</def>
				<method>DropPods</method>
			</li>
			<li Class="ScenPart_StartingThing_Defined">
				<def>StartingThing_Defined</def>
				<thingDef>ChunkSlagSteel</thingDef>
				<count>2</count>
			</li>
			<li Class="ScenPart_StartingThing_Defined">
				<def>StartingThing_Defined</def>
				<thingDef>ChunkSlagSteel</thingDef>
				<count>1</count>
			</li>
			<li Class="ScenPart_ScatterThingsNearPlayerStart">
				<def>ScatterThingsNearPlayerStart</def>
				<thingDef>ChunkSlagSteel</thingDef>
				<count>2</count>
			</li> 
			<li Class="ScenPart_ScatterThingsNearPlayerStart">
				<def>ScatterThingsNearPlayerStart</def>
				<thingDef>ChunkSlagSteel</thingDef>
				<count>1</count>
			</li> 
			<li Class="ScenPart_ScatterThingsNearPlayerStart">
				<def>ScatterThingsNearPlayerStart</def>
				<thingDef>ChunkSlagSteel</thingDef>
				<count>1</count>
			</li> 
			
			<!--<li Class="ScenPart_StartingThing_Defined">
				<def>StartingThing_Defined</def>
				<thingDef>Silver</thingDef>
				<count>40</count>
			</li>
			<li Class="ScenPart_StartingThing_Defined">
				<def>StartingThing_Defined</def>
				<thingDef>Gold</thingDef>
				<count>25</count>
			</li>
			<li Class="ScenPart_StartingThing_Defined">
				<def>StartingThing_Defined</def>
				<thingDef>Uranium</thingDef>
				<count>35</count>
			</li>
			<li Class="ScenPart_StartingThing_Defined">
				<def>StartingThing_Defined</def>
				<thingDef>Steel</thingDef>
				<count>35</count>
			</li>
			<li Class="ScenPart_StartingThing_Defined">
				<def>StartingThing_Defined</def>
				<thingDef>ChunkSlagSteel</thingDef>
				<count>1</count>
			</li>-->
		</parts>
	</scenario>
	
</ScenarioDef>
</Defs>