<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>[KYD] Rebalanced - Apothecary</name>
	<author>Kayedon</author>
	<packageId>KYD.RebalancedApothecary</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
	  <li>1.2</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>Mlie.Apothecary</packageId>
			<displayName>Apothecary (Continued</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2195469123</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/emipa606/Apothecary</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Mlie.Apothecary</li>
		<li>Argon.VMEu</li>
	</loadAfter>	
	<incompatibleWith>
		<li>pelador.apothecary</li>
	</incompatibleWith>
	<description>[KYD] Rebalanced - Apothecary is the first entry into my Rebalanced series, focusing on reducing clutter and tweaking recipes, drugs, meals, buildings, and more in other mods.

Apothecary (Continued) is one of my favourite mods for Neolithic, Tribal, or Medieval playthroughs – I'd even consider it Essential. As such, I wanted to take the time to address my criticisms by creating this add-on to improve my own experience, and hopefully that of others. I removed some content, buffed some things, and nerfed others. I'm very open to feedback so if you think something I did is way off, or think I should make a change I didn't, just let me know.

Pelador's original mod is [b]not[/b] supported. While I'm thankful for his work, much like him it's time to move on.
	
Rebalanced - Apothecary brings the following changes and more to Apothecary (Continued):
* Removes all but one x1 recipe.
* Removes powders and oils - pending final removal, these are no longer craftable.
* All buildings except the Charcoal Crematorium can now be uninstalled/moved.
* Requires lime plaster blocks for lime plaster tiles and art.
* Recategorizes all plants into one category.
* Shows time remaining on all drugs and medicines.
* Reduces optimality of feeding herbs to animals.
* Rebalance many drugs and recipes.

* Vanilla Cooking Expanded: Switches to VCE Salt, look for the recipe on the Condiment Table. All Salt costs in recipes reduced to 1/10th rounded up. (Patch has been provided to Mlie for inclusion in base mod)
* Medical Supplements (Continued): Yarrow Bandages recipe changed from Cloth/Nettle Hemp x10 to Bandages x5.
* Salted Meat: Removes Salted Meat Barrel recipe from Apothecary.</description>
</ModMetaData>