<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Egyptian/Kemetic Factions and Culture</name>
	<author>OdysseyLotus</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>odysseylotus.KemeticAllTogether</packageId>
	<description>Adds a kemetic culture, two industrial/ultratech Egyptian-inspired factions, many custom namers, a starting scenario, and a bunch of patches.
	
That's right, back again with another one. This one took a frankly ridiculous amount of research. I literally edited some Wikipedia pages to add the Anglicization of ancient Egyptian, that's how much research I put into this. Initially, it was just going to be at about the level of my Aztec mod, but then I decided that I wanted a Kemetic playthrough and made a bunch of other stuff.

Culture: Added custom pawn names (972 female names, 1322 male names, and 616 surnames), custom deity names, custom festival names, and custom leader titles. Adds the amazing Roo's HD Dreadlock Hairstyles as the default hair if you have it and Roo's Birthmarks and Blemishes as tattoo options.

Factions: Added two factions that are ultratech level, but use the Outlander pawnKinds and attack groups. I didn't want them to be too overpowered. Based on Upper Egypt (Nekhbet, the vulture goddess) and Lower Egypt (Wadjet, the cobra goddess). Fun fact: upper and lower Egypt were named after the Nile's flow, not the north-south direction, so upper Egypt is actually to the south of lower Egypt. Very confusing, I know.

Scenario: Religious Defection, your group of four are exiled from one of the two major factions. A bit of a mix of the tribal and crashlanded starts, you have industrial level research, but very few resources. And also three camels, why not?

Patches: I tweaked the Kemetic structure from Alpha Memes to include some more gods and other small things (it's in the Embodied Theist section now and I changed the nemes, the Egyptian crown thing, from the top hat to the crown).
There's a patch that removes the Kemetic structure from More Religious Origins (no need to have two, and the Alpha Memes one has more features).
Added the clothes from Kemetic Apparel as ideological styles (they can still be crafted. The robe is the robe, the seto is the top hat, the priest cowl is the broadwrap, and the citizen cowl is the hood).
Added some clothes from Ancient Rim as ideological styles (you can still craft the items, too. The headwrap is the headwrap, and the cap is the tuque).
Added the buildings from Kemetic Decorations to the Kemetic structure designator (I believe that means that they'll only show up if you have the kemetic structure).</description>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>Sarg.AlphaMemes</packageId>
			<displayName>Alpha Memes</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2661356814</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VMemesE</li>
		<li>Sarg.AlphaMemes</li>
		<li>Sovereign.Elseud</li>
		<li>Sovereign.Kemet</li>
		<li>Sovereign.Samsucksfrozenchicken</li>
		<li>kirby.morereligiousorigins</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>