<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>

	<name>Wild Cultivation - Continued</name>
	<author>Jellypowered</author>
	<packageId>jelly.WildCultivation</packageId>
	
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	
	<modDependenciesByVersion>
		<v1.3>
			<li>
				<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
				<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
				<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
				<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			</li>
		</v1.3>
		<v1.4>
			<li>
				<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
				<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
				<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
				<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			</li>
		</v1.4>
	</modDependenciesByVersion>
	<loadAfter>
	<li>ludeon.rimworld.ideology</li>
	<li>VanillaExpanded.VPlantsE</li>
	<li>Owlchemist.SeedsPleaseLite</li>
	<li>Makaru.FertilePlanet</li>
	</loadAfter>

	<description>NOTE: I (Saucy_Pigeon) am not the original author of this mod. The original author is Rainbeau Flambe, who has provided permission for modders to use his mods as the basis of derivative mods on the condition of notifying him.

=====

Blur the lines between wild and cultivated plants! "Wild Cultivation" allows you to cultivate a variety of plants formerly found only in the wild, and adds wild generation of most of the plants that previously could only be cultivated.

Plants which can now be found naturally include corn, haygrass and smokeleaf (most commonly, but not exclusively, found in arid shrubland biomes), daylilies, devilstrand and hops (most easily found in boreal forests), psychoid plants (least uncommon in deserts), cotton, potatoes and roses (most readily discovered in temperate forests), and rice (most easily obtained from tropical rainforests and swamps). 

The ability to find these plants in the wild provides a few extra resource options in the early game, and also allows those using the "Seeds Please!" mod a chance to obtain seeds for plants they might otherwise not be able to grow.

"Wild Cultivation" also allows you to cultivate pincushion cacti, agave, astragalus, clivia, brambles, bushes, low shrubs and grass, all of which could formerly only be found in the wild, as well as glowstools, agarilux mushrooms and bryolux, which otherwise can only be found naturally within caves.

You can also now create growing zones on any terrain that's not completely infertile. This doesn't allow you to grow plants on ground that's not fertile enough to support them, of course. The change is primarily intended to allow you to create growing zones on sand for cacti.

The mod also adds a very small chance of finding wild healroot in tropical rainforests and swamps, where otherwise it doesn't exist.

Finally, "Wild Cultivation" adds one new type of flower, the geranium. Geraniums are functionally identical to daylilies, and in fact the geranium graphic is simply a recolored version of the daylily graphic. I just wanted a purple flower in the game, to add a bit more variety to garden colors.

- Rainbeau Flambe (dburgdorf)

=====

Cultivated Plant Notes:

Agave grows more slowly and has a lower yield than in vanilla, to prevent it becoming a "superplant" when cultivated. It also takes a bit more work to sow and to harvest than most other plants.

Glowstools, agarilux mushrooms and bryolux will all die if exposed to light, so be sure to grow them in enclosed spaces. Cultivated fungi mature faster than their natural counterparts. Additionally, agarilux mushrooms, due to their large size, require extra space, just as do trees.

Cultivated brambles are denser than natural brambles, and thus slow movement more, nearly as much as does chokevine.

=====

Compatibility:

You should be able to add "Wild Cultivation" to an existing saved game without trouble, but removing it from a game in progress will almost certainly cause problems.

"Wild Cultivation" changes a few vanilla plant definitions, but mostly just adds new definitions. So while it might conflict with other mods that alter vanilla plants, it also might not. And generally speaking, any such conflicts which do arise probably won't even be noticeable. For the record, it should be fully compatible with "Vegetable Garden."

If you're using "Vegetable Garden," "[T] Expanded Cloth," or another mod that alters the harvest of cotton, "Wild Cultivation" will automatically adjust the harvest of wild cotton to match it.

"Wild Cultivation" is fully compatible with "Seeds Please!" If you have that mod installed, the wild versions of various plants will drop seeds which can be used to grow their cultivated counterparts.

=====

Credits:

Rainbeau Flambe, the original author.

The mod utilizes Pardeike's "Harmony Patch Library." (For 1.0, no additional download is required, as the library is included with the mod. For 1.1/1.2, please load the external mod before "Wild Cultivation".)

Notfood and boundir, for updating compatibility for SeedsPlease.

Saucy_Pigeon for updating to 1.2

=====

License:

If you're a modpack maker and want to include "Wild Cultivation" in your pack, or if you're a modder and want to use "Wild Cultivation" as the basis of a derivative mod, please feel free to do so. I ask only that you let me, Rainbeau Flambe, know about it. 

=====

If you have any (helpful) suggestions for improvement, please let me know!

	</description>

</ModMetaData>
