<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Kilhn Race Continued</name>
  <author>Commander Storm</author>
  <packageId>CommanderStorm.KilhnRaceContinued</packageId>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <description>This mod about a Dragon / Draconic/ Dragoniod - like race and includes a new unique winged race and faction. 
  
  REQUIRES ALIEN FRAMEWORK to be loaded BEFORE / ABOVE this mod. 

  DISCLAMIER This mod has not been tested with the Anomaly DLC as i do not own it.
  I will do my best to fix bugs with it.
  
  This race, known as the Kilhn, has quite a few advantages, but also some downsides.  
  
  Perks of the Kilhn:
 - 2 x health!
 - Innate armor 20% blunt, 50% sharp, and 75% heat.
 - Natural fighters, strong melee capabilities.
 - They live a long time, around 1500 years.
 - Fire resistant so a little heat isn't bad but extreme temperatures are still deadly.
 - Adept at surviving cold weather by shutting down most bodily functions. 
 - Dragon Rage when injured and bleeding, giving them an edge in survival.
 - Hunting Stealth doubled, meaing less likely to cause animal revenge when hunting.
 - Research 12% faster, as many sources of lore state dragons are vastly intellegent.
 - They tend wounds 20% better than most other races!
 - Innately 10% more resistant to toxins.
 - 10% more meat when butchering!
 - Eat about 10% less often and can eat more food before becoming full.
 - Don't care about nudity, sleeping outside, sleeping on the floor, corpses, eating raw meat, or butchering anything, however...

 Disadvantages of the Kilhn:
 - Carnivore animal diet, meaning only Meals, Kibble, Meat, and Corpses.
 - They move SLOWER than most humanoids.
 - They take 20% LONGER on any tasks with plants.
 - 20% SLOWER when mining!
 - 20% LONGER construction times.
 - They gather 20% LESS from animals, like wool or milk.
 - Anything less than 20 Celsius or 68 Fahrenheit is considered cold.
 - Animals are more likely to attack them when taming from the wild if they fail.
 - Social fights can be dangerous or even deadly.
 - Will always start with The Dragon trait, meaning they can have less individuality.
 - About 20% of the time will start with the trait Greedy.
 - Hard to kill when attacking.
 - Also very hard to recruit as they are proud creatures.
 

 - A special Dragon trait that gives the Kilhn another advantage over other races at a cost, it can be found on other races, but VERY RARE. The Dragon trait has 4 tiers, each less likely to be had than the last.  The effects for tier 1:
 - Immunity gain + 0.5%
 - Melee Skill + 1
 - Melee Dodge + 2
   As Dragons tend to be lazy it also adds the following negatives:
 - more likely to start social fights
 - rest rate - 10% so they sleep longer
 - global work speed - 5% meaning they will always work slower
 
 
  Kilhn cannot gain the traits:
 - Ascetic
 - Jealous
 - Cannibal
 - Nimble
 
 The Kilhn do have a few different body parts:
 - Paws / Talons vs Hands / Fingers / Feet / Toes
 - Snout vs Nose / Jaw
 - Wings added
 - Horns added
 - Tails added
 

 
 Each tier adds more to the positives and negatives while also adding something more... but again it's rare to see tiers 2 tier 3 is extremely rare, and tier 4 is almost non-existant.  

 - This mod should be compatible with most mods as I only added things and didn't touch any base code, starting fresh would be best as with most mods.   


* Changes for 1.0.1 *
 - Changed diet/hunger ratio as it was working in unintended ways. 
 - Altered several %'s to make up for dietary restriction loss. Reflected above.
 - Added the ability to sleep outside/on ground.
 - Fixed a few spelling errors.
 - Cleaned up some code and spent several hours realizing how little I know about programming.
 
 * Changes for 1.0.2 *
 - Reworked Art a little.  Tried adjusting face coloring. 
 - Edited Side Wing graphic.  

 * Changes for 1.0.3 *
 - Added replacement parts for Tails


 I would like to state my thanks for everyone who supports Rimworld, both Tynan Sylvester and all the modders out there.  Seriously this is a great community and this game is one of the best I have ever had the pleasure to experience, both the original work and of course modded!



 This mod was cobbled together by myself and what little art has been a combined effort of my spouse and I. 
 
 
 
 Kilhn v2.0 for 1.1 changelog:
 1. New and changed graphics. Includes:
 - Gendered heads.
 - "Hair" styles with spikes, frills and crests.
 - Wings disappear individually when lost.
 - Visible tails... well, unless lost.
 - Red blood and meat.
 
 2. More uniform bodyparts code allowing for more bodyparts mod interaction.
 - Includes compatibility patch for Evolved Organs.
 
 3. Changes to functionality.
 - Tail is now a blunt weapon and negatively affects movement when damaged/lost.
 - - Craftable bionic tail now comes with "improved balancing" which is a fancy fluff way to justify it boosting movement speed.
 - - Bionic tail now comes with retractable spikes for more melee damage. With "Evolved Organs" can be installed on other humanoids and humans.
 - - Archotech tail with even better mobility and sharper spikes + poison damage. Only craftable with "Archotech Expanded" mod, else you need to buy it or get it from quests. With "Evolved Organs" can be installed on other humanoids.
 - - - Won't give non-Kilhn a visible tail tho.
 - Wings now are related to beauty.
 - - Bionic wings boost mobility tho.
 - Bionic and Archotech Kilhn arms, also bionic Kilhn hand. All come with claws and can be installed on any humanoids.
 - Kilhn are no longer bothered by fresh humanoid corpses.

 Updated and reworked by ChaosKnight.
 Now Maintained by Commander Storm
 
  </description>
  
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
      <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races 2.0</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadBefore>
  </loadBefore>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
  </loadAfter>
  
</ModMetaData>