<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <packageId>Dra.YayoCombatWarcaskets</packageId>
  <name>Yayo's Combat Warcaskets</name>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <author>Sokyran, Hush</author>
  <description>
Do you like my mods? You can support me on Ko-Fi: https://ko-fi.com/sokyran

This mod applies several patches for (mostly) Yayo's Combat to make other mods work with it properly. Patches and features include:

- Warcaskets from Vanilla Factions Expanded - Pirates. No more are the days of paper armor caskets!
- Shields from Vanilla Expanded Framework, used by many mods. They now actually do something when used!
- Bulletproof power from Vanilla Factions Expanded - Ancients. It'll properly change the injury type now.
- Biotic Warp from Rim-Effect: Asari and Reapers. It's going to reduce armor as intended while active.
- Option to modify how strong or weak the Warcaskets are going to be to tailor your experience.
- Option to make Warcaskets more or less common during raids. Also work without Yayo's Combat.
- (1.4+ only) Fixes error spam from Yayo's Combat while androids from Vanilla Races Expanded - Android are clearing their memory.
- (1.3 only) A couple of abilities from Rim-Effect mods that didn't apply their correct effect: Tactical Cloak, Adrenaline Rush, Combat Mastery, Biotic Pull, Biotic Stasis, Biotic Warp, Biotic Charm, and Dark Channel. Also work without Yayo's Combat.
  </description>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>com.yayo.combat3</li>
    <li>Mlie.YayosCombat3</li>
    <li>oskarpotocki.vfe.pirates</li>
    <li>vanillaexpanded.vfea</li>
    <li>vanillaracesexpanded.android</li>
    <li>RimEffect.Core</li>
    <li>RimEffect.AsariReapers</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>