<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<packageId>Shard.PsycastRange</packageId>
	<name>Psycast Sensitivity-based Ranges</name>
	<author>Shard</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>

	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</packageId>
			<displayName>RimWorld - Royalty</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1149640/RimWorld__Royalty/</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2009463077</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li> 
	</modDependencies>

	<description>Psycast ranges scale with psychic sensitivity.  Initial code by Stomir in their mod "Psycast range scales with psychic sensitivity" for the initial targeting range and drawn circle increase.  Code added to patch AOE and secondary target.  Incompatible with Stomir's original mod.

Now your high sensitivity pawns can become incredibly powerful psycasters, while those with reduced sensitivity can barely do anything.

Skipped increasing area of effect:
  Skipshield (Difficult to do, and on further thought, it would negate the purpose)
  Chunkskip (Unlikely to be useful if chunks end up massively spread out)
  Wallraise (Didn't seem very useful, plus annoying to edit)
  Flashstorm (Expanding the radius made it even more unlikely to hit anything useful)

As a bonus, pawns have a small check after being teleported, and if they are both yours and ended up in a unseen location, they make it visible.  Now if you have a mod that makes it possible to teleport through obstacles, you can teleport into places and actually see where you end up.

Note: If you use mods that increase your psychic sensitivity, it is possible to exceed the draw limit as it relies on a set maximum size, and I did not want to consume too much memory -- this mod already uses 10x the original value.  Additionally, modded psycasts may not be supported, I have tried to exclude the ones I know from the drawn radius increase since their actual radius is the same, but I have probably missed several.

I do not intend to update this much, but anyone who wants is free to take the code and make their own better version, I am certain it is possible to do the same thing much better.</description>
    <incompatibleWith>
      <li>Stomir.SensitivePsycastRange</li>
    </incompatibleWith>
    <loadAfter>
      <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
      <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>