<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>[Eng-SZ]English Pack for SZ Series Chinese Traditional Cultural Things Expanded</name>
	<author>Diamond.J,DaJian(has exited)</author>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
    </supportedVersions>
	<packageId>ChiExpanded.English</packageId>
<description>&lt;color=#33ff00&gt;[Note]&lt;/color&gt;
&lt;color=#33ff00&gt;[Note]&lt;/color&gt;
&lt;color=#33ff00&gt;Because the review of the old version with merchants has been stuck, the content of the workshop has been hidden, please go to the workshop to search and subscribe: [Comprehensive update] with merchants— Shenzhou Culture expands to get the latest Shenzhou version update, and there are follow-up update instructions, I will remind everyone in the announcement. (It is expected that the comprehensive version of the mod containing Shang Tsui will be used as a comprehensive version of furniture, animals and other modules after modularization, and the old containing Shang Tsui will be used as a pure frame) &lt;/color&gt;
This is the English translation part of the Shenzhou series, the following is a detailed introduction:

(1) External translation mod (need this module):

(I) (Miscellaneous and Alternative Technologies)
Separation of Different Cuan-Miscellaneous Technology Expansion

Link: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2477792890

Some miscellaneous black technologies, such as human flesh processors, cars, sculptures, etc., are integrated into one section, and some useful and interesting technologies are added. For details, please click on the link to view.

(II)(Comprehensive expansion of Chinese style in China and the main part)
Including Shangzui Levy—Expansion of Chinese Culture

Link: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2371079000

On the basis of ensuring the balance of the original version, this mod adds a lot of Chinese-style objects, animals, plants, and corresponding technologies, as well as unique food and furniture, whether you are a medieval player. You are still a colony manager pursuing high-tech, you can use this mod well. Belongs to a large comprehensive Mod

(2) Mod with built-in English translation

(I)(Shenzhou Music Package) Finale Song-Shenzhou Music Package
Link: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2589811788
This Mod has expanded the Chinese style music, adding traditional music played by various traditional Chinese instruments, as well as some pure tones of ancient music

(II)
! ! ! Translation is in production, not fully translated
! ! ! Translation is in production, not fully translated
(Shenzhou Chinese style faction equipment and cultural dlc expansion, highly recommended)
Refining the soul of the country-traditional faction and cultural dlc expansion
(!!! Translation is in production, not fully translated)
Link: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2597175850

This part expands the cultural DLC, factions and equipment content, and also adds some classical music. The cultural part adds the origin of Chinese culture, symbols of Chinese culture and settlement naming, leader naming, religious naming, and character naming mechanism (both Is a Chinese name), and introduced a set of commandments system related to Shenzhou culture. Three factions have been added to the factions. They are all factions with Shenzhou culture, and each faction has its own era style equipment system. In addition, There are also unique caravans and character backgrounds and character types. It also adds its own technology for forging national soul equipment. It is a very easy-to-use mod that enhances the sense of substitution. Music, there is basically no sense of violation, suitable for any player, compatible with all mods.

(III)
! ! ! Translation is in production, not fully translated
! ! ! Translation is in production, not fully translated
(Shenzhou Chinese style background story)
Moving business moulting-additional narrator and background story expansion

Link: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2430092725

The extended content part adds some background stories, (Background stories such as Dali Temple Qing, Luan Yishi, Hanlin Bachelor, etc.) and the characteristics attached to the background story (in this mod, such as Miaoshou Rejuvenation, Swiftness and Wind, etc.), You can choose according to your preferences.
</description>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Dajian.ChiTeaditional.Expanded</li>
		<li>ChiTeaditional.ExtraPack</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<url>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2371079000</url>

	<modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>Dajian.ChiTeaditional.Expanded</packageId>
      <displayName>Chinese Traditional Cultural Things Expanded 中国风扩展</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2371079000</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
</modDependencies>    
</ModMetaData>