<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Researchable Stat Upgrades Rewritten</name>
  <author>Spdskatr,firefoxpdm,Mlie,kd8lvt</author>
  <url>https://github.com/kd8lvt/researchablestatupgrades</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>firefoxpdm.ResearchableStatUpgrades</packageId>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
        <packageId>imranfish.xmlextensions</packageId>
	      <displayName>XML Extensions</displayName>
	      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/15adhami/XmlExtensions/releases</downloadUrl>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2574315206</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>imranfish.xmlextensions</li>
    <li>kikohi.BetterGroundPenetratingScanner</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>
Reupload of [SS Researchable Stat Upgrades] for 1.4-1.5 by yours truly, kd8lvt.

I'll be maintaining this where I can for as long as I can - AKA as long as I stay interested in RimWorld modding.

This replaces Mlie's old Steam Reupload - please unsubscribe from it, to prevent errors: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2034010625

--- Mlie's Description ---

Steam-upload of firefoxpdms mod for RimWorld 1.2.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/Qo3mAvS.png[/img]

GitHub repository: https://github.com/firefoxpdm/Researchable-Stat-Upgrades

Replaces the old steam-version:
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=936594912

Discord-channel: https://discord.gg/SuhwVpM	

--- firefoxpdms Description ---
This mod is pretty much the same as Spdskatr's original, it has only been updated for 1.1.

The changes that were made:

Mean time between ore detection of the long range scanner in 1.1 is 4 days, guaranteed ore detection time (this seems to be new) is 8 days. With the Scanner efficiency research, these values are reduced to 2 and 4 days. The range increase was not implemented as that particular variable has been removed from the object and I didn't feel like digging through the code to find where it went.
The ground scanner's behaviour has been changed, it no longer displays all undergound veins, but instead detects them one by one, same as with the long range scanner. It also had the 4 and 8 days default values. The scanner efficiency research also reduces these numbers to 2 and 4.
I have also removed the russian language resources, as the scanner efficiency description has changed and I don't speak russian to be able to update it. It felt safer this way.

Everything else should work the same as with the original mod.

--- Original Description ---
Adds stat upgrades that can be researched.

====STATS SHOWCASE====
TIERED
Mining: Improves mining speed. Included Pneumatic Picks research back from Alpha 12 for nostalgia.
Growing: Improves harvest speed and harvest success chance.
Building: Improves construction speed and construct success chance.
Animals: Improves animal gather speed and animal gather chance.
Productivity: Improves move speed and global work speed. Also a repeatable research at the end of the tree
v.1.0
Combat: (courtesy of Swenzi) Improves various stats in combat. (Daniel_USA you were just a bit too late :P)
Medical research: (Courtesy of KingSihv) Improves medical operation speed, quality and success chance.

SINGLE
Nutrient Resynthesis: Nutrient paste dispenser uses 33% less resources. 1000 research points. Also back from Alpha 12
Gun turret cooldown: Gun turrets fire shots in bursts of 4 instead of 3. Also back from Alpha 12
v.1.0
Nutrient flavoring: (name from rageage001) reduces mood debuff of eating mutrient paste meal from -4 to -2.
Psychology: (Courtesy of KingSihv) Prisoner recruit chance increased by 15%
v.2.0
Scanner Efficiency: (Courtesy of KingSihv) long-range mineral scanner takes 50% less time to detect new resource but can appear over wider area
Meat Cut Charts: (Courtesy of KingSihv) more meat yield per animal

FAQ
Does this require a new save/colony/world/game/map/thing/stuff/computer/universe to use? No
Can I suggest something? You see the empty spaces in the research tree? Fill them. (Yes)
I've found a bug, what do I do? Tell me how you got to the bug, post a screenshot, and backup your save file because I might ask for it
Do you have the stats in detail? Get the mod, you don't need to do anything, just enter the research screen. If I put it here it might not be up-to-date
My items keep truncating, and it's really annoying what do I do? Right now the solution is to put Researchable Stat Upgrades higher up in the modlist (Thanks Hinanawi-sama). If that doesnt work join in the bug discussions!

Just a few tips on how to make ideas:
1. Does this really work as a research? Maybe your idea is better to be a special item or a special building, instead of a stat upgrade.
2. Think up of an ideal cost/tech level of your research
3. Think up of a nice name!
4. Where would it go in the research tree?
5. That tree is getting rather full, which means short but sweet researches probably have a higher chance of getting in!


GitHub repo: https://github.com/spdskatr/ResearchableStatUpgrades</description>
</ModMetaData>