<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Monster Mash</name>
	<author>ilikegoodfood</author>
	<supportedVersions><li>1.0</li></supportedVersions>
	<description>
DESCRIPTION:
Version 4: Changed over to use the Verb Expansion Framework as a dependancy instead of the Range Animal Framework.

The RimWorlds contain a broad variety of Earthly and artificial animals, ranging from tiny squirrels to the extinct megasloth (megatherium), from chemically useful boomalopes to rogue bioweapons.
Yet, here in the lawless Rim, far beyond the reach of the shining cities and ethics review boards of the GlitterWorlds, many a mad scientist or budding entrepreneur has attempted to establish themselves as a new giant in the field of genetic manipulation. Regardless of how well their creations were received in the journals back home, the beasts they forged still roam, wild and untamed, in the wildernesses of the RimWorlds.

This mod aims to implement a (hopefully) large number of interesting, dangerous and exotic creatures to the game; some serious, some fanciful.

CURRENTLY IMPLEMENTED:
Carrion Crawler
A huge land snail that roams the arid shrublands in an unending quest for prey. This acid spitting, flesh eating beast is a beautiful native creature of some RimWorld's. It's shell makes for a fine furnishing to any room.

Inferno Beetle
A giant dendrevour (tree eater) that converts timber into chemfuel. Originally developed as a means of industrial espionage in the timbre industry, the creature was abandoned due to its powerful flaming spit.

Land Kraken
A small, soft bodied, and lethal predator. Reasonably easy to kill but extremely dangerous in melee combat, the land kraken is armed with eight bladed tentacles and a poisonous bite. Keep your distance... or else.

Polar Colossus
An immense bear-like cyborg, the result of illegal experimentation with Mechanoid technologies. This monstrous beast is armed with an integrated power-core and thermal lance assembly. This assembly can be sergically extracted and transfered to human colonists, providing significant bonuses.

Sanguine Drake
A large predatory lizard developed for military operations on arid and desert-like worlds. Tough to kill, ride-able (with Giddy-Up!), capable of transporting goods and a fierce fighter, they far surpass camels or horses. In addition to their formidable capabilities, they are able to fire blood from the capillaries around their eyes at ballistic speeds, inflicting a powerful anti-coagulant venom, both from the blood-spray and their bite.

OTHER FEATURES:
Full prosthetics suite for the Land Kraken while A Dog Said... is installed.
Monster Sighting (Event) - A random event that spawns a small number on Monsters on your colony map, regardless of normal biome-locking. They'll hang around for a few days and then leave again.
Thermal Core (Legacy) - A self-contained power supply and heat source that functions as the power core and heart of the cybernetic creature known as the Polar Colossus.
Thermal Lance Assembly - The thermal Lance Assembly is a set of three archo-tech equivelent prosthetic parts that can occasionally be purchased from tarders, or harvested sergically form the Polar Colossus. All three provide significant bonuses in their own right, and when all are installed on a paw. the pawn gains full use of the Thermal Lance Assembly, granting them a ranged attack option (scales according to body size). The parts are:
Thermal Core: Comfotable Temperature Min - 40, Max -10 (results on a human is a comfortable temperature range of -24 to +16)
Optical Firing Assembly: +2 Accuracy and Aiming Time reduced by 10%.
Thermal Lance Firing Assembly: Provides a powerful bite attack that does both bite and burn damage.

IN PROGRESS:
New creatures coming soon.

INSTALLATION AND COMPATIBILITY:
This mod automatically detects and adjusts for the presence of the following other mods:
A Dog Said...
Giddy Up

Monster Mash should be loaded after all of the mods that it depends on. So, if you have A Dog Said... installed, the load order for those mods should be Core, Verb Expansion Framework, A Dog Said..., Monster Mash.
It should be safe to add this mod to existing save files, but as always, back-up the save beforehand.
It should also be safe to remove from active saves, so long as no animal, projectile or animal product that is added by this mod are on the map at the time of removal.

This mod is intended to work alongside such great mods as the Animal Collab Project and the Megafauna mod. Similarity in creatures should be minimal.

BUGS AND LOCALIZATIONS:
Please report any bugs that you find, so that I may try and solve them. When reporting a bug, please provide the error log and mod list.
I only speak English, so I cannot make localizations for other languages. If you know how and speak those languages, please feel free to create localizations and I can incorporate them into the core mod (Credits will be given).

CREDITS:
A Dog Said... Animal Surgery, created and maintained by spoonshortage. A mod that provides Animal Prosthetics and operations systems. Some A Dog Said... definitions are used in my mod for compatibility purposes.
Megafauna, created and maintained by Spino. A fantastic animal addition mod that acted both as the inspiration for my mod and an excellent template from which to learn.
Verb Expansion Framework, created by myself. A brand new framework designed to facilitate the various new features that I wish to implement in this mod.

LICENSE:
If you're a modpack maker and want to include Monster Mash or if you are a modder and want to use it as the basis of a derivative or similar mod, please feel free to do so. I only ask that you let me know about it and credit me where appropriate.
	</description>
</ModMetaData>