<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>CorpseTab</name>
  <author>tikubonn</author>
  <packageId>tikubonn.CorpseTab</packageId>
  <url>https://twitter.com/tikubonn</url>
  <description><![CDATA[<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Overview</color></size>

Do you have any experience with that scavenge corpses killed by carnivorous when starting game? This MOD provide new useful tab to you. This MOD add a new tab window that list-up all corpses in the map. You could check corpse is rotten or not, and look its location, change corpse permission to allow or deny by its tab. This MOD is compatible with AllowTool, and if you have installed the corresponding MOD, you will be able to issue Haul urgently instructions from the tab.

ゲーム開始時に、肉食動物に殺された死骸を漁った経験はありませんか？このMODはそんなあなたに便利なタブを提供します。このMODはマップ内の死骸をリストアップするタブを追加します。追加されたタブを通じて、腐敗の有無や死骸の場所の確認、許可・禁止の指定をすることができます。本MODはAllowToolに対応しており、該当MODが導入済みであれば、タブから緊急運搬(Haul urgently)の指示を出すことができるようになります。

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Mod Compatible</color></size>

* AllowTool(https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=761421485)

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Bug Report</color></size>

Bug reports other than bugs that can be reproduced with this MOD alone will not be accepted. We do not intend to resolve issues that occur when playing the game using other MODs, so please resolve them by changing the load order or uninstalling this MOD yourself. Additionally, if you are reporting a bug that can only be reproduced with this mod, please be sure to provide the following information.

* What happened?
* When and under what circumstances did it happen?
* How can I replicate the issue?
* What's your RimWorld version?
* Post an error log! (If you have HugsLib -> Ctrl+F12 and paste the link in the comments!)

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>FAQ</color></size>

Q) Is the mod compatible with...?
A) We do not accept questions regarding compatibility with other MODs. If you can't resolve it yourself, please contact the mod's author.

Q) I want to report a bug!
A) Guidelines for reporting bugs can be found in `Bug Report`.

Q) Please add the features I came up with!
A) This MOD was originally written for my own use, so I generally do not accept requests. I feel more motivated and happy when I receive positive feedback rather than requests.

Q) Your translation is terrible!
A) If you think my translation is terrible, you can send the correct translation to me. If you sent the correct translation, I replace it and old translation after checked.

Q) May I upload a game video taken with this mod installed?
A) No problem of course. I give permission for you to upload videos taken with this mod installed and for you to monetize those videos. I also give you permission to use thumbnail images of this mod in your videos to showcase this mod.

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Translation</color></size>

English (tikubonn with Google Translation)
Japanese (tikubonn)

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Copyright</color></size>

© 2021 tikubonn

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>License</color></size>

Redistributing my MOD is prohibited.
These Terms of Use supersede CC BY-NC-ND 4.0.

CorpseTab © 2021 by tikubonn is licensed under Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivatives 4.0 International. To view a copy of this license, visit http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/4.0/

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Update History</color></size>

<color=#7f7f7f>2023-11-29:</color>
RimWorld 1.4に対応しました。それにともないRimWorld 1.3向けの更新を終了します。MODの設計を見直し、RimWorldが提供する機能を利用してテーブルを作成するようにしました、過去のコードは破棄され、すべて新しいものに置き換わりました。それにより、前バージョンよりもより高速に快適に動作するようになりました。本MODのライセンスを CC BY-NC-ND 4.0 に設定し、それに合わせてMOD説明欄の文章を新しいものに変更いたしました。本体のみの機能でAllowToolに対応しました。AllowTool導入済みであれば、テーブル作成時に専用の列が追加されるようになります。それにともない CorpseTab for AllowTool の更新を停止します。
Compatible with RimWorld 1.4. Accordingly, updates for RimWorld 1.3 will be terminated. We have redesigned the mod to create tables using the functionality provided by RimWorld, and all previous code has been discarded and replaced with new ones. As a result, it now runs faster and more comfortably than the previous version. The license of this MOD has been set to CC BY-NC-ND 4.0, and the text in the MOD description has been changed accordingly. AllowTool is now supported as a function only for the main unit. If AllowTool has been installed, a dedicated column will be added when creating a table. Accordingly, we will stop updating CorpseTab for AllowTool.

<color=#7f7f7f>2022-3-16:</color>
描画速度を向上させるためにDLLのコードを最適化しました。十分高速化することができたことと、作業につかれたのでこれ以降の最適化は行いません。メンテナンスを容易にするためDLLのコードを整理しました。
Optimized code to draw faster than previous version. I'll never more optimize this MOD since this version, because I'm tired. Refactoring code to more maintain easily.

<color=#7f7f7f>2021-9-13:</color>
タブに死骸が腐敗するまでの期間を表示するようにしました。タブに死骸の冷蔵状況を表示するようにしました。タブの死後日数の表示形式をよりわかりやすいものに変更しました。
Added a new column that show the time of until rot to tab. Added a new column that show the refrigerate state to tab. Changed label format to more understandable in day of death column.
]]></description>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies></modDependencies>
  <loadBefore></loadBefore>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>UnlimitedHugs.AllowTool</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <incompatibleWith></incompatibleWith>
</ModMetaData>
