<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Alien Vs Predator</name>
	<author>Ogliss</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>Ogliss.AlienVsPredator</packageId>
	<description>V1.5.0.10
	
	Requirments
	Humanoid Alien Races
	
	"All right, sweethearts, what are you waiting for? Breakfast in bed? It's another glorious day in the Corps. A day in the Marine Corps is like a day on the farm: Every meal's a banquet. Every paycheck's a fortune! Every formation's a parade! I love the Corps!" - Sgt. Apone
	Thats right, the USCM have arrived on the Rim!
	
	Apparel:
	USCM Bandana
	USCM Military Cap
	USCM Fatigues
	USCM Medical jumpsuit
	USCM Engineer jumpsuit
	
	Armour:
	M10 Ballistic Helmet
	M3 Personal Armor
	M56 Combat Harness - (Smart Gun System Component)
	
	Equipment:
	Head Mounted Sight - (Smart Gun System Component)
	Weapons:
	M4A3 Service Pistol
	M4A4 Pistol
	88 Mod 4 Combat Pistol
	M41A Pulse rifle - (Underslung Grenade Launcher)
	M41B Pulse rifle - (Underslung Shotgun)
	M56 Smartgun - (Smart Gun System Component)
	M240 Incinerator Unit
	M2402 Heavy incinerator
	M39 Submachine gun
	M37A2 Pump Shotgun
	M42A Sniper Rifle
	M5 Rocket Propelled Grenade
	
	Turrets:
	UA 571-C automated sentry gun
	
	Misc:

	Synth race:
	
	"El Diablo, cazador de hombre. Only in the hottest years this happens. And this year it grows hot."
	The Yautja are one of the fiercest hunters in the known galaxy. Smart, cunning, strong and endurable, their thirst for Glorious hunting can never be sated.
	Play as the fearless race. Develop new technologies. Weapons with unique abilities. Equipment usable only by the Hunters. Hunt targets, mark yourself for Honour. 
	Play as human and pray that the Yautja do not take interest in your colony.

	Yautja(Predator) Race from the Predator film franchise to the game as a playable race.

	Pawns:
	Yautja Race (Male &amp; Female)
	
	Mechanics:
	Blooding and Marking: the Yautja value physical prowess above all else, the stronger the creature they kill, the higher their social status is.
	
	Apparel:
	Yautja Thermal Webbing
	Yautja Bio Mask (Standard, Elite, Ornate Variants)
	Yautja Hunter Armour (Standard, Light, Heavy, Elite, Ornate Variants)

	Equipment:
	Yautja Gauntlets: Thes contain the Self Destruct Device, they also gives the wearer a Wristblade melee attack (Thanks to LoonyLadle's Hediff Apparel Resource)
	and can also be upgraded with a Medicomp to treat the wearers wounds in the field, a Shard injector to quickly bring the wearer back to combat readiness, and a cloaking device.
	
	Yautja Shoulder Cannon: This item gives the wearer an automated ranged attack when active (Based on Rikki's Mining Helmet)

	Weapons: Melee
	Yautja Combistaff: can be thrown to pin enemies in place
	Bladed Maul: Simple melee weapon

	Weapons: Ranged
	Yautja Smart Disk - Research allows this to hit multiple targets while wearing a Bio Mask
	Yautja Blaster
	Yautja Needler
	Yautja Speargun - Sniper rifle equivalent
	
	incidents:
	Man in Black: using the yautja starts, enables Yautji Man in Black replacer.(it will also work for other races, if they have a pawnkind with StrangerinBlack in its name)
	El Diablo: Yautja raids during Heatwaves are larger than normal.


	“Perfect organism. Its structural perfection is matched only by its hostility.”
	The Xenomorphs join the RimWorld as a new threat to your colony. Experience the full life cycle of the Xenomorphs. Learn to fear their infestations. Be wary of those spaceship parts that fall down, you never know what they may contain.

	Xenomorph race from the Alien film franchise to the game as an enemy race.
	Full Xenomorph life cycle, facehuggers can impregnate pawns, the resulting xenomorph is mostly random, however if the host is a yautja then it will always result in a predalien.
	
	Pawns:
	Queen, Drone(Spitter), Warrior, Runner, Facehugger. Chestburster, Predalien, Thrumbomorph, Neomorph
	
	Mechanics:
	Acidic Blood: Xenomorph Blood is Highly Acidic and will damage everything in the same tile as it for a short period after being dropped by a LIVING xenomorph
	Hidden Infections: Can be disabled Via Mod Options, if enabled, there is a small chance any pawn spawned will have a hidden impregnation.
	
	incidents:
	They Mostly Come at Night: Xenomorph raids during the night are larger than normal
	Neomorph Spores:  Hint; Flamers maybe required
	Crashed Ship part:  Hint; Bring a strong squad
	Xenomorph Infestation:  Hint; Don’t wait too long
	
	Credits 
	Authors and their credits:
	Ogliss: Coding, XML, mechanics
	Rebelrot: Yautja concepts and textures
	acide_bob: XML &amp; balancing
	Temmy: Texturs, concepts &amp; balancing
	Cortanakya: textures &amp; balancing
	SerpyDerpy: textures
	Makura Gaeshi: Grammatical Corrections Officer

	Arts:
	Rebelrot: Everything except what follow.
	Temmy: Needler, Bladed Maul, combistaff
	Deon: Drone, Warrior, Runner, Queen Xenomorphs.
	Hiztarr: M4A3 Service Pistol, M4A4 Pistol, 88 Mod 4 Combat Pistol M42A Sniper Rifle.
	Cortanakya: UD-4 "Cheyenne" Dropship, Ovomorph Container, Hellhound
	Odz: USCM Combat Armour, USCM Combat Helmet
	SerpyDerpy: Rynath
	[H.M] Hellfire: Yautja Apparel &amp; Body resize
	
	Translators are welcome!

	Special Thanks
	Lore:
	Daiki97427 &amp; SilentLord 

	Erdelf - For the framework and all the help in general
	Jecrell - Those tools are awesome
	UnlimitedHugs - HugsLib is a must around the workshop
	Stan Winston - For creating one of the most badass creature in sci-fy history
	H. R. Giger- For creating The most badass creature in sci-fy history

	also a big Thank you to Jecrell, Erdelf, Menhi, Roolo, Walking Problem, Ministry of MOM and the many others who assisted with the C#

	Thrumbomorph named by ＧｅｎｅｒａｌＴｈｉｃｃＬｏｌｉ
	</description>
    <modDependencies>
      <li>
        <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
        <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
        <downloadUrl>https://github.com/RimWorld-CCL-Reborn/AlienRaces</downloadUrl>
      </li>
    </modDependencies>
	<incompatibleWith>
		<li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
	</incompatibleWith>	
  <loadAfter>
    <li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>