<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Artifacts Expanded</name>
	<author>Carnagion</author>
	<packageId>Carnagion.ArtifactsExpanded</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadBefore/>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<incompatibleWith/>
	<description>It's rare to come across an artifact or powerful item in RimWorld, and even then, there's not much variety, severely limiting strategies and situations when they could be used. 

With that in mind, this mod adds 9 new limited-use items that are relatively balanced, and will (hopefully) fit vanilla playstyles quite well. All of them have custom 128x128 sprites that should look and feel like they are part of the vanilla game.

	FEATURES

Psychic fear lance
- A limited-use utility slot item that makes the target flee in panic. Just like the vanilla psychic lances, its effectiveness depends on the target's psychic sensitivity, and it will not have any effect on targets with 0 psychic sensitivity.

Psychic chaos pulser
- A powerful artifact that will make every pawn (animals, humanlikes, and mechanoids) on the map go berserk. Pawns that belong to the player's faction have a 16% chance to go berserk (as opposed to 100% for all other pawns).

Anti-psychic pulser
- A rare artifiact that reduces the psychic sensitivities of all colonists on the map to 10%. The effect wears off after a few days.

Revitalizer mech serum
- A mech serum that makes pawns instantly younger.

Grower mech serum
- A mech serum that makes pawns grow older instantly. There is a possibility of mild scarring.

Amnesiac mech serum
- Makes the user forget all negative memories (such as a colonist/animal death, insults, "ate without table", etc) instantly. Also provides a small mood buff that lasts a few days.

Archotech neurotrainer
- A very rare and valuable item that grants instant experience to every single skill of the pawn that uses it. The experience gained is affected by passion modifiers, and disabled skills remain unchanged.

Mind suppressor
- A brain implant that passively reduces the resistance of prisoners, and attempts to recruit them as well.

Archotech sacrificer belt
- A powerful yet dangerous artifact that can be worn by colonists. Colonists that wear it will be resurrected immediately upon death, but another colonist (if one exists on the map) will die instead. It can be used indefinitely, but cannot be removed from its wearer after the first resurrection.

Certain features are configurable in the mod settings.

	FAQ

1. I set the commonality of artifacts to maximum, but they're still not common. Why?
A. That setting is not a magic wand that will automatically generate hundreds of artifacts as rewards. RimWorld's reward generation works such that artifacts are part of an overarching category of reward items, so increasing the commonality of artifacts means increasing the commonality of those items as well. Overall though, you should expect to see a somewhat decent increase in artifacts as rewards.

2. Is this mod compatible with:
	- More Archotech Garbage?
	A. Yes. Its author even has a patch to craft the artifacts from this mod; check it out.

	- Any other mod that adds more archotech items, mechanics, etc?
	A. Yes, this mod should not have any compatibility issues.

3. Is it safe to add to an ongoing save?
A. Yes, absolutely. However, it is good practice to make a backup of the save file before adding it, just in case something unexpectedly goes wrong.

4. Is it safe to remove from ongoing saves?
A. Yes, absolutely. Just remove all instances of the items added by this mod before doing so. Also, be sure to make a backup of the save file, just in case something unexpectedly goes wrong.

	CREDITS

Shoutout to the modders on the RimWorld Discord server for giving me good ideas.

Thanks to Brrainz for making Harmony, which is an amazing tool for modders like me.

RimWorld is owned by Tynan Sylvester.
	</description>
</ModMetaData>