<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

    <ThingDef ParentName="ArmorHelmetMakeableBase">
		<defName>US_HackerShades</defName>
		<label>M.A.R.A. medic-class shades</label>
		<description>A pair of circle rim sunglasses that, while they are more unconventional, are still fashionable. These glasses are concealing a secret however, as they are fitted with a M.A.R.A. class (short for Medical Assistant and Research Aid) subpersona AI. The main focus of these glasses is to assist the user in intellectual endeavors. Having access to a local satellite containing a variety of information, the M.A.R.A. AI can assist its wearer with research by pulling up relevant information for the wearer to peruse as needed.

These glasses also have a medical module installed to assist with medical operations. The M.A.R.A. AI can map any creature's anatomy just from a quick scan and then download any relevant medical information into its internal databank. This allows the wearer to both patch up wounds more efficiently and be more precise with any surgeries they perform.

These glasses also have a lesser PLATE class shield generator built in that fully envelops the wearer's head. It acts similarly to standard armor, as while it does not provide perfect protection, it will never break from heat buildup, nor does it get in the way of projectile weaponry. The shield is also invisible, because having a giant bubble around the user's head would be a crime against fashion. Due to the amount of space the research and medical modules take up and combat not being the primary focus for these glasses, the shield generator is significantly less effective than other shielded sunglasses.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<texPath>Apparel/HackerShades/HackerShades</texPath>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
		</graphicData>
		<techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
	        <generateCommonality>0.0</generateCommonality>
	        <costList>
	            <ComponentSpacer>3</ComponentSpacer>
	            <Gold>2</Gold>
	            <Plasteel>75</Plasteel>
	            <Uranium>20</Uranium>
	        </costList>
		<statBases>
			<WorkToMake>25000</WorkToMake>
			<MaxHitPoints>200</MaxHitPoints>
			<Mass>0.5</Mass>
			<Flammability>0.1</Flammability>
           		<ArmorRating_Sharp>0.7</ArmorRating_Sharp>
           		<ArmorRating_Blunt>0.3</ArmorRating_Blunt>
           		<ArmorRating_Heat>0.3</ArmorRating_Heat>
           		<Insulation_Cold>3</Insulation_Cold>
           		<Insulation_Heat>5</Insulation_Heat>
           		<EquipDelay>0.5</EquipDelay>
		</statBases>
		<equippedStatOffsets>
			<ResearchSpeed>0.35</ResearchSpeed>
			<MedicalTendSpeed>0.25</MedicalTendSpeed>
			<MedicalTendQuality>0.3</MedicalTendQuality>
			<MedicalSurgerySuccessChance>0.15</MedicalSurgerySuccessChance>
			<SocialImpact>0.2</SocialImpact>
		</equippedStatOffsets>
		<thingCategories Inherit="False">
			<li>Headgear</li>
		</thingCategories>
		<apparel>
			<bodyPartGroups>
				<li>FullHead</li>
				<li>Eyes</li>
			</bodyPartGroups>
			<wornGraphicPath>Apparel/HackerShades/HackerShades</wornGraphicPath>
			<hatRenderedFrontOfFace>true</hatRenderedFrontOfFace>
			<useDeflectMetalEffect>true</useDeflectMetalEffect>
			<layers>
				<li>Overhead</li>
				<li>EyeCover</li>
			</layers>
			<tags>
				<li>EVA</li>
			</tags>
			<defaultOutfitTags>
				<li>Soldier</li>
            </defaultOutfitTags>
		</apparel>
		<recipeMaker>
			<researchPrerequisite>US_UtilitySunglasses</researchPrerequisite>
			<recipeUsers Inherit="False">
				<li>FabricationBench</li>
			</recipeUsers>
			<skillRequirements>
				<Crafting>8</Crafting>
			</skillRequirements>
			<unfinishedThingDef>UnfinishedTechArmor</unfinishedThingDef>
		</recipeMaker>
	<colorGenerator Class="ColorGenerator_Options">
	      <options>
	        <li>
	          <weight>10</weight>
	          <only>(0.9,0.9,0.9)</only>
	        </li>
	        <li>
	          <weight>10</weight>
	          <only>(1.0,1.0,1.0)</only>
	        </li>
	      </options>
	</colorGenerator>
    </ThingDef>

  </Defs>