<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

 <XenotypeDef>
    <defName>GS_Illithid</defName>
    <label>Illithid</label>
    <description>Illithids are a race of psychically gifted, archotech-enhanced xenohumans. Armed with frightening mental abilities, they seek dominion over all. The scourge of every world they set upon, the illithids prey upon the weak and feebleminded, enthralling them into doing their bidding as mindless slaves. Yet an even worse fate awaits those strong enough to resist them, as upon capture they are infected with illithid tadpoles that rapidly change them into another illithid, adding the host’s unique strengths into their own ranks. Struggling in direct combat, they prefer to hang back, directing their thralls while floating above the battlefield and distributing their foes with their psychic abilities. \n\nNobody knows the precise origin of the illithids. Some say they are a plague engineered by a mad archotech, while others theorize they are a result of human hubris, playing with powers they did not understand. Reviled and feared as a threat to civilization itself, the illithids are relentlessly hunted in the core worlds, making their presence limited mostly to rimworlds, where the lack of centralised planetary government that could put a meaningful resistance lets them grow their thrall empires largely unimpeded.</description>
    <descriptionShort>Illithids are a race of psychically gifted, archotech-enhanced xenohumans.</descriptionShort>
    <iconPath>UI/IllithidXenotype</iconPath>
    <inheritable>false</inheritable>
	

    <genes>
	
			<li>Ageless</li>
			<li>ArchiteMetabolism</li>
			<!--<li>DiseaseFree</li>-->
			<li>GS_Enthrall</li>
			<li>GS_PsyLevel</li>
			<li>PsychicAbility_Extreme</li>
			<li>GS_Levitate</li>
			<li>GS_Uncanny</li>
			<li>MoveSpeed_Slow</li>
			<li>Sterile</li>
			<li>Hair_BaldOnly</li>
			<li>Beard_NoBeardOnly</li>
			<li>GS_Illithid_Head</li>
			<li>GS_IllithidVoice</li>
			<li>Body_Thin</li>
			<li>GS_Skin_Colour_Illithid</li>
			<li>Learning_Fast</li>
			<li>DarkVision</li>
			<li>Hair_Grayless</li>
			<li>GS_Alien_Blood_Silver</li>
			<li>GS_Arrogant_Gene</li>
			
			
			
			
<!--			<li>AptitudeTerrible_Construction</li>
			<li>AptitudeTerrible_Mining</li>
			<li>AptitudeTerrible_Plants</li>
			<li>AptitudeTerrible_Artistic</li>-->
  

    </genes>
	
	
	
  </XenotypeDef>
  
  
  </Defs>