<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<LanguageData>
  <AIU_HoursUntilUncomfortable_title>Hours Until Uncomfortable</AIU_HoursUntilUncomfortable_title>
  <AIU_HoursUntilUncomfortable_desc>The number of hours it takes for a pawn with 1 discomfort to get the maximum mood penalty. Having higher discomfort will speed this up considerably.</AIU_HoursUntilUncomfortable_desc>
  <AIU_HourUntilComfortable_title>Hours Until Comfortable</AIU_HourUntilComfortable_title>
  <AIU_HoursUntilComfortable_desc>The number of hours it takes a totally uncomfortable pawn to completely recover.</AIU_HoursUntilComfortable_desc>
  <AIU_DiscomfortRecoveryMultiplier_title>Discomfort Recovery Multiplier</AIU_DiscomfortRecoveryMultiplier_title>
  <AIU_DiscomfortRecoveryMultiplier_desc>How fast a pawn recovers from being uncomfortable. At 1, it takes 1 hour to recover from 1 hours of wearing uncomfortable clothes at discomfort 1. At 2, it takes 30 minutes from to recover from 1 hour of uncomfortable clothes, at 0.5 it takes 2 hours, etc.</AIU_DiscomfortRecoveryMultiplier_desc>
  <AIU_GlobalDiscomfortMultiplier_title>Global Discomfort Multiplier</AIU_GlobalDiscomfortMultiplier_title>
  <AIU_GlobalDiscomfortMultiplier_desc>A pawn's total discomfort will be multiplied by this amount. Set this low if you feel pawns get uncomfortable too easy, or higher for the opposite effect.</AIU_GlobalDiscomfortMultiplier_desc>
  <AIU_DisableThought_title>Disable Mood Penalty</AIU_DisableThought_title>
  <AIU_DisableThought_desc>Turns off the uncomfortable apparel thought. Use this if you are running into issues.</AIU_DisableThought_desc>
  <AIU_DeceleratingNeed_title>Slowing Discomfort</AIU_DeceleratingNeed_title>
  <AIU_DeceleratingNeed_desc>As a pawn's apparel comfort need falls, the rate of decline slows, meaning it takes longer and longer to reach the most severe mood penalties.</AIU_DeceleratingNeed_desc>
  <AIU_EnvironmentalEffects_title>Environmental Factors</AIU_EnvironmentalEffects_title>
  <AIU_EnvironmentalEffects_desc>When this is on, hot, humid weather accelerates discomfort gain.</AIU_EnvironmentalEffects_desc>
  <AIU_DebugInfo_title>Debug Mode</AIU_DebugInfo_title>
  <AIU_DebugInfo_desc>Prints debug info to the log. Not useful for regular play.</AIU_DebugInfo_desc>
  <AIU_EquipmentWeight_title>Equipment Weight</AIU_EquipmentWeight_title>
  <AIU_EquipmentWeight_desc>If this is turned on, the weight of your equipment (mostly, your equipped weapon) increases the rate at which you get uncomfortable and . Makes the game *much* harder.</AIU_EquipmentWeight_desc>
  <AIU_InsulationDiscomfort_title>Insulation Discomfort</AIU_InsulationDiscomfort_title>
  <AIU_InsulationDiscomfort_desc>If this is turned on, cold insulation contributes to discomfort. Makes the game MUCH harder. Requires a reload to completely take effect.</AIU_InsulationDiscomfort_desc>
  
</LanguageData>

