<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>A RimWorld of Magic - Apotheosis DemiGod Class</name>
	<author>Drakonite</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>Drakonite.Apotheosis</packageId>
	<url></url>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>Kure.AROM</packageId>
			<displayName>Kure's Rimworld of Magic Class Expansion Pack</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2236103336</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</packageId>
			<displayName>HugsLib</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=28066.0</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>jecrell.jecstools</packageId>
			<displayName>JecsTools</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=932008009</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://discord.gg/AaVFA7V</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		  <li>
			<packageId>Torann.ARimworldOfMagic</packageId>
			<displayName>A RimWorld of Magic</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1201382956</steamWorkshopUrl>
		  </li>
    </modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
		<li>jecrell.jecstools</li>
		<li>Torann.ARimworldOfMagic</li>
		<li>Kure.AROM</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<description>
Version 1.2, Version 1.3
Have you ever wanted your pawn to ascend to a higher plane of magic? One without bounds, one with limitless potential? There is a process known by some as Apotheosis where one can achieve divinity.

This knowledge was not meant for mankind, yet it is here to stay. Acquiring the knowledge will give you demi-god-like potential. You are not an immortal by any means, but your potential for magic is boundless.

(Highly recommend Immortals mod for full effect)

------- End Power Monologue here -------

Provides a custom class via A RimWorld of Magic that is a demi-god. The class will have multiple spells and abilities that are present in other RimWorld Magic class mods and the primary package.

Credit to those developers that made the magic. (Torann RimWorld of Magic, Kure's Rimworld of Magic Expansion Pack) This is just a custom class to provide an OP kit for a pawn. This is primarily for my own usage, use at your own risk. I don't want to break my game as much as I don't want to break yours! :)
I'm currently running it without issue. I did notice that the more abilities that were available, the larger performance impact it had. My system normally runs at 100 FPS and this class does not really affect the FPS anymore than any other class in a meaningful way at least for my setup.

There are NO changes anywhere else, this is simply a clean class implementation following Torann's guide. (This will not conflict or modify any existing pawns or magic users, it is 100% isolated)

You can read the changes below on what this provides. You are by no means unkillable or even OP at the start. This simply provides more spells in a kit that you can achieve that are powerful. Over time, you can become unstoppable-- but you don't start that way.

New Class: Demi-God
	Might (Same kit as Psionic class but without barrier, I had some issues finding the spell upgrade values for that one so I just took it out of this class)
	Magic (spells are below)
	Max Magic Level: 500
	Max Might Level: 200

Yes there will be some points leftover, I did not specifically make it so you cap out. Think of it this way, you constantly grow in power lore wise even when you achieved everything.
If anyone wants me to reduce the levels so there is no overage I'm glad to do so. :) For my own purposes, I don't particularly care one way or the other.

Notable Magic Traits:
	40% reduced cooldown on all magic spells and might abilities
	1000% increased mana regen and mana pool (I believe this may also apply to the stamina pool)

Item's added to get this class:
	BookOfApotheosis

Passive Trait increase MULTIPLIERS: (Note: None of these are 'negative', they all buff your pawn)
	PsychicSensitivity: 50
	GlobalLearningFactor: 5
	PainShockThreshold: .20
	MoveSpeed: 1
	MeleeHitChance: 25
	MeleeDodgeChance: 25
	ShootingAccuracyPawn: 100
	WorkSpeedGlobal: 2.5
	SocialImpact: 2
	TradePriceImprovement: 2
	NegotiationAbility: 2
	ResearchSpeed: 10
	ImmunityGainSpeed: 1
	ToxicSensitivity: -1
	MentalBreakThreshold: -0.2

Spells:
	Blink
	Blink_I
	Blink_II
	Blink_III
	*** Spells from Paladin Class ***
	Shield
	Shield_I
	Shield_II
	Shield_III
	Overwhelm
	*** Spells from Starseeker Class RFS -- Kure's AROM Expansion Pack***
	Lightshow
	Dazzle
	Impact
	Decimate
	Obliterate
	OldWivesChant
	LesserWard
	WardAgainstHarm
	GreaterWard
	OmniWard
	LesserLesserFirebolt
	LesserFirebolt
	ConjureFlame
	Perdition
	Cataclysm
	ExpiredSnowball
	ChillyBreeze
	Freeze
	Avalanche
	Whiteout
	StaticShock
	StaticBolt
	ForkedLightning
	LightningRod
	Cloudburst
	Daydream
	StrikeAPose
	ArcaneAwareness
	EtherFlux
	ArchmagesAbsolution
	*** Harbinger RFS Kure's AROM Expansion Pack ***
	InfuriateB
	Infuriate_I
	Infuriate_II
	Infuriate_III
	ShadowFettersB
	ShadowFetters_I
	ShadowFetters_II
	ShadowFetters_III
	RendSoulB
	RendSoul_I
	RendSoul_II
	RendSoul_III
	*** Chronomage spells ***
	AccelerateTime
	ReverseTime
	*** Geomancer Spells ***
	Meteor
	Meteor_I
	Meteor_II
	Meteor_III
	*** Summoner Spells ***
	SummonPylon

Dependencies:
Kure's Rimworld of Magic Class Expansion Pack -- Kure
A Rimworld of Magic -- Torann
		
	</description>
</ModMetaData>