<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>

	<!-- Insect primacy meme -->
	<MemeDef>
		<defName>InsectoidPrimacy</defName>
		<label>insectoid primacy</label>
		<description>Insectoids are the ultimate goal of evolution.</description>
		<iconPath>UI/Memes/PrimacyInsectoid</iconPath>
		<groupDef>Primacy</groupDef>
		<impact>2</impact>
		<renderOrder>50</renderOrder>
		<exclusionTags>
			<li>Primacy</li>
		</exclusionTags>
		<requireOne>
			<li>
				<li>InsectoidSlaughter_Abhorrent</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>KillingInnocentInsectoids_Horrible</li>
				<li>KillingInnocentInsectoids_Abhorrent</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>TamingInsectoids_Abhorred</li>
				<li>TamingInsectoids_Disapproved</li>
				<li>TamingInsectoids_Approved</li>
				<li>TamingInsectoids_Loved</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>InsectMeatEating_Abhorrent</li>
			</li>
		</requireOne>
		<generalRules>
			<rulesStrings>
				<li>memeAdjective->insectean</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->entomean</li>
				<li>memeCreed->nest</li>
				<li>memeCreed->hive</li>
				<li>memeCreed->colony</li>
				<li>memeConcept->insectoids</li>
			</rulesStrings>
		</generalRules>
		<descriptionMaker>
			<rules>
				<rulesStrings>
					<!-- Theist myth -->
					<li>creation(tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->[deity0_name] created nature, and created multitudes of insects, giving them some of the most important roles to fulfill.</li>
					<li>episode(uses=1,tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->The people began killing insects en masse, and seeing their helpnessness, [deity0_name] armed them with larger, stronger bodies, and deadly limbs.</li>

					<!-- Theist founder -->
					<li>intro(tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->The first to arrive at the [place_summery] [place_name] tried to exterminate an insectoid nest. They were wiped out instead, due to the newfound strength bestowed on the insects by [deity0_name].</li>
					<li>conflict(tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->A violent [foeLeader] set fire to an insectoid hive, causing great suffering to its inhabitants and the surrounding environment.</li>
					<li>founderJoin(tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->Since childood, [founderName] was fascinated by the coordination and selflessness of insects. [founder_pronoun] dreamed of becoming a [founder_objective] in order to reform human society such that it resembled that of insectoids.</li>
					<li>victory(tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->[founderName] marched with an army of [memberNamePlural] and insectoids towards [place_powerCenter]. A long battle ensued, resulting in the defeat of [foeLeader] and [foeLeader_possessive] [foeSoldiers].</li>

					<!-- Ideological founder -->
					<li>setup(tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->Seeing the suffering brought about by waging war against insectoids, [founderName] advocated for taming and raising them instead.</li>
					<li>story(uses=1,tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->We realized that there was much to learn from insectoids, and that were more docile than expected.</li>

					<!-- Ideological lesson -->
					<li>lessonIntro(tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->Look at any insectoid colony, and it becomes clear as day that</li>
					<li>lesson(tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->insects are the perfect organisms, deserving immense respect rather than comtempt.</li>
					<li>lesson(tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->it is better to co-exist and have a symbiotic relationship with insects.</li>
					<li>lessonReinforcement(tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->Those who raise and live with insectoids in harmony seem to lead fulfilling and joyful lives.</li>

					<!-- Archist -->
					<li>archistBasis(tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->Archotechs are a part of the universal consciousness, just as insectoids are a part of their hive's collective mind.</li>
					<li>archistFact(tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->Archotechs and insectoids are both highly adaptible, resilient, and intelligent beings. These shared characteristics are no mere coincidence.</li>
					<li>archistProphecy(tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->[inTheEnd], humanity will incorporate into itself the advantageous characteristics of the insectoids, and gain mass conscioussness. Their combined power will enable them to rise to the level of the archotechs.</li>

					<!-- Animist -->
					<li>animistFact(tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->Insectoids can connect to the spirit world just as humans can.</li>
					<li>animistProphecy(tag=meme_InsectoidPrimacy)->[itIsSaid] that one day the true owner of the [relic0_name] will bring out its spirit, who will bestow humans with the strength and capabilities of insectoids.</li>
				</rulesStrings>
			</rules>
		</descriptionMaker>
		<symbolPacks>
			<li>
				<ideoName>Insecteanism</ideoName>
				<theme>insectoids</theme>
				<adjective>insectean</adjective>
				<member>insectist</member>
			</li>
			<li>
				<ideoName>Entomism</ideoName>
				<theme>insectoids</theme>
				<adjective>entomean</adjective>
				<member>entomist</member>
			</li>
		</symbolPacks>
	</MemeDef>

</Defs>