<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>MMTankMOD</name>
  <author>dragon</author>
  <packageId>dragon.MMTank.MOD</packageId>
  <url>
  </url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <description>
～Created by google translation～

Contents
A metal max-like car + drum can is added as an animal.

Wild buses, mosquitoes, buggies, wolfs, armored vehicles and drums will appear in each biome.
From the added car (pet), you can harvest Namari mushrooms and components (Wolf is an advanced component) on a regular basis.
Also, if you dismantle the car corpse, you will get a lump of iron scraps and components (same as above).


◎2021/07/16 Update
-Supports Ver1.3. It should be okay because the load folder is divided so that it works with Ver1.2 / 1.1.

◎2021/01/25 Update
-Angelring can now be created. Prosthetics research is needed.

◎2021/01/15 Update
-Namari mushrooms are now in the material category, no more manual transportation instructions
-You can now process Namari mushrooms on a fuel-powered workbench.

◎2021/01/08 Update
-The remaining durability is now displayed while the car is wearing the tile pack.
 Thank you Udon!
-Changed the items that can be obtained by cutting the hair of the car from iron scraps to namari mushrooms.
 Namari mushrooms can be refined into iron in the blast furnace in the raw material category, just like iron scraps.

◎ 2021/01/03 Update
-If the hunger rate is 0%, it may freeze when the caravan is configured, so set the hunger rate only slightly.

◎ 2020/08/07 Update
-I tried to see if it works with Ver1.2, so it was ok so I wrote the support version.

◎2020/06/13 Update
-We have implemented a vehicle tile pack that can be produced and used by introducing the Animal Gear MOD.
 It is treated like a shield belt that breaks with certain damage.
 Production requires plate armor research.

◎2020/06/09 Update
-An angel ring has been added as a type of implant. In addition, it is a complete minus item.
-The frequency of iron scraps collected from each car has been changed from 5th to 15th.

◎ 2020/05/19 Update
-Slightly modified Patche because the illustration of drum mod was replaced.

◎ 2020/05/18 Update
-Since the drumcan was unexpectedly strong, some abilities such as armor value were corrected.
-If you have introduced MMDrumcan MOD, we have included a patch that will allow cars to bathe.
　MMMDrumcan MOD → https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2100895553

◎2020/05/10 Update
- Added melee attack method to drums.
- If you introduce "Range Animal Framework (Continued)" (+ Harmony) as a prerequisite mod, some vehicles will be able to carry out long range attacks.

I would like to take this opportunity to thank you.

ーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーーー

このModで追加されるもの
メタルマックスっぽいクルマ＋ドラム缶を動物として追加します。

野バス・モスキート・バギー・ウルフ・装甲車とドラム缶が各バイオームに出現します。
追加されたクルマ（ペット）からは、ナマリ茸とコンポーネント（ウルフは先進コンポーネント）が定期的に収穫できます。
また、クルマの死体を解体した場合は、鉄クズの塊とコンポーネント（同上）が手に入ります。

◎2021/07/16 Update
・Ver1.3対応を実施。Ver1.2・1.1でも動くようにロードフォルダーを分けたから多分大丈夫なはず。

◎2021/01/25 Update
・エンジェルリングが作成可能になりました。人工装具の研究が必要です。

◎2021/01/15 Update
・ナマリ茸を正式に素材カテゴリにしました、もう運搬指示を手動で行う必要はありません。
・燃料式の工作台でナマリ茸を加工できるようになりました。

◎2021/01/08 Update
・クルマがタイルパックを装着中に残耐久力が表示されるようになりました。
　うどんさんありがとうございます！
・クルマの毛刈りで入手できるアイテムを鉄クズからナマリ茸に変更。
　ナマリ茸は原材料カテゴリで鉄クズ同様溶鉱炉で精錬して鉄にできます。

◎2021/01/03 Update
・空腹率が0%だとキャラバン構成時にフリーズする事があるため、空腹率をほんの僅か設定。

◎ 2020/08/07 Update
・Ver1.2で動くか試したら大丈夫だったのでサポートバージョンを記載。

◎2020/06/13 Update
・Animal Gear MODを導入することで生産・使用できるクルマ用タイルパックを実装しました。
  一定ダメージで壊れるシールドベルトのような扱いです。
  生産にはプレートアーマーの研究が必要です。

◎2020/06/09 Update
・インプラントの一種としてエンジェルリングを追加しました。なお、完全なマイナスアイテムです。
　どうしてもクソMOD要素を盛り込みたかった、満足している（などと供述しており）。
・各クルマから採取される鉄クズの頻度を5日から15日に変更しました。

◎2020/05/19 Update
・ドラム缶MODのイラストを差し替えたためPatcheを微修正しました。

◎2020/05/18 Update
・ドラム缶が想定外に強かったため、アーマー値など一部能力を修正しました。
・MMDrumcanMODを導入している場合、クルマたちも入浴するようになるパッチを同梱しました。
　MMDrumcanMOD→https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2100895553

◎2020/05/10 Update
・ドラム缶に近接攻撃の手段を追加しました。
・Range Animal Framework(Continued)（＋Harmony）を前提MODとして導入すると一部のクルマが遠距離攻撃を行います。
　※前提MODが無くても遠距離攻撃をしないだけでエラー等は発生しません。
　　もし問題が発生した場合は、HugsLibエラーログのURLをコメントに含めて報告してください。

～スペシャルサンクス～
○テクスチャは、pixivでkouto様が公開されているキャラチップを使用させていただきました。
○Defファイルはうにーぬ様の動物テンプレMODを元に作成しております。
○本MODを作るきっかけはtikubonn様のPanjangDrum MODを見て脳内でティンと来たためです。
○Rimworld相談所の皆様方から暖かい応援とご意見をいただきました。

この場を借りて御礼申し上げます。
</description>
</ModMetaData>