<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>[WarHammer 40k] GeneSeed</name>
	<author>AliceTries, updated by Ogliss</author>
	<supportedVersions>
        <li>1.0</li>
        <li>1.1</li>
        <li>1.2</li>
        <li>1.3</li>
        <li>1.4</li>
        <li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
   <packageId>Ogliss.AliceTries.GeneSeed</packageId>
	<description>Gene-Seed, the cure for rejection of the additional 19 organ implants on the path to becoming a super human. Mutates your pawns genetic code to be better down to every last cell.

		Slaughter and Butcher Human like to get GeneSeed. Take it to become a Astarte, complete with all bonus organs for optimal crusading.

		Once an astarte has the first nine organs in they are battle ready for Legionaries Astartes scout corps, with all 19 your pawn can become be a primarch worthy of challenging even Horus or the lords of chaos.
		
		----

		Differences to 40k Lore

		GeneSeed in 40k is extracted for existing Astarte that have had a progenoid organ for at least a few years, typically on death then crafted into the the 19 organs to be implanted in a male child under the age of 14. But thats a lotta micro management and astarte are ultra rare so lets assume geneseed is integrated with the main line humans in this world.

		GeneSeed in this mod is named differently than traditional 40k naming it should be called Gene Seed with a space; Ill change it if anyone is bugged by it.

		----
		Unique Organ Functions while under the effects of Gene Seed.
		- *Haemastamen* - ~Rapidly increased blood production~ Clots injuries for now.
		- *LarramansOrgan* - Clots injuries periodically
		- *Preomnor* - Removes food poisoning and just poisoning as a general
		- *OoliticKidney* - Rapidly reduce toxins from the body, you poop them out. It's lore.
		- *ProgenoidGlands* - Slowly produce GeneSeed within the Astarte's body increasing their combat abilities as time passes.
		
		Todo make the Black Carapace increase armor levels to Masterful version of whatever is on or a flat bonus.
		
		----
		Other WarHammer 40k Mods (Not by me)
		Astra Militarum:
			- Compatible, this mod adds additional gene seed for generating advanced organ to raise your neophytes to new levels... also armor, guns, plants, ...
			- Its more than I want but its there and we run together.
		Steam : https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=771341092&amp;searchtext=+Astra+Militarum

		----

		This mod and all my others are thanks to Girl Develop It - Empowering women to code. Please support if only by changing your Humble bundle donate to GDI. I give to my local chapter in Philly, hope you consider it too.
		[img]https://raw.githubusercontent.com/girldevelopit/gdi-website/4f226d6a61191c3e98b22854a2d9481f42f3c81b/app/assets/images/gdi-logo.png[/img]
		https://www.girldevelopit.com/
		
		----
		
		This mod Powered by harmony and has no other dependencies. 
			- Mod with Harmony not Hugs, because this is WarHammer 40k and its a rough place where I dont think the power armour is designed to allow you to hug. Full Nelson While Flaying your Neophyte's for the Black Carapace sure. Hugs, no.
	</description>
	<url>https://steamcommunity.com/id/AliceTries/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100</url>
</ModMetaData>