<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Patch>

	<Operation Class="PatchOperationFindMod">
		<mods>
			<li>Science Never Stops: You're Going Too Far</li>
		</mods>
		<match Class="PatchOperationSequence">
			<success>Always</success>
			<operations>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="PRF_Unobtainer"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
            <label>Abyssal AutoForge</label>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="PRF_Unobtainer"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
            <description>An automated version of the Abyssal Forge. The Abyssal AutoForge collects Abyssal Matter from the Eternal Planes without input, and then can weave it into a Plasteel and Gold catalyst in the form of Abyssal Alloy, along with providing other ways to refine Abyssal Alloy.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="PRF_Constructor"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
            <label>Entropic AutoFabricator</label>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="PRF_Constructor"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
            <description>An automated version of the Entropic Fabricator. The Entropic AutoFabricator is able to assemble many items from pure Abyssal Matter with extreme speed and ease. Such a wonderful device.</description>
					</value>
				</li>

				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="PRF_CosmicDrawer"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
            <label>Abyssal AutoDrawer</label>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="PRF_CosmicDrawer"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
            <description>An automated version of the Abyssal Matter Drawer. The Abyssal Matter AutoDrawer draws pure Abyssal Matter from the Eternal Planes, trading a vast amount of energy and time for stable, well-contained Abyssal Matter.</description>
							</value>
				</li>

				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="PRF_CosmicCall"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
            <label>The Automated Call of the Abyss</label>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="PRF_CosmicCall"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
            <description>An automated version of the Call of the Abyss. "All will heed the call of the Abyss Bloodline, else we fade into the ether."\n\nThe investment will be worth it, trust me. You can make it all back, and ten-thousand times more...</description>
					</value>
				</li>

				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="PRF_PinnacleFabricator"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
            <label>Automatic Dystopia</label>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="PRF_PinnacleFabricator"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
            <description>A device of pure horror, of pure beauty, of true perfection, automated. The very fabric of all existence is tied to its own existence, allowing things to be forged from the very foundation of all.\n\nNow you have a true Dystopia, for you have all the power where nobody else could even dream of dreaming for.\n\nThis item is ridiculously powerful and not balanced in the slightest, nor will it ever be. This is your reward for achieving the Pinnacle of Creation. Good luck.</description>
					</value>
				</li>

				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[@Name="CosmicCall_Part"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
            <description>Turn raw Abyssal Matter into one of the mysterious components needed to realize The Call of the Abyss.</description>
					</value>
				</li>

			</operations>
		</match>
	</Operation>

</Patch>