<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Medieval World (No Guns/Low Tech)</name>
	<author>Tamias</author>
	<targetVersion>0.18.1722</targetVersion>
	<description>(Updated 5/4/18)
	
"Medieval Worlds: Similar to Earth from the agricultural revolution until the industrial revolution. Social structures are usually feudal or imperial. Planets can stay in this state for millennia."

                                                                                                            - Rimworld Fiction Primer
__________________________________________________________________________

Medieval World is a world-limiter mod designed as a companion to Vindar's Medieval Times that makes the world a no gun/low technology setting. To keep this mod as compatible as possible, it adds no content to the base game, and all changes to the base game are made through the patch system. These changes are meant to make tribal/medieval game types more immersive, and include (but are not limited to):

- Removal of ancient shrines from map creation.
- Removal of guns from all vanilla factions and traders.
- Removal of all advanced armor except armor vests and simple helmets.
- Disabling the Mechanoid and Spacer factions.
- Disabling the ability of vanilla factions to siege.
- Disabling certain advanced events (pod crashes, psychic/poison ships, ect.)
- Making electricity unresearchable, as well as all technology beyond that point.
- Renaming armor vests to be slightly more thematic.
- Making both the armor vest and the simple helmet craftable at the fueled smithy work station.
- Removal of certain advanced items (AI core, glitterworld medicine, ect.)
- Removal of all advanced body parts (bionic and higher) from vanilla factions and traders.

As stated before, this mod was originally created to serve as a companion mod for Medieval Times. However, Medieval Times isn't required for this mod to function (but highly recommended), so it is entirely possible to play with just this mod alone. But, because this mod removes so much content, and wasn’t really designed to act as a standalone mod, it is recommended that you at least play with other mods that fill in the missing content with whatever you like. For example, you could combine this mod with a pre-electricity historic period mod to create whatever historic/low tech game type you wish. This mod *should* be compatible with most mods, and won’t affect the weapons, apparel, and factions of other mods provided they use their own item tags. (Even guns)

In addition to the above changes to the vanilla game, this mod also includes patches for a few mods that make them more “low tech” friendly. These include:

1. EPOE (Moved simple prosthetic research to medieval era, replaced electricity requirement from the simple prosthetic workbench with a wood fuel requirement.)
2. Mending: Easy Version (Moved mending research to medieval era, replaced electricity requirement from the mending workbench with a wood fuel requirement.)
3. Concrete Walls *REQUIRES THE MEDIEVAL TIMES MOD AS WELL* (Moved concrete research to medieval era, made concrete slabs craftable at the blacksmith’s smelter from the Medieval Times mod instead of the vanilla electric smelter.)
4. A Dog Said... (Moved simple animal prosthetics research to medieval era, replaced electricity requirement from the animal prosthetic workbench with a wood fuel requirement.)
5. Colony Manager (Reflavored managing software research to be more low tech, added a simple research bench requirement, and moved it to the medieval era.)
6. Combat Extended (Too many changes to list.)
7. Misc. Core (Disabled both the Railgun and the BrainPal.)
8. Medic Addons (Disabled industrial and spacer medical station add-ons)

Other recommended mods for low tech game types:

1. Medieval Times (My personal favorite mod, and the reason I made Medieval World in the first place. The mod is spectacular, and it's creator, Vindar, is a absolute class act. This one is a literal game changer, and I can't recommend it enough.)
2. Fishing Industry (Adds fishing. Excellent mod in almost all games, but nearly essential for those tribal tundra games where food is extremely scarce.)
3. Simple Sidearms (Allows pawns to carry bow + melee weapon together.)
4. Defensive Positions (Adds the ability to draft pawns to a saved position. This one is a lifesaver for all the micromanagement it takes care of.)
5. No Power Comms Console (Replaces the comms console with a message raven, Game of Thrones style.)
6. Dubs Skylights (Very useful for making greenhouses.)
7. Firepit + Torch Sconce (Adds a fire pit and torch sconce that can be refueled instead of simply disappearing like the regular fire and torch)
8. Bridges (Not only useful for the bridges, but also allows you to place water tiles for that castle moat you’ve always dreamed of.)
9. Tilled Soil (Adds buildable soil for growing crops almost anywhere. Pairs very nicely with Dubs Skylights.)
10. Quarry (Adds an excellent end-game electricity free resource mining solution)
11. Misc. Bees'n'Honey (Adds beehives, honey, and brewable mead. Skyrim approved.)

Suggested Load Order:

1. Core
2. Medieval Times
3. Combat Extended (Optional: Greatly enhances all aspects of melee combat. Adds skill based block, parry, and riposte mechanics, as well as fully functional shields).
4. Medieval Times + Combat Extended Compatibility Mod (Optional: Use if you intend to play with both Medieval Times and Combat Extended together.)
5. Medieval World

If you have any feedback or ideas, please feel free to leave me a comment on the Steam Workshop or the Ludeon Forums.
	</description>
</ModMetaData>