<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <COF_Torture_SpeedingRegeneration.label>Speeding Regeneration</COF_Torture_SpeedingRegeneration.label>
  <COF_Torture_SpeedingRegeneration.description>The extraordinary nano machine in the body of the gene carrier can make it repair the wound at an incredible speed.</COF_Torture_SpeedingRegeneration.description>


  <!-- Torture -->

  <COF_Torture_BoneSpike.label>Bone Spike</COF_Torture_BoneSpike.label>
  <COF_Torture_BoneSpike.description>The carriers of this gene have "bone spurs" in their bodies. These "bone spurs" are not bone warts/osteophytes in the medical sense, but bone spurs produced by the natural growth of bones, which can cause severe pain and occasional wounds. It is caused by the failure of a bone fractal gene, which was originally used to generate a large number of support structures inside the bone, thus strengthening the bone toughness of the gene warrior. After mutation, "bone spur" gene is used to pollute gene pool. It will be hidden in the body during childhood, but it will torture the owner from childhood.</COF_Torture_BoneSpike.description>

  <COF_Torture_NeverPainDowned.label>Never Pain Downed</COF_Torture_NeverPainDowned.label>
  <COF_Torture_NeverPainDowned.description>Carriers of this gene do not become unconscious from pain. The side effect is that their brains will endlessly receive the original pain signals.</COF_Torture_NeverPainDowned.description>
  <COF_Torture_NeverPainDowned.customEffectDescriptions.0>The pain signal received by the brain has no limit.</COF_Torture_NeverPainDowned.customEffectDescriptions.0>
  <COF_Torture_NeverPainDowned.customEffectDescriptions.1>The pain signal received by the brain cannot be attenuated or enhanced by other effects (disable pain multiplier)</COF_Torture_NeverPainDowned.customEffectDescriptions.1>

  <COF_Torture_Barbecued.label>auto cooked (Barbecued)</COF_Torture_Barbecued.label>
  <COF_Torture_Barbecued.description>The carriers of this gene will become barbecues after death, providing more nutritional value.</COF_Torture_Barbecued.description>
  <COF_Torture_Barbecued.customEffectDescriptions.0>The skin is barbecue color</COF_Torture_Barbecued.customEffectDescriptions.0>
  <COF_Torture_Barbecued.customEffectDescriptions.1>Turn into barbecue after death</COF_Torture_Barbecued.customEffectDescriptions.1>

  <COF_Torture_Epsilon.label>Epsilon Gene</COF_Torture_Epsilon.label>
  <COF_Torture_Epsilon.description>There was an anti Utopian near shining world that believed that it was a sin to give food and oxygen to members of the lower Epsilon level society, so this gene was designed. Later, the excessive sympathy of Alpha level members caused social division, and the world was destroyed by war, which failed to reach the technological level of the shining world.</COF_Torture_Epsilon.description>
  <COF_Torture_Epsilon.customEffectDescriptions.0>The secret of happiness and virtue is, to love what you must do. The goal of this genetic design is to make people like their unavoidable social destiny.</COF_Torture_Epsilon.customEffectDescriptions.0>


</LanguageData>