<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<REB.EditableBackstories>Rainbeau's Editable Backstories</REB.EditableBackstories>
	
	<REB.UseLiteMode>Use "Lite Mode."</REB.UseLiteMode>
	<REB.UseLiteModeTip>By default, "Editable Backstories" allows only its custom backstories to be selected randomly for new pawns. However, if this box is checked, the mod will instead allow new pawns to draw backstories from both its custom database and the vanilla database. (Note that vanilla backstories will always be visible and manually selectable when using a mod such as "Prepare Carefully," regardless of this option's setting.)</REB.UseLiteModeTip>
	
	<REB.CategorizeSource>Tag Backstories by Source.</REB.CategorizeSource>
	<REB.CategorizeSourceTip>If this option is selected, backstory titles will be tagged to indicate their source, with "(Vanilla)" and "(VanillaPK)" indicating basic vanilla backstories and "Pirate King" designated backstories, respectively, "(REB)" indicating backstories added by this mod, and "(Other)" indicating backstories added by other mods. These tags can make it easy to tell what you're looking at when searching through backstories in "Prepare Carefully" or a similar mod. However, the tags will also be visible on the character bio windows within the game itself, so you probably won't want to turn the option on except when you're actually manually creating new pawns.</REB.CategorizeSourceTip>
	
	<REB.AllowVanillaTriples>Allow Vanilla "Triple Names."</REB.AllowVanillaTriples>
	<REB.AllowVanillaTriplesTip>By default, the only predefined "triple" (or "full") names that will be available for random assignment to new pawns are the names defined in the mod's data files. If this box is checked, though, the "triple names" defined in the vanilla databases will also be available. (Note that even if you don't allow vanilla names, if you're playing in "lite" mode as defined above, the vanilla "Pirate King" pawns, whose names and bios are linked, can still show up in your games.)</REB.AllowVanillaTriplesTip>

</LanguageData>
