<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>A RimWorld of Magic - Space-Time Mage Class</name>
  <author>NetzachSloth</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>NetzachSloth.ARimworldOfMagic.SpaceTimeMageClass</packageId>
  <url>https://discord.gg/drTWJDg</url>
  <modDependenciesByVersion>
    <v1.4>
      <li>
        <packageId>Torann.ARimworldOfMagic</packageId>
        <displayName>A RimWorld of Magic</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1201382956</steamWorkshopUrl>
      </li>
    </v1.4>
  </modDependenciesByVersion>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
    <li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
    <li>jecrell.jecstools</li>
    <li>Torann.ARimworldOfMagic</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>
Adds the Space-Time Mage Class: Controllers of the space-time manifold. Their magic is designed to gain control of the battlefield, made to prevent enemies from reaching them, and is typically granted as part of a pact with with an extraplanar creature of similar abilities.

Sometimes this pact marks a Space-Time Mage's sould in such a way that the a small piece of the being granting them their power becomes visble through the mage's eyes. This can be as benign as an odd eye color, or as overt as clocks for pupils. Since this is mereley a reflection of the soul, the effect persists, and is still visible should thier physical eyes be lost.

Source:
https://www.dandwiki.com/wiki/Space-Time_Wizard_(5e_Class)
https://powerlisting.fandom.com/wiki/Space-Time_Magic

Mage: Blink, Reverse Blink, Accelerate Time, Reverse Time, Attraction, Repulsion

They also have a buff similar to Prediction that's always active.

Reverse blink is a custom version of summon that has it's stats changed to match blink, so at max, slightly less range than summon, but it's instant cast.

They also have a signifigant reduction to cooldown and mana cost. The idea is you can pop around instantly all over the place, moving enemies where ever you want. Since they have no real direct damage spells, I think it's still kinda balanced; let me know what you think.

Uses Torann's new A RimWorld of Magic - Custom Class Editor Add-on.
	</description>
</ModMetaData>