<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- 哨兵 -->

  <WarcasketHelmet_Sentinel.label>sentinel helmet</WarcasketHelmet_Sentinel.label>
  <WarcasketHelmet_Sentinel.description>The 5th generation warcasket of Interstellar Industries Complex of Nara, designed and mass-produced as a technical verification platform and a cheap backup solution for the humanoid automatic weapon program.\n\nThe helmet design of the Sentinel is derived from the standard shipbreaker equipment of Interstellar Industries Complex of Nara, which has reliable protection against high-speed objects and heat resistance.</WarcasketHelmet_Sentinel.description>

  <Warcasket_Sentinel.label>sentinel warcasket</Warcasket_Sentinel.label>
  <Warcasket_Sentinel.description>The 5th generation warcasket of Interstellar Industries Complex of Nara, designed and mass-produced as a technical verification platform and a cheap backup solution for the humanoid automatic weapon program.\n\nSince the turbulent period of air routes caused by the large-scale use of warcasket by pirates as an armed force, Interstellar Industries Complex of Nara has also become interested in such low-cost humanoid armored combat units, and a series of projects have been established as humanoid automatic weapons project's technical verification, and the Sentinel is the 5th generation warcasket that they put into mass production based on the technology of the humanoid automatic weapon AES-2 BoneMan.</Warcasket_Sentinel.description>

  <VFEP_WarcasketShoulders_Sentinel.label>sentinel shoulders</VFEP_WarcasketShoulders_Sentinel.label>
  <VFEP_WarcasketShoulders_Sentinel.description>The 5th generation warcasket of Interstellar Industries Complex of Nara, designed and mass-produced as a technical verification platform and a cheap backup solution for the humanoid automatic weapon program.\n\nThe Sentinel's shoulder armor parts are derived from the AES-2S Engineer Model A of the Humanoid Automatic Weapon Project, because its combat loss rate in actual combat is far less than expected, and its parts are reused in a large number of other projects.</VFEP_WarcasketShoulders_Sentinel.description>


  <!-- 守護者 -->

  <WarcasketHelmet_Guardian.label>guardian helmet</WarcasketHelmet_Guardian.label>
  <WarcasketHelmet_Guardian.description>The 5th generation warcasket of Interstellar Industries Complex of Nara, has been put into production since the Sentinel was successfully in active service in the security forces.\n\nThe Guardian's Helmet is a modification of the Sentinel's Shipbreaker Helmet, with additional full armor installed.</WarcasketHelmet_Guardian.description>

  <Warcasket_Guardian.label>guardian warcasket</Warcasket_Guardian.label>
  <Warcasket_Guardian.description>The 5th generation warcasket of Interstellar Industries Complex of Nara,A series of warcasket variants have been used for technical verification and data collection of humanoid automatic weapon projects and sold to all parts of the rimworld.</Warcasket_Guardian.description>

  <VFEP_WarcasketShoulders_Guardian.label>guardian shoulders</VFEP_WarcasketShoulders_Guardian.label>
  <VFEP_WarcasketShoulders_Guardian.description>The 5th generation warcasket of Interstellar Industries Complex of Nara, has been put into production since the Sentinel was successfully in active service in the security forces.\n\nThe Guardian's pauldrons armor are also derived from the Model A shoulder armor of the AES-2S Engineer project, but the bulletproof armor plate is mounted on the modular interface.</VFEP_WarcasketShoulders_Guardian.description>


  <!-- 暴君(數據尚未完成) -->

  <WarcasketHelmet_Tyrant.label>tyrant helmet</WarcasketHelmet_Tyrant.label>
  <WarcasketHelmet_Tyrant.description>An anti-mechanical cluster warcasket designed by Interstellar Industries Complex of Nara based on the purpose of a weapon carrying experimental platform.\n\The Tyrant's full-coverage helmet is equipped with an experimental electromagnetic jammer, which can effectively interfere electronic equipment from a long distance.</WarcasketHelmet_Tyrant.description>
  <WarcasketHelmet_Tyrant.verbs.0.label>electromagnetic jammer</WarcasketHelmet_Tyrant.verbs.0.label>

  <Warcasket_Tyrant.label>tyrant warcasket</Warcasket_Tyrant.label>
  <Warcasket_Tyrant.description>An anti-mechanical cluster warcasket designed by Interstellar Industries Complex of Nara based on the purpose of a weapon carrying experimental platform. \n\nThe Tyrant was originally designed to provide test data support for the project called AES-5S Colossus in the humanoid automatic weapon program. It is equipped with a large number of experimental technologies\n\nBut it should be noted that because the experimental nature of the tyrant. its protection is not ideal.</Warcasket_Tyrant.description>
  <Warcasket_Tyrant.verbs.0.label>shell launcher</Warcasket_Tyrant.verbs.0.label>

  <VFEP_WarcasketShoulders_Tyrant.label>tyrant shoulders</VFEP_WarcasketShoulders_Tyrant.label>
  <VFEP_WarcasketShoulders_Tyrant.description>An anti-mechanical cluster warcasket designed by Interstellar Industries Complex of Nara based on the purpose of a weapon carrying experimental platform. \n\nThe Tyrant's Pauldrons are equipped with a pair of smoke launcher arrays for the bipedal assault mech AES-5A Tauren, which can create a smoke screen to obscure the enemy's view.</VFEP_WarcasketShoulders_Tyrant.description>
  <VFEP_WarcasketShoulders_Tyrant.verbs.0.label>smoke launcher</VFEP_WarcasketShoulders_Tyrant.verbs.0.label>


</LanguageData>