<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<SZ_RE_Food_First.label>Shenzhou-Traditional Cooking</SZ_RE_Food_First.label>
<SZ_RE_Food_First.description>Culinary culture from China is also an art, and your subjects are just new apprentices, teach them to start from the very basics!</SZ_RE_Food_First.description>

<SZ_RE_Food_First_Rice.label>Shenzhou-Hybrid Rice</SZ_RE_Food_First_Rice.label>
<SZ_RE_Food_First_Rice.description>In the Shenzhou colony, the amazing super rice filled the stomachs of billions of people. And some more special varieties may be hidden on this continent quietly, waiting for your subjects to explore.</SZ_RE_Food_First_Rice.description>
<SZ_RE_Food_First_Rice.discoveredLetterText>Yuan Longping (September 7, 1930-May 22, 2021), male, Han nationality, person without party affiliation, from De'an County, Jiujiang City, Jiangxi Province. Born in Beijing on September 7, 1930, he is a Chinese hybrid rice breeding expert and pioneer in the research and development of hybrid rice in China. He is known as the "father of hybrid rice in the world". \n\n Three meals a day, the fragrance of rice permeates, and those who are full should always remember Yuan Gong. Without the efforts of Yuan Lao, these delicacies would hardly appear on ordinary people's tables!</SZ_RE_Food_First_Rice.discoveredLetterText>
<SZ_RE_Food_First_Rice.discoveredLetterTitle> About: Academician Yuan Longping</SZ_RE_Food_First_Rice.discoveredLetterTitle>

<SZ_RE_Food_First_Wheaten.label>Shenzhou-Noodles</SZ_RE_Food_First_Wheaten.label>
<SZ_RE_Food_First_Wheaten.description>Guess what you can make with this dough? \n\nA world! ! !</SZ_RE_Food_First_Wheaten.description>

<SZ_RE_Food_First_EXI.label>Diverse recipes[I]</SZ_RE_Food_First_EXI.label>
<SZ_RE_Food_First_EXI.description>Your colonists seem to be disgusted with ordinary food, and they want to eat more delicious food! \n\nPerhaps you can listen to their opinions?</SZ_RE_Food_First_EXI.description>
 
<SZ_RE_Food_First_Tree.label>Shenzhou-Mu Zhi</SZ_RE_Food_First_Tree.label>
<SZ_RE_Food_First_Tree.description>The popularity of these trees in the old earth may far exceed your imagination! Some of them will bear delicious and valuable small fruits in the corresponding season. \n\nMade these fruits into wine in a still, so that your colonists will experience a hearty feeling!</SZ_RE_Food_First_Tree.description>

<SZ_RE_Food_Second.label>China-improved cooking</SZ_RE_Food_Second.label>
<SZ_RE_Food_Second.description>The technology from the Chinese civilization gives your colonists the ability to become fat, but the premise is that you need a dexterous master to satisfy the increasingly discerning taste buds of your citizens.</SZ_RE_Food_Second.description>

<SZ_RE_Food_Second_EXII.label>Diverse recipes[II]</SZ_RE_Food_Second_EXII.label>
<SZ_RE_Food_Second_EXII.description>Your colonists are starting to get restless, they crave more rare foods, more complex cooking, and deeper soul shocks! \n\nFortunately, we know the solution~</SZ_RE_Food_Second_EXII.description>

<SZ_RE_Food_Second_Machine.label>China-Power Processing</SZ_RE_Food_Second_Machine.label>
<SZ_RE_Food_Second_Machine.description>The use of power tools in China can nearly double the processing time of raw materials! Now that you already have the technology, why not do it?</SZ_RE_Food_Second_Machine.description>


<SZ_RE_FoodStart.label>China-Food</SZ_RE_FoodStart.label>
<SZ_RE_FoodStart.description>This research represents the basic knowledge of "China-style food and related cooking". \nAnd we are about to lead all the way to the feast of taste buds.</SZ_RE_FoodStart.description>
<SZ_RE_FoodStart.discoveredLetterTitle>[Color, flavor]</SZ_RE_FoodStart.discoveredLetterTitle>
<SZ_RE_FoodStart.discoveredLetterText>Congratulations! The efficient treatment of starchy crops has been widely spread among your colonists! \nThis is only the first step, it is indeed a key step to unlock the mystery of food!</SZ_RE_FoodStart.discoveredLetterText>

<SZ_RE_Home_Ceramics_First.label>Shenzhou-ceramic kiln</SZ_RE_Home_Ceramics_First.label>
<SZ_RE_Home_Ceramics_First.description>Be careful of your fingers! She has an enthusiasm of 1500 degrees Celsius.</SZ_RE_Home_Ceramics_First.description>

<SZ_RE_Home_Ceramics_Second.label>Shenzhou-Electric Kiln</SZ_RE_Home_Ceramics_Second.label>
<SZ_RE_Home_Ceramics_Second.description>The technology of the new era makes the firing of porcelain a lot easier, but it is still an extremely complex and difficult task. \n\nHigh-quality porcelain is produced by masters after decades of experience, and its beauty and artistry far exceed real gold and silver.</SZ_RE_Home_Ceramics_Second.description>

<SZ_RE_Home_Ceramics_Third.label>Industrial casting</SZ_RE_Home_Ceramics_Third.label>
<SZ_RE_Home_Ceramics_Third.description>The powerful factions in this world are eyeing the colony you have created step by step! We must do everything possible to use limited materials, limited technology, and limited manpower to forge an endless Great Wall that will never collapse! \n\nUnlocking the process of directly converting stones into quartz bricks and batch calcined stone bricks requires work on an electric ceramic kiln. At the same time, the craft of making medicines and some addictive drugs in batches is unlocked. \n\nUnlock the forging of military ceramics, which is a new era of synthetic materials, durable and beautiful.</SZ_RE_Home_Ceramics_Third.description>

<SZ_RE_Home_Furniture.label>Shenzhou-Home</SZ_RE_Home_Furniture.label>
<SZ_RE_Home_Furniture.description>[Luxury, elegant and understated]\n\n[Exquisitely carved and unpretentious]\n\n[Small and elegant]</SZ_RE_Home_Furniture.description>

<SZ_RE_Home_Furniture_Joy.label>Shenzhou-Leisure Furniture</SZ_RE_Home_Furniture_Joy.label>
<SZ_RE_Home_Furniture_Joy.description>Ingeniously designed entertaining furniture, they once swept the entire old earth! \n\nThe gameplay usually changes according to different people, and it is an excellent place to cultivate family or friendship.</SZ_RE_Home_Furniture_Joy.description>

<SZ_RE_HomeStart.label>Shenzhou-Juxing</SZ_RE_HomeStart.label>
<SZ_RE_HomeStart.description>This research represents the basic knowledge of "Shenzhou-style furniture, dresses and production facilities". \nLet's open a fan of magnificent hesitation.</SZ_RE_HomeStart.description>
<SZ_RE_HomeStart.discoveredLetterTitle>[And'Ning' beauty]</SZ_RE_HomeStart.discoveredLetterTitle>
<SZ_RE_HomeStart.discoveredLetterText>Congratulations! The life of Ru Mao drinking blood has become history among your ministers! Put on your hand-knitted clothes, sit on the benches that you have carved yourself and have a good night's sleep!</SZ_RE_HomeStart.discoveredLetterText>

<SZ_RE_YiYaoStart.label>Shenzhou-Hanging Pot</SZ_RE_YiYaoStart.label>
<SZ_RE_YiYaoStart.discoveredLetterText>Congratulations! Your colonists now have a preliminary understanding of the medical theory of China! Pick a few sticks of wormwood, and then give your body and mind a real relaxation!</SZ_RE_YiYaoStart.discoveredLetterText>
<SZ_RE_YiYaoStart.description>This research represents the basic knowledge of "China's unique medicine". \nWe are about to open a magical world of medicine.</SZ_RE_YiYaoStart.description>
<SZ_RE_YiYaoStart.discoveredLetterTitle>[An'Tai' Kang]</SZ_RE_YiYaoStart.discoveredLetterTitle>

<SZ_RE_ExtraStart.label>Shenzhou-Xunzhen</SZ_RE_ExtraStart.label>
<SZ_RE_ExtraStart.description>This research represents the basic knowledge of "exotic content in China". \nThe origin of these things is no longer known, but we can take a good look at these things from foreign mountains and rivers.</SZ_RE_ExtraStart.description>
<SZ_RE_ExtraStart.discoveredLetterTitle>[Different'Home' Cuan]</SZ_RE_ExtraStart.discoveredLetterTitle>
<SZ_RE_ExtraStart.discoveredLetterText>Congratulations! The design concepts of some weird sculptures have been discovered by our colonists, let us see and continue to explore!</SZ_RE_ExtraStart.discoveredLetterText>

<DajianTech_JiCheFirst.label>Shenzhou-Broken Grand Plan [I]</DajianTech_JiCheFirst.label>
<DajianTech_JiCheFirst.description>These lost blueprints show the crazy ideals of the designers. After careful research, some ancient and dusty technologies have surfaced. \n\nAlthough these things seem a little crazy, when in a critical juncture, their role will be greatly highlighted.</DajianTech_JiCheFirst.description>

<DajianZiDongRenRouTech.label>Shenzhou-Broken Grand Plan [II]</DajianZiDongRenRouTech.label>
<DajianZiDongRenRouTech.description>After some research, the prototype of the automated device has emerged, and the automated device through detailed construction and design will greatly improve the efficiency of our production.</DajianZiDongRenRouTech.description>

<SZ_RE_JiuLei.label>Shenzhou - fine wine</SZ_RE_JiuLei.label>
<SZ_RE_JiuLei.description>These wines brought by Chinese civilization have been sought after by colonists in the marginal world! We only need to carry out special processing and fermentation of various grain products to make the most delicious wine!</SZ_RE_JiuLei.description>

<SZ_RE_Home_Furniture_Misc.label>ShenZhou - Zha burden</SZ_RE_Home_Furniture_Misc.label>
<SZ_RE_Home_Furniture_Misc.description>These exquisite sculptural furniture and beautiful storage facilities have been popular in the entire Shenzhou world! They not only have excellent aesthetics, but also have strong practicability. They are all high-quality and inexpensive treasures! \n\nUnlock these beautiful and generous buildings and facilities to add a new touch to your colony!</SZ_RE_Home_Furniture_Misc.description>

<SZ_RE_Food_YinPin.label>ShenZhou - tea</SZ_RE_Food_YinPin.label>
<SZ_RE_Food_YinPin.description>All kinds of delicious tea are waiting to be explored! These special drinks from China are made with pure natural plant formula, delicious and healthy!</SZ_RE_Food_YinPin.description>


<DajianTech_WenDuFirst.label>Other - advanced temperature control</DajianTech_WenDuFirst.label>
<DajianTech_WenDuFirst.description>After the preliminary analysis of these exotic data, we have mastered the relevant scientific and technological knowledge foundation for the construction of advanced temperature control devices. What we need to do next is to turn these theoretical knowledge into reality.</DajianTech_WenDuFirst.description>


</LanguageData>

