<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Defs>
	<!-- ||| Leo RACE |Metabolism +2|Complexity 13|Archite 1|  ||| -->
	<XenotypeDef>
		<defName>JAR_Leo</defName>
		<label>leo</label>
		<description>The Leo are a genetically spliced race of nomadic lions, adapted to thrive in savanna climates. Their golden fur and muscular build make them well-suited to withstand the intense heat and dry conditions of the savanna.\n\nAs a tribal culture, the Leo prioritize cooperation and strength. They rely on their physical prowess and hunting abilities to survive in the harsh environment, and have developed a deep respect for the balance of nature. They are skilled at tracking prey, and are able to take down even the largest of animals with their sharp claws and powerful jaws.The Leo value honor and loyalty above all else, and maintain a strict code of conduct within their tribes. They believe in earning one's place through strength and skill, and those who prove themselves in battle or hunting expeditions are highly respected. However, they are cautious of outsiders and will not hesitate to defend their territory and way of life against perceived threats.</description>
		<descriptionShort>The Leo race is a subspecies of humanoid creatures that have been genetically engineered using a combination of ancient feline gene patterns. They are most effective when working together in a pack, using their coordination and pack tactics to take down even the most formidable opponents.</descriptionShort>
		<iconPath>UI/XenotypeIcons/Leo</iconPath>
		<inheritable>true</inheritable>
		<nameMaker>JAR_NamerPersonFeline</nameMaker>
		<chanceToUseNameMaker>0.85</chanceToUseNameMaker>
		<combatPowerFactor>2.5</combatPowerFactor>
		<genes>
			<li>JAR_LeoSkin</li><!-- Skin -->
			<li>JAR_Leo_Tuft</li><!-- Hair -->
			<li>Hair_BaldOnly</li><!-- Hair Fallback -->
			<li>Beard_NoBeardOnly</li>
			<li>JAR_AdrenalineGene</li>
			<li>JAR_LeoEars</li><!-- Ears-->
			<li>JAR_LeoTail</li><!-- Tail-->
			<li>JAR_LeoVoice</li><!-- Voice -->
			<li>Ears_Cat</li><!-- Ears Fallback -->
			<li>Body_Thin</li><!-- Body Fallback -->
			<li>Body_Standard</li><!-- Body Fallback -->
			<li>Body_Fat</li><!-- Body Fallback -->
			<li>Body_Hulk</li><!-- Body Fallback -->
			<li>JAR_NineLives</li>
			<li>JAR_PrideHunter</li>
			<li>JAR_FelineClaws</li>
			<li>Hair_Gray</li><!-- Color -->
			<li>Hair_Blonde</li>
			<li>Hair_SandyBlonde</li>
			<li>Immunity_Weak</li>
			<li>PsychicAbility_Dull</li>
			<li>AptitudePoor_Shooting</li>
			<li>MinTemp_SmallDecrease</li>
			<li>MoveSpeed_Quick</li>
			<li>Sleepy</li>
			<li>FireWeakness</li>
		</genes>
	</XenotypeDef>
	
	<!-- ||| Tigris RACE |Metabolism +1|Complexity 14|Archite 1|  ||| -->
	<XenotypeDef>
		<defName>JAR_Tigris</defName>
		<label>tigris</label>
		<description>The Tigris are a genetically spliced race of nomadic tigers, possessing traits that allow them to survive in colder climates. Their thick fur provides insulation against the cold, and their sharp claws and teeth make them formidable hunters in snowy terrain.\n\nAs a tribal culture, the Tigris rely on their communal bonds and hunting prowess to survive. They are skilled at tracking prey and using all parts of the animals they hunt, from the meat to the bones and fur. Their nomadic lifestyle allows them to follow the herds and avoid over-hunting in any one area.Despite their fierce appearance and reputation, the Tigris place great importance on hospitality and respecting their fellow tribe members. They are fiercely loyal to their own kind, but are wary of outsiders and will defend their territory and way of life at all costs.</description>
		<descriptionShort>The Leo race is a subspecies of humanoid creatures that have been genetically engineered using a combination of ancient feline gene patterns. They are most effective when working together in a pack, using their coordination and pack tactics to take down even the most formidable opponents.</descriptionShort>
		<iconPath>UI/XenotypeIcons/Tigris</iconPath>
		<inheritable>true</inheritable>
		<nameMaker>JAR_NamerPersonFeline</nameMaker>
		<chanceToUseNameMaker>0.85</chanceToUseNameMaker>
		<combatPowerFactor>2.5</combatPowerFactor>
		<genes>
			<li>JAR_TigrisSkin</li><!-- Skin -->
			<li>JAR_Tigris_Tuft</li><!-- Hair -->
			<li>Hair_BaldOnly</li><!-- Hair Fallback -->
			<li>Beard_NoBeardOnly</li>
			<li>JAR_AdrenalineGene</li>
			<li>JAR_TigrisEars</li><!-- Ears-->
			<li>JAR_TigrisTail</li><!-- Tail-->
			<li>JAR_TigrisVoice</li><!-- Voice-->
			<li>Ears_Cat</li><!-- Ears Fallback -->
			<li>Body_Thin</li><!-- Body Fallback -->
			<li>Body_Standard</li><!-- Body Fallback -->
			<li>Body_Fat</li><!-- Body Fallback -->
			<li>Body_Hulk</li><!-- Body Fallback -->
			<li>JAR_NineLives</li>
			<li>JAR_PrideHunter</li>
			<li>JAR_FelineClaws</li>
			<li>Hair_LightOrange</li><!-- Color -->
			<li>Hair_SandyBlonde</li>
			<li>WoundHealing_Fast</li>
			<li>Immunity_Weak</li>
			<li>PsychicAbility_Deaf</li>
			<li>AptitudePoor_Social</li>
			<li>MinTemp_SmallDecrease</li>
			<li>MoveSpeed_Quick</li>
			<li>Sleepy</li>
			<li>FireWeakness</li>
		</genes>
	</XenotypeDef>
</Defs>