<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Defenses Expanded</name>
  <author>N7Huntsman</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
	<li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>n7huntsman.defensesexpanded</packageId>
  <description>Version: 4.0.1
   
A collection of fortifications from throughout history.

Gabions:
Hollow, usually cylindrical structures constructed from wicker or wood, the use of gabions for military and civil engineering purposes dates back centuries. Stood on end and packed with earth, rocks, or other locally available material, they provide a reasonable degree of protection against incoming fire. While their wooden construction makes them lightweight and portable, it leaves them vulnerable to incendiary weapons.

Hesco Barriers:
Also known as a “Hesco bastion” or “h-barrier,” the Hesco barrier is a modernized gabion, consisting of a cubic structure made of steel wire and a heavy-duty liner. Each cell stands roughly nine feet tall, and multiple cells can be stacked to create robust walls. Though they still need to be packed with sand or soil, they are much faster to construct than a sandbag structure of equivalent size. Once completed, the barriers are resistant to both gunfire and explosions, making them useful for the construction of perimeter walls and bunkers.

T-wall:
Also known as Bremer walls, T-walls are modular barriers made of reinforced concrete. Standing nearly twelve feet tall, they are practically impossible to scale, and are designed to withstand both direct fire as well as explosions. The barriers offer a compromise between cheaper, weaker masonry walls, and strong, but extremely expensive reinforced concrete walls.

Razor Wire:
An evolution of barbed wire, concertina wire is named for its helical shape and tendency to expand—resembling a musical instrument of the same name. It is generally made of two wires, a stronger, un-barbed support wire and a length of razor tape with sharp, pointed barbs produced in several different lengths. The result is a self-supporting wire structure that can quickly be deployed to create a formidable obstacle to infantry. Cheaper to deploy than a traditional wire-and-stake fence and simple to manufacture on an industrial scale, its low cost and lightweight make it ideal for fortifications and portable field defenses. 


</description>
</ModMetaData>