<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
  <ModMetaData>
	<name>Industrial armory 1.4 MKII (Previously Iron Accord)</name>
	<author>Civvie</author> <!-- \\\ Change to your username for Steam \\\ -->
	<supportedVersions>
	  <li>1.4</li> 	<!-- \\\ your can add more line when the new version for the game\\\ -->	
	</supportedVersions>	<!-- \\\ I forget all the code I stole, but there's a whole lot. Vanilla expanded for a start. \\\ -->
	<packageId>Civvie.IAArmorMark3</packageId>	<!-- \\\ Can change to anything \\\ -->
	<description>
The problem gets worse- I switched computers, had to download my own mod from the workshop, scratch in my new changes (You can now dye them! Yay!) (And the spacesuits work again!) and reupload. Sorry for the jank-shit.

Don't like Rimworld shield technology? Think plasteel's kinda unrealistic? Same here.
Adds industrial-tier zero-spacer power armor/advanced flak substitutes - No Plasteel, no Advanced Components, no Fabrication.
This mod spews errors, baby!

[h1]Starring:[/h1]
 - Thermal suits - Hot, cold and thermal, with corresponding belts and a helmet. Excellent temperature management and good weight but fragile.
 - Trench set - Like flak, but no plasteel.
 - MFAS sets - Want power armor? Well, we can't really pull it off without computers, but quaff enough steroids and growth hormones and wear twenty pounds of pulleys, and you can basically do the same thing.
 - SOS2-compatible Theta-Exosuit - Old russian-inspired EVA suit, with amazing thermal/environmental protection but little armor and high weight.

 Original credits included; Thank you, "Mechanized Armor Set"
Seriously, thanks. I wouldn't have figured this out without using your mod as a basis.
Feel free to reupload, rebuild, modify, do whatever with this mod. I steal code from others, anyways.

[h1]Credits:[/h1]
-/]rchon- Main Artist for the Apparel
-JangoDsoul- Artist retexture in Vector and XML coder
-CaptainMuscles - C# coder "Pizzacat_MechanizedArmor.dll"
-Myself - New XML frankenstein code and shitty paint.net textures

P.S.
Yeah, I don't know what I'm doing.

[url=https://discord.gg/7B7xqHh][img]https://i.imgur.com/cfoFEMA.png[/img][/url]
    </description>
  </ModMetaData>
