<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

  <TipSetDef>
    <defName>BoSTips</defName>
    <tips>
      <!-- BoS -->
      <li TKey="MainframeHint1">The Brotherhood of Steel fiercely protects its knowledge. Nevertheless, some exotic merchants can still give you access to their technologies.</li>
      <li TKey="MainframeHint2">Pre-war mainframes can be purchased in Brotherhood of Steel settlements or via caravan traders, provided you are not at war with them.</li>
      <li TKey="BoSrelations">The Brotherhood of Steel often maintains unstable and paranoid relations toward outsiders. Fortunately, they mostly stand receptive to acts of goodwill.</li>
      <li TKey="BoSstory1">In its frantic race for lost knowledge, it is very likely that the Brotherhood of Steel eventually reached the prerequisites for interstellar journeys.</li>
      <li TKey="BosScribequote">"The only salvation this tortured planet and its people have. Without us, humanity is sure to perish." - Brotherhood Scribe Vree</li>
      <li TKey="BoSstory2">The Brotherhood of Steel is a quasi-religious technocratic military order, founded in 2082 by members of the United States Armed Forces and government scientists.</li>
    <li TKey="BoSstory3">There are growing rumors of frightening figures in black power armor roaming the desert.</li>
    <li TKey="BoSstory4">Light recon armors allows colonists to mitigate the movement penalty induced by T-serie armors.</li>
<li TKey="Encstory1">Losing secured datakeys can be considered an act of treason and punishable by death. This is why the majority of Enclave officers carry them, rather than taking this risk.</li>
<li TKey="Encstory2">The Enclave is a post-War institution that developed from continuity of government of the pre-War federal government of the United States of America, frequently styling itself as the United States of America.</li>
<li TKey="Encstory3">Unless you prove your American citizenship, the Enclave will always be hostile to you. Whenever. For whatever reason.</li>
<li TKey="Encstory4">If you choose to play for the Enclave, expect strong opposition from other factions, and very few allies.</li>
<li TKey="Encstory5">"Another glorious day in this man's army !"</li>
    
    </tips>
  </TipSetDef>

</Defs>
