<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <supportedVersions>
	   <li>1.1</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <name>Transmution</name>
  <author>SomewhereOutInSpace</author>
  <packageId>SomewhereOutInSpace.Rimworld.Transmution</packageId>
  <description>Transmution is an efficient, reasonable late game way easily acquire vital resources without it feeling like cheating. Unlike other replicator mods, Transmution both requires you to input a resource to convert, and requires a special, expensive power source to further prevent abuse. I would especially recommend this mod to:

* Anyone playing on a map with limited crucial resources, like an ice sheet or a flat forest
* Anyone who likes long-term colonies but encounters problems with metal supply as the map is mined out
* Anyone who just wants to circumvent annoying resource shortages
* The 5 people with a supercomputer and 150 hungry colonists to feed (transmute some tasty tasty nutrient paste)

Transmute adds:

- The Transmution Reactor. The main part of the mod, Transmution Reactors can convert raw resources into other raw resources, and can also convert more specific ingredients into higher-tier resources. For example, you can turn wood into bluefur, and then turn that bluefur (or other textile) into devilstrand.

Generally the conversion rate is 10-10, but may change for higher-tier resources to prevent abuse. For example, 10 wood can be turned into 10 steel, but 10 wood will only equate to 5 plasteel.

Transmution Reactors can also draw directly on their own fuel reserves to create voxels, which can take the place of any raw material, but are low-volume and require 10 times as much for recipes, like gold and silver. Voxels are useful if you don't have cheap raw resources on hand, such as during toxic fallout events.

- Power cells. An advanced power storage solution created from uranium, plasteel and components at a fabrication table, this is the only power source available for Transmution Reactors. Even then, active use of a Reactor can drain the cells very quickly. Have a lot of uranium on hand, or transmute some before you run out of power. This is one of the limiting factors that helps Transmution feel reasonable.

One power cell costs 5 uranium, 5 plasteel, and 2 components.

- A new research tree that gates off transmution of more advanced materials. By default, you can only convert raw materials to wood, voxels and marble blocks. However, through the use of various research nodes, you can unlock metals, textiles, medical supplies, food, components, liquids, and drugs.

FULL LIST OF MATERIALS AND ITEMS THAT CAN BE PRODUCED VIA TRANSMUTION
Organized by research node

Basic Metals
* Steel
* Silver
Advanced Metals
* Gold
* Uranium
* Jade
Plasteel
* Plasteel

Basic Textiles
* Cloth
* Bluefur (for cold climates)
* Camelhide (for hot climates)
Advanced Textiles (requires simpler textiles/leathers)
* Synthread
* Devilstrand
Hyperweave (requires simpler textiles/leathers)
* Hyperweave

Basic Medical
* Herbal medicine
Advanced Medical
* Neutroamine
* Industrial medicine

Basic Food
* Nutrient paste meals
Advanced Food
* Simple meals (requires some form of food as input)
* Beef (can be used in transmution of simple meals)
* Corn (can be used in transmution of simple meals)

Basic Drugs
* Penoxycyline
* Smokeleaf joints
* Psychite tea
Advanced Drugs
* Yayo
* Flake
* Wake-up
* Go-juice
Luciferium
* Luciferium

Liquids
* Chemfuel
* Wort

Other
* Industrial Components
* Wood
* Marble blocks
* Voxels (produced directly from power cell reserves, no input resources needed)


-- POSSIBLE FUTURE EXPANSIONS --

- If there's enough demand, I might release additional module patch mods that add transmution of things like weapons, organs, more food, shells, etcetera.

- Balance numbers if the reviews say I didn't balance them right the first time.</description>
</ModMetaData>
