<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Waterproof Battery</name>
  <author>tikubonn</author>
  <packageId>tikubonn.WaterproofBattery</packageId>
  <url>https://twitter.com/tikubonn</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <description><![CDATA[<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Overview</color></size>

This Mod is very simple. This Mod add new waterproof batteries into your RimWorld. You can built those with construction after researched "Waterproof Battery". If you installed another Mod of "Small Battery", this Mod add more battery that small waterproof one.

屋外環境でも安全に使用できる防水バッテリーを追加します。追加されたバッテリーは研究「防水バッテリー」の履修後に建設することができます。また、Mod「Small Battery」も導入することで小型の防水バッテリーも建造できるようになります。

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Mod Compatible</color></size>

* Small Battery(https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2746038426)

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Bug Report</color></size>

Bug reports other than bugs that can be reproduced with this MOD alone will not be accepted. We do not intend to resolve issues that occur when playing the game using other MODs, so please resolve them by changing the load order or uninstalling this MOD yourself. Additionally, if you are reporting a bug that can only be reproduced with this mod, please be sure to provide the following information.

* What happened?
* When and under what circumstances did it happen?
* How can I replicate the issue?
* What's your RimWorld version?
* Post an error log! (If you have HugsLib -> Ctrl+F12 and paste the link in the comments!)

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>FAQ</color></size>

Q) Is the mod compatible with...?
A) We do not accept questions regarding compatibility with other MODs. If you can't resolve it yourself, please contact the mod's author.

Q) I want to report a bug!
A) Guidelines for reporting bugs can be found in `Bug Report`.

Q) Please add the features I came up with!
A) This MOD was originally written for my own use, so I generally do not accept requests. I feel more motivated and happy when I receive positive feedback rather than requests.

Q) Your translation is terrible!
A) If you think my translation is terrible, you can send the correct translation to me. If you sent the correct translation, I replace it and old translation after checked.

Q) May I upload a game video taken with this mod installed?
A) No problem of course. I give permission for you to upload videos taken with this mod installed and for you to monetize those videos. I also give you permission to use thumbnail images of this mod in your videos to showcase this mod.

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Translation</color></size>

English (tikubonn with Google Translation)
Japanese (tikubonn)

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Copyright</color></size>

© 2022 tikubonn

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>License</color></size>

Redistributing my MOD is prohibited.
These Terms of Use supersede CC BY-NC-ND 4.0.

Waterproof Battery © 2022 by tikubonn is licensed under Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivatives 4.0 International. To view a copy of this license, visit http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/4.0/

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Update History</color></size>

<color=#7f7f7f>2023-12-1:</color>
継続的な更新のためにビルド用のコードを整理しました。本MODのライセンスを CC BY-NC-ND 4.0 に設定し、それに合わせてMOD説明欄の文章を新しいものに変更いたしました。RimWorld 1.3向けの更新を終了しました。
Refactored code for builds for continuous updates. The license of this MOD has been set to CC BY-NC-ND 4.0, and the text in the MOD description has been changed accordingly. Finished updating for RimWorld 1.3.

<color=#7f7f7f>2022-10-6:</color>
This Mod has supported to RimWorld 1.4 unstable experimentally.
本 Mod を試験的に RimWorld 1.4 unstable に対応させました。

<color=#7f7f7f>2022-2-9:</color>
Fixed Japanese translation file little. Fixed research project file little.
日本語翻訳ファイルに小さなミスがあったので修正しました。研究「防水バッテリー」の表示位置を修正しました。]]></description>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>tikubonn.SmallBattery</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
