<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Uncompromising Fires</name>
	<author>Fuu Chan</author>
	<packageId>Fuu.UncompromisingFires</packageId>
	<description>
The goal of this mod is to make fires more interesting and dynamic!

For indoor fires, fires will grow and spread 2x faster (value adjustable in the options), which makes designing a base capable of containing indoor fires (such as with fire proof materials and fire extinguishing tools) a more important consideration.

For outdoor fires, fire growth and spread will scale depending on a new value called "Map dryness".

Right after rainfall fire growth and spread on outdoor objects will drop to 0%, making fires unable to grow or spread. But over time and highly dependent on the map's current temperature, that number will scale back up.

Because the rate at which the map dries depends on the temperature, summer will reclaim its throne as "fire season", while winter gives a short time to relax. Watch the world come alive, as the seasons and rain directly influence the outdoor fire risk!

Jungle and swamp biomes will behave more realistically, no longer igniting into massive forest fires due to their high rainfall. While boreal, tundra, and the ice caps will behave more realistically too, where the low temperature means the wetness stays high despite low rainfall. But watch out if it's a scorching hot desert during a heat wave! (Evaporation rate adjustable in the options).

Also allows the vanilla "Firewatcher" timer to be adjusted in the options, allowing time for forest fires to naturally burn instead of immediately triggering a rain upon any fire.

NEW!
Seasonal Extremeness slider: Increase the temperature difference between the coldest winter and hottest summer by a configurable degree! Want to see winters in the jungle? Want to vaporize in the summer? Now you can!

Compatibility
*Highly optimized for near 0% performance impact (Less than 0.001ms average in Dub's Performance Analyzer).

*Safe to add and remove mid-game (One-time error message is harmless).

*Independent, isolated, and minimal in scope, with no unsafe modifications to vanilla behavior/code: Only needs two simple "+" operations on "Fire growth per tick" and "Ticks until next fire spread", which should be compatible with nearly every mod, leaves no permanent changes to your saved game, and will not brick your game.

*Confirmed compatible with Vanilla Expanded series, Alpha series, Dubs series, and hundreds more.

*NOT compatible with Combat Extended however, because they replace vanilla's fire system with their own "wind speed and direction" system.
		
Updates
~3.1 update: New Seasonal Extremeness slider in the options! Can now increase the temperature difference between the coldest winter and hottest summer by a configurable degree in the mod options. Snow in the rainforest? Now you can!
~3.0 update: Now compatible with 1.5! Firewatcher time is now configurable in the options, and triggers sooner than before. Default max fire rate is 200% for both indoor and outdoor, due to proliferation of fire weapons since Biology.
~2.01 update: Reduced default maximum fire rate to 2x due to all the new fire weapons in 1.4 making big fires more dangerous (Existing users need to change this manually in the options).
~2.0 update: Now compatible with 1.4! Greatly increased the time the Firewatcher will wait before triggering.
~1.1 update: Improved the dryness GUI, and added options to customize it (such as a percentage view).
~1.01 update: Increased outdoor evaporation rate by 33%.

Github Link: https://github.com/tenguin/Rimworld_UncompromisingFires

Credits to: Walfieee, _LM7_, Amelia Watson, and unknown artist for the artwork used in the thumbnail and tanosii_chan for the upvote animation! Give them a visit!
	</description>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Anomaly</li>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>