<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>BuckleUp</name>
	<author>BoeDankles</author>
	<supportedVersions>
	<li>1.1</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>boe.buckleup</packageId>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>dninemfive.d9framework</packageId>
			<displayName>dninemfive</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2037445541</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>dninemfive.d9framework</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<description>	

	Requires Royalty DLC and D9 Framework.
	
	Required Mod can be found here: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2037445541
		
	This mod adds 5 new belts to the game that offer useful bonuses and give the player more options to use in their belt slots. Some of these belts are craftable, while some must be acquired from traders or quests. Can be safely added to saved games. For best results during removal, make sure you destroy all belts from your game first to avoid errors.
		
	
	Luminary Belt: A belt outfitted with an array of bright, lightweight bulbs that can illuminate the area around the wearer. 
	-Requires Machining Research (Made at Machining Tables)
	-Requires crafting level 3 and a Machining Table
	-Costs 20 steel, 20 silver and 2 components
	-Wearer emits light in a 4 tile radius and will never suffer from mood or speed penalties while working in dark areas
	(Special Thanks to Rikiki, TheGoofyOne, and Safety Mets for all their work on wearable lighting, they deserve all credit for this as I'm merely copying code from Safety's mod)
	
	
	Bandolier Belt: A shoulder-slung belt for holding various ammunition types that provides quick access for rapid reloading. Holsters are reinforced with plasteel to protect the ammunition stored inside.
	-Requires Machining Research (Made at Machining Tables)
	-Requires crafting level 5 and a Machining Table
	-Costs 40 cloth, 30 steel, 10 plasteel and 2 components
	-Wearer's aiming time is shortened by 25%, allowing them to fire more often
	
	
	Deflector Belt: A projectile-repulsion device designed for ranged combat. Unlike shield belts, deflector belts do not continuously sustain a barrier, therefore allowing the wearer to fire out. Instead, it uses a sensor array to detect incoming projectiles and deflects them by generating micro-shields in their trajectory. Can protect the wearer from small, controlled bursts, but is easily overwhelmed by sustained gunfire.
	-Requires Shield Belt Research
	-Requires crafting level 6 and a Machining Table
	-Costs 40 steel, 30 plasteel, 10 uranium and 3 components
	-Wearer is protected by a low capacity, quick recharging shield that doesn't block outgoing projectiles, can only block 2~3 shots in quick succession before breaking, will quickly recharge if not broken
	(Special thanks to dninemfive for his framework, which includes the framework for Ranged Shield Belts. Making this belt would not have been possible without it.)
	
	
	Psyfocus Belt: A bejeweled belt studded with psychic focusing crystals. Increases the wearer's psychic sensitivity and entropy recovery. It is also very stylish, boosting the wearer's social impact.
	-Not craftable, must be acquired from traders or quests (~1200 Market Value)
	-Wearer's Psychic Sensitivity and Entropy Recovery rates are increased, as well as their Social Impact
	
	
	Windforce Belt: A specialized mobility enhancing belt. Creates an aerodynamic bubble around the user which greatly reduces their drag, allowing them to move rapidly with ease and fluidity. It also comes equipped with a lighting array.
	-Not craftable, must be acquired from traders or quests (~1600 Market Value)
	-Wearer emits light identical to a Luminary Belt and is able to move considerably faster


	</description>
</ModMetaData>