<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<HadTangYuan.label>Enjoyed the glutinous rice balls</HadTangYuan.label>
<HadTangYuan.description>Due to the rich nutrition of glutinous rice balls, traditional Chinese medicine has always regarded Yuanxiao as a substance that can nourish deficiency, regulate blood, invigorate the spleen, and appetite. Modern nutritionists also highly praise the health function of Yuanxiao. \n\nThis individual has gained some buffs due to the consumption of glutinous rice balls.</HadTangYuan.description>
<HadTangYuan.stages.0.label>The nourishing effect of glutinous rice balls</HadTangYuan.stages.0.label>

<HadHuntun.label>Enjoyed the wonton</HadHuntun.label>
<HadHuntun.description>Wonton is made of flour and is a staple food. It contains sugars and vitamins, and is the main source of body heat. Wonton fillings are vegetables and meat. This combination is very reasonable. \n\nThis individual gained some buffs because of eating wontons.</HadHuntun.description>
<HadHuntun.stages.0.label>The nourishing effect of wonton</HadHuntun.stages.0.label>

<HadJiaoZi.label>Enjoyed dumplings</HadJiaoZi.label>
<HadJiaoZi.description>There are various fillings of dumplings, such as leek fillings, shepherd's purse fillings, pork fillings, beef fillings, etc. Therefore, dumplings with different fillings have different nutrients, but they can improve nutrition and energy for the body. \n\nThis individual gained some buffs because of eating wontons.</HadJiaoZi.description>
<HadJiaoZi.stages.0.label>The nourishing effect of dumplings</HadJiaoZi.stages.0.label>

<HadBaoZi.label>Enjoyed the Baozi(buns)</HadBaoZi.label>
<HadBaoZi.description>Steamed buns are fermented foods, and eating more fermented foods is very good for health. Traditional fermented foods have a wide range of raw materials, and the types of microorganisms used in fermentation are diverse. The main forms of fermentation are liquid or solid fermentation and natural or pure-bred fermentation. Traditional fermented foods have rich nutritional value and powerful health functions. \n\nThe individual became less hungry in a short period of time because of the consumption of buns.</HadBaoZi.description>
<HadBaoZi.stages.0.label>The feeling of fullness brought by buns</HadBaoZi.stages.0.label>

<HadManTou.label>Enjoyed the steamed buns</HadManTou.label>
<HadManTou.description>If the human body lacks vitamin B1 and vitamin B2, it will feel weak, lack of energy, and fatigue easily. The buns are rich in vitamin B1 and vitamin B2 and other B vitamins, which can invigorate the spirit and relieve hunger.</HadManTou.description>
<HadManTou.stages.0.label>The satiety brought by steamed buns</HadManTou.stages.0.label>

<HadHuoGuo.label>Enjoyed the hot pot</HadHuoGuo.label>
<HadHuoGuo.description>There is less nutrient loss when eating hot pot, and the nutrients of the food in the pot can be almost completely eaten. And it helps to remove moisture from the body. \n\nBecause the individual had enjoyed the hot pot, he received a good bonus that lasted 8 hours.</HadHuoGuo.description>
<HadHuoGuo.stages.0.label>The ultimate enjoyment of hot pot</HadHuoGuo.stages.0.label>

<HadBaoBing.label>Enjoyed Chinese crepes</HadBaoBing.label>
<HadBaoBing.description>In the Qingming season, spring leek is warm in nature. It is a good vegetable to protect the liver. It has the effects of promoting qi, regulating blood and removing blood stasis. The addition of mung bean sprouts also has the effects of clearing heat and detoxification, quenching thirst and diuresis. The curative effect is wonderful, nutritious, delicious, folk saying There are: "bean sprouts and chives, everyone loves". \n\nThis individual has a slight increase in metabolism due to the consumption of pancakes.</HadBaoBing.description>
<HadBaoBing.stages.0.label>The nourishing effect of pancakes</HadBaoBing.stages.0.label>

<HadChaoFan.label>Enjoyed fried rice</HadChaoFan.label>
<HadChaoFan.description>The main raw material of fried rice is rice, and rice is rich in carbohydrates. The protein is mainly rice protamine. Its amino acid composition is relatively complete, and it is easier to be absorbed by the body. digestion. \n\nAs a result of eating fried rice, the individual's metabolic ability has been slightly improved.</HadChaoFan.description>
<HadChaoFan.stages.0.label>The nourishing effect of fried rice</HadChaoFan.stages.0.label>

<HadLaoGanMa.label>Excessive liver fire</HadLaoGanMa.label>
<HadLaoGanMa.description>Eating old Ganma often can lead to problems such as body fire. \The individual was inflamed by the long-term and frequent consumption of Laoganma. Fortunately, as long as he stopped taking Laoganma for a period of time, he would get better.</HadLaoGanMa.description>
<HadLaoGanMa.stages.0.label>Extremely subtle, no impact</HadLaoGanMa.stages.0.label>
<HadLaoGanMa.stages.1.label>slight</HadLaoGanMa.stages.1.label>
<HadLaoGanMa.stages.2.label>Heavy</HadLaoGanMa.stages.2.label>
<HadLaoGanMa.stages.3.label>Very serious</HadLaoGanMa.stages.3.label>
 
<AiJiuHigh.label>Curative effect of Moxibustion</AiJiuHigh.label>
<AiJiuHigh.labelNoun>A moxibustion to relax</AiJiuHigh.labelNoun>
<AiJiuHigh.description>Moxibustion can warm meridians and disperse cold. Hot moxibustion can stimulate meridians and acupoints in a warm way and strengthen the movement of Qi and blood. After using moxibustion stick, the individual has a good gain in blood circulation and some aspects.</AiJiuHigh.description>

<AiJiuNaiShou.label>Special tolerance of Moxibustion</AiJiuNaiShou.label>
<AiJiuNaiShou.description>Although moxibustion has no obvious side effects in theory, it is also not addictive. However, due to the special environment of the edge world, the high frequency of using moxibustion stick will affect the user's consciousness to a certain extent. But don't worry, as long as you stop using it for a while, the negative effect will disappear. \n\nGenerally speaking, using the moxibustion stick once every one day or more will not produce negative effects.</AiJiuNaiShou.description>
<AiJiuNaiShou.stages.0.label>Extremely subtle, no impact</AiJiuNaiShou.stages.0.label>
<AiJiuNaiShou.stages.1.label>slight</AiJiuNaiShou.stages.1.label>
<AiJiuNaiShou.stages.2.label>Heavy</AiJiuNaiShou.stages.2.label>
<AiJiuNaiShou.stages.3.label>Very serious</AiJiuNaiShou.stages.3.label>

<HadMingCai.label>Enjoyed the traditional dishes</HadMingCai.label>
<HadMingCai.description>This colonist has recently enjoyed traditional dishes. It takes a lot of energy and materials to make a traditional dish, so the health benefits it provides are also considerable. \n\nThis effect can be obtained by enjoying any traditional famous dishes, but considering the balance of the game, the effect benefits cannot be superimposed, but the duration of the effect can be extended by continuing to enjoy traditional famous dishes.</HadMingCai.description>
<HadMingCai.stages.0.label>Health benefits brought by traditional famous dishes</HadMingCai.stages.0.label>

<BaiGuoJiuHigh.label>Ginkgo wine</BaiGuoJiuHigh.label>
<BaiGuoJiuHigh.description>Because ginkgo wine can reduce blood fat, cholesterol, improve memory, soften blood vessels and other effects, this individual will not be infected with asthma, arteriosclerosis, Alzheimer's disease and other diseases in the next period of time.</BaiGuoJiuHigh.description>

<HediffDef_ZhuanZhuo.label>Turntable impact</HediffDef_ZhuanZhuo.label>
<HediffDef_ZhuanZhuo.description>Colonists can provide dining speed when enjoying food at the turntable.</HediffDef_ZhuanZhuo.description>

<HadZongZi.label>Enjoyed Zongzi</HadZongZi.label>
<HadZongZi.description>The Zongzi adopts the unique new formula of the Chinese colonists. After enjoying the Zongzi, the colonists can get a sense of fullness, their metabolic spiritual power has been improved, and the body is more energetic.</HadZongZi.description>
<HadZongZi.stages.0.label>Zongzi synergies</HadZongZi.stages.0.label>


<HadMenMian.label>Enjoyed Liao Rice noodles</HadMenMian.label>
<HadMenMian.description>Because braised noodles are rich in flour, colonists can get a good satiety bonus. At the same time, braised noodles can also nourish the spleen and kidneys. Therefore, the metabolic capacity of colonists after enjoying braised noodles also gains a small margin. Promote.</HadMenMian.description>
<HadMenMian.stages.0.label>Enjoyed Liao Rice noodles</HadMenMian.stages.0.label>

<HuangJiuHigh.label>China liquor synergies</HuangJiuHigh.label>
<HuangJiuHigh.description>Alcohol and herbs have been incorporated into the blood. Similarly, these refined Chinese herbal ingredients have made the colonist excited. Similarly, the individual’s metabolic ability has been improved, and his sensitivity to pain has also been reduced a lot, but this It also makes him less sober than before drinking.</HuangJiuHigh.description>
<HuangJiuHigh.stages.0.label>Slightly drunk</HuangJiuHigh.stages.0.label>

<ShenZhouJiuTolerance.label>Shenzhou alcohol tolerance</ShenZhouJiuTolerance.label>
<ShenZhouJiuTolerance.description>The colonists were produced by drinking Shenzhou liquor. The more severe the tolerance, the more Shenzhou liquor needed to obtain the same effect. \n\nFortunately, the negative effects of the raw materials of Shenzhou liquor are very small, so this tolerance dissipates quickly.</ShenZhouJiuTolerance.description>

<ShenZhouJiuAddiction.label>China alcohol addiction</ShenZhouJiuAddiction.label>
<ShenZhouJiuAddiction.description>Excessive consumption of Shenzhou alcohol may cause colonists to develop addiction and dependence on Shenzhou alcohol. Although compared with beer and other alcohol, the raw materials used in the brewing of Shenzhou alcohol are less harmful to the nerves, but this is not It means that the colonists' addiction to Chinese alcohol is a good thing. \n\nIf the supply of alcohol products (including beer and Chinese alcohol) is lacking, colonists will have withdrawal reactions, and the brain will return to normal after a period of time, so that the problem of addiction can be fundamentally solved Of course, it will take longer for the colonists to get rid of their dependence on Shenzhou liquor.</ShenZhouJiuAddiction.description>

<XiongHuangHigh.label>Realgar wine extra potency</XiongHuangHigh.label>
<XiongHuangHigh.description>Because braised noodles are rich in flour, colonists can get a good satiety bonus. At the same time, braised noodles can also nourish the spleen and kidneys. Therefore, the metabolic capacity of colonists after enjoying braised noodles also gains a small margin. Promote.</XiongHuangHigh.description>

<PiShuangHigh.label>Arsenic efficacy</PiShuangHigh.label>
<PiShuangHigh.description>The medicinal effect provided by arsenic drugs can last for a long time. It can make colonists immune to diseases such as malaria and asthma, and at the same time improve the breathing and operation ability of colonists, but even after treatment, it still has a certain degree of toxicity. Therefore, colonists The consciousness and metabolic ability of the patient are slightly affected.</PiShuangHigh.description>

<MeiGuoChaHigh.label>Berry tea</MeiGuoChaHigh.label>
<MeiGuoChaHigh.description>Berry tea has the effect of relieving summer heat and refreshing. After enjoying berry tea, the colonists alleviated the symptoms of heatstroke (functional production), and the rate of fatigue improvement was also reduced.</MeiGuoChaHigh.description>

<HadYueBing.label>Enjoyed moon cakes</HadYueBing.label>
<HadYueBing.description>Mooncakes are filled with plant-based raw material seeds, such as almonds and walnut kernels. After enjoying the mooncakes, the colonists have improved their metabolism and blood circulation, and they are also more vigorous.</HadYueBing.description>

<ShenZhouTea_High.label>Shenzhou tea general efficiency</ShenZhouTea_High.label>
<ShenZhouTea_High.description>The synergy obtained after drinking some varieties of tea from China. Generally speaking, the drink of China tea can increase the spirit of the colonists, as well as promote their blood circulation and improve the speed of immunity. This effect often lasts for a long time.</ShenZhouTea_High.description>


</LanguageData>