<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>SF Comfy Meditation</name>
  <author>SheiFoxy</author>
    <packageId>SF.Comfy.Meditation</packageId>
  <supportedVersions><li>1.3</li><li>1.4</li></supportedVersions>
  <description> 
 ★·.·´¯`·.·★ What does it do? ★·.·´¯`·.·★ 
Gives you 6 cushy comfy meditation pillows, one for each meditation focus type!

Stats:
10 beauty (except Minimal type has 0 beauty)
1 comfort

Pawns will sit on them and meditate at a nearby focus just like a meditation spot! So put them near your pawn's favored focus type and let them meditate away in comfort!

Exception: Dignified cushion acts as a throne! You can have your pawn meditate on it like a throne.
It will also satisfy room throne room requirements, but it does not give as powerful focus gain as a normal throne.

 ★·.·´¯`·.·★ Compatibility ★·.·´¯`·.·★ 
SHOULD be compatible with basically everything unless it directly messes with the meditation spot?
Save-game compatible.


 ★·.·´¯`·.·★ License ★·.·´¯`·.·★ 
Open Source. Zombie License 1year. 
If I don't respond to permission requests for 1 year, permission is granted for someone else to do so.
  
   ★·.·´¯`·.·★ Thanks! ★·.·´¯`·.·★ 
   HUGE thanks to legodude17 for writing the C# part of this mod! I couldn't have done this without you!
   Also huge thanks to the Rimworld discord modding community which has been utterly essential in helping me learn enough xml to code a mod like this! Thank you all!
   
----[Modder Luv]----
If my mod is a Must Have! or you like it enough to toss me a couple smackaroos, please click this button and send me a meager donation with which to buy a tasty coffee, or more likely, go toward continuing to eat and keep internet on.
[url=https://ko-fi.com/sheifoxy][img]https://i.imgur.com/lIUBY5J.png[/img][/url] [url=https://ko-fi.com/sheifoxy][img]https://i.imgur.com/lIUBY5J.png[/img][/url] [url=https://ko-fi.com/sheifoxy][img]https://i.imgur.com/lIUBY5J.png[/img][/url] [url=https://ko-fi.com/sheifoxy][img]https://i.imgur.com/lIUBY5J.png[/img][/url] [url=https://ko-fi.com/sheifoxy][img]https://i.imgur.com/lIUBY5J.png[/img][/url] 
	</description>

</ModMetaData>
