<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>RimTrash</name>
	<author>tikubonn</author>
  <packageId>tikubonn.RimTrash</packageId>
	<url>https://twitter.com/tikubonn</url>
	<description><![CDATA[<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Overview</color></size>

do you want to be moderate inconvenient?
if its answer is yes, I recommend this MOD!

ほどよい面倒臭さをお求めですか？
だとしたらこのMODはぴったりだと思います。

after installed this MOD, colonists will create a trash bag when clean filth.
created trash bag is not dirty, but it has a beauty penalty.
if you want to destroy those, you can burn those with campfire and crematorium.
or, you can make new products with those.

本MODを導入すると、入植者が掃除をするたびにゴミ袋が生成されるようになります。
生成されたゴミ袋は不潔ではありませんが、美しさへのペナルティをもちます。
これらのゴミ袋は焚火や焼却炉で消滅させることができます。
また、これらのゴミ袋から武器や食事などのアイテムを作成することができます。

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>MOD Compatibles</color></size>

this MOD has compatibles for these MODs. but, I don't promise keep those compatibles forever.

本MODは下記のMODに対応しています。ただし、これらの互換性は将来にわたって継続される保証はございません。ご留意ください。

* [1.2]Silkiera Race
* [1.2]Xenoorca Race
* [1.2]Idhale Race
* [1.2]Nearmare Race
* NewRatkinPlus
* Kijin Race 2.0
* Moyo-From the depth

becareful, this MOD apply many patches to RimWorld's system. so if you make or use added things by this MOD by incompatible pawn and mortar, it may not work perfectly.

本MODは数多くの処理にパッチを当てています。そのため、未対応の種族で追加されたアイテムを製造・使用した際に、満足する結果が得られない場合がございます。あらかじめご了承ください。

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Bug or MOD Conflict</color></size>

I will not resolve MOD conflict, because I have no free time. if you want to resolve MOD conflict, you have to resolve yourself. if you want to report a bug to me, you have to give these detail. if you report without these details, I cannot fix it.

RimWorld には数多くのMODがあり、それらすべてに対応することは不可能です。なので、MODの競合があっても対応することはございません。また、不具合を発見して報告したい場合には、必ず以下の情報を提供してください。提供していただけない場合には、修正を行うことができません。ご留意ください。

* what happen? (なにが起こったのか)
* when caused it? (いつ起こったのか)
* how to cause it? (どのようにすると起こるのか)
* what record in error log? (エラーログはどうなっているのか)
* what your RimWorld's version? (RimWorldのバージョンはいくつなのか)
* used this MOD only or not? (このMODのみを使用しているのか)

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>FAQ</color></size>

Q) is this compatible for ~?
A) try check it yourself, because I have no free time for you.

Q) please compatible this to ~.
A) make a patch yourself.

Q) how to use ~? how to get ~?
A) read this page all first before question.

Q) I want to report a bug!
A) read section of "Bug and MOD Conflict" first before report.

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Copyright</color></size>

(c) 2020 tikubonn

this MOD require Harmony.dll, it has released under the MIT License. you can read its license to About/Harmony.LICENSE.

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Update History</color></size>

2020/11/17:
ゴミ袋生成時に ThingID を節約するように処理を改良しました。
upgraded processing to reduce spend ThingID on create trash bag.

2020/12/11:
敵が汚物ランチャーを装備してこないように修正しました。レシピ「ゴミ袋を焼却する x75」で75個未満のゴミを燃やさないよう修正しました。
deny enemy to equip trash launcher when raid. deny burn trash on "Burn trash x75" until its stack count greater than 75th.]]></description>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
	<loadBefore>
	</loadBefore>
	<loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>Ayameduki.HARSilkiera</li>
    <li>Ayameduki.HARXenoorca</li>
    <li>Ayameduki.HARIdhale</li>
    <li>Ayameduki.HARNearmare</li>
    <li>Solaris.RatkinRaceMod</li>
    <li>ssulunge.KijinRace2</li>
    <li>Nemonian.MY</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<incompatibleWith>
	</incompatibleWith>
</ModMetaData>
