<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
	<ModMetaData>
		<name>Flashlights</name>
		<author>TheGoofyOne</author>
	<url>about:blank</url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.0</li>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>TheGoofyOne.Flashlights</packageId>
		<description>A Flashlight!

Version 1.6

One for your hand, as well as a tortoise shell mining helmet.

Way before there was electricity on The Rim, there were flashlights. ;)

Since we have no battery replacements in place, the lifespan of the flashlights is 2 weeks. Craft a new one when you need it they're cheap, 20 steel and one component. Lifespan info available when not worn.

Butcher a Tortoise and use the shell to make a stylish helmet made from a tortoise shell and a flashlight. It will help protect you as well as lighting your way though the night, and for some reason helps a little with psychic drones.

No Tortoises? No Problem. Take a Simple Helmet and a Flashlight and make a lighted helmet to assist in mining. :)

All available after researching machining.

NOTE: Flashlights cannot be seen while equipped as the colonists don't have any hands.

Flashlight uses a new layer for hands and does not take up a spot for clothing or armor.

Flashlights cannot be worn on arcotech arms as the hand where the flashlight goes has been removed and the arcotech arm seems to not have a seperate hand definition. If I find a way to resolve this I will.

Turtle mining helmet takes up the standard helmet spot.

Compatibility: Adds a few lines to the Tortiose to allow acquiring a shell while butchering, but everything else is new and should have no conflicts.

Known Issues: Simple Sidearms

Original idea and assemblies by Rikiki



Version 1.0 - Release
Version 1.1 - Added time frame to Flashlights. Now last 2 weeks on the RIM.
Version 1.2 - Updated to work with 1.1
Version 1.3 - Added Lighted Helmet made from Simple Helmet and Flashlight.
Version 1.4 - Smelting Turtle shells should now work again and the red error is gone.
Version 1.5 - Updated to RW 1.3
Version 1.6 - Updated to RW 1.4

</description>
</ModMetaData>
