<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> <!-- Comments in XML look like this-->
<ModMetaData>
    <name>No more RiceWorld</name> <!-- This is the name of the mod -->
    <author>Voidfirefly</author> 
    <packageId>Voidfirefly.NoMoreRiceWorld</packageId> <!-- It is best to use this format-->
    <description>
    This mod aims to make food variety a necessity for both mental and physical health. When pawns eat food with different ingredients, their mood and performance improve. When pawns do not get enough food variety, the opposite happens: their mood and performance worsen.
	Pawns need a variety of nutrients to stay healthy and perform their best. These nutrients include proteins, carbohydrates, and vitamins.
	Proteins are found in meat, animal products, and some plants.
	Carbohydrates are the body's main source of energy.Carbohydrates can be found in plant foods like rice, corn and potatoes.
	Vitamins are essential for many bodily functions, such as maintaining a healthy immune system, producing blood cells, and protecting against disease. Vitamins can be found in a variety of foods, including animal products and berries.
	In addition to providing your pawns with the nutrients they need, it is also important to provide them with a variety of food. Pawns will not be happy if they are only ever given rice to eat. A mod has added a new need called "Food Variety," and to keep this need high, you should provide your pawns with different meals made from different ingredients.
    </description> <!-- Be Creative The description is what people will see when they look at your mod -->
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.4</li>
    </supportedVersions> <!-- This is the version of Rimworld that the mod is compatible with -->
    <modDependencies>
      <li>
        <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
        <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      </li>
    </modDependencies>
</ModMetaData> <!-- be sure to close all tags you open -->