<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

<!-- 141 -->

	<RH_OFOFriendlyText_Label>Radio Message</RH_OFOFriendlyText_Label>
	<RH_OFOFriendly_Text>Task Force 141 enters your line of communications.
	
"How'd muppets like you pass selection.. ? 

This is Bravo Six, we hear you boys are popping by. We will look out for you until you give us reasons not to. 

Bravo Six out."
	
The call ends. Task Force 141 is now your ally.</RH_OFOFriendly_Text>

<!-- The Ghosts -->

	<RH_GhostsFriendlyText_Label>Radio Message</RH_GhostsFriendlyText_Label>
	<RH_GhostsFriendly_Text>The Ghosts enter your line of communications.
	
"Delta huh? We're Ghosts. We're here if you need us brother, we've got our own problems to deal with but you're not alone out here. 

Drop by our outposts anytime for resupply, we'll give you discounts.

Stay safe out there, over and out."
	
The call ends. The Ghosts have acknowledged you as allies.</RH_GhostsFriendly_Text>

<!-- Cordis Die-->

	<RH_CordisDieHostilityText_Label>Radio Message</RH_CordisDieHostilityText_Label>
	<RH_CordisDieHostility_Text>A male gruff voice with a thick spanish accent speaks to you over the radio.
	
"Opulence is sinful and we all pay for it... She was taken from me. Do you know what that feels like yet?

An insurance scammer torched our warehouse for money. 11,000 dollars, that was the value they placed on her life. 

She was the reason for me to live.

What about you? What drives you? Is it us?... 

Einstein once said the economic anarchy of capitalism is the real source of evil. Your idealogy, and it's people, took Josefina from me. 

Pues... Tú y tus amigos pronto estaréis muertos."

The call ends. It seems you have a powerful enemy.</RH_CordisDieHostility_Text>

<!-- MSF -->

	<RH_MSFNeutrality_Label>Radio Message</RH_MSFNeutrality_Label>
	<RH_MSFNeutrality_Text>A male gravelly voice speaks to you over the radio.
	
"We forsook our countries. We left our motherlands behind us and became one with this earth.

We have no nation, no philosophy, no ideology. We go where we're needed, fighting, not for government, but for ourselves. 

We need no reason to fight. We fight because we are needed. We will be the deterrent for those with no other recourse. 

We are soldiers without borders, our purpose defined by the era we live in.

We will sometimes have to sell ourselves and services. If the times demand it, we'll be revolutionaries, criminals, terrorists. And yes, we may all be headed straight to hell. But what better place for us than this? It's our only home. Our heaven and our hell. 

This is Outer Heaven."

The call ends. Militaires Sans Frontières has been hired against you.</RH_MSFNeutrality_Text>

	<!-- Make sure to change the keys if using this mod for different factions. -->
	<USASOC_startLetterLabelKey>care package</USASOC_startLetterLabelKey> <!-- title of the letter sent the first time provisions arrive -->
	<USASOC_startLetterTextKey>Command has sent you a care package containing valuable supplies. You will receive a care package every 3 days.</USASOC_startLetterTextKey> <!-- text of the letter sent the first time provisions arrive, {0} is automatically replaced with the faction's label (not the player's custom name) -->
	<USASOC_endLetterLabelKey>supplies cut off</USASOC_endLetterLabelKey> <!-- title of the letter sent when no more provisions will arrive -->
	<USASOC_endLetterTextKey>Command presumes your team members have been killed, wounded, captured, or deserted. Care packages have been stopped.

You have been on mission for too long.</USASOC_endLetterTextKey> <!-- text of the letter sent when no more provisions will arrive, {0} is automatically replaced with the faction's label -->
	<USASOC_dropMessageKey>care package has arived</USASOC_dropMessageKey> <!-- {0} is automatically replaced with the faction's label -->
	<USASOC_noDropMessageKey>Something went wrong, your care package failed to deliver</USASOC_noDropMessageKey> <!-- {0} is automatically replaced with the faction's label -->
</LanguageData>