<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>World Map Beautification Project - for Alpha Biomes</name>
  <author>Carolusclen</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
	<li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>Carolusclen.DLC.WMBP</packageId>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>sarg.alphabiomes</packageId>
      <displayName>Alpha Biomes</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/1841354677</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
      <displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AndroidQuazar/VanillaExpandedFramework</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Anomaly</li>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>BiomesTeam.BiomesIslands</li>
    <li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
    <li>sarg.alphabiomes</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>
  
This is a DLC for the mod "World Map Beautification Project" by Odeum.

The DLC adds support for the "Alpha Biomes" mod

[h1] Features [/h1]
- Feralisk Infested Jungle
 - An incredibly thick jungle, completely infested with spiders.
[*] Lush green hills
[*] Thick jungles
- Gallatross Graveyard
 - These parched mudflats are littered with the ancient bones of colossal Gallatrosses.
[*] Sandy windswept mountains
[*] Bone Jungles
- Gelatinous Superorganism
 - A huge mold-like organism has grown in this area, basically destroying the previous existing ecosystem, and replacing it with an alien landscape of its own creation.
[*] Solidified Slime mountains
[*] Strange sticky trees
- Mechanoid Intrusion
 - A mechanoid hive was dismantling this biome, turning its mass into computronium, and hastily left it abandoned for unknown reasons.
[*] Mountains made of machine
[*] Strange looking trees
- Mycotic Jungle
 - The Mycotic Jungle is a super dense overgrowth of massive giant mushrooms, covered in a coat of mycelium.
[*] Fungus covered mountains
[*] Forests of strange mushrooms
- Ocular Forest
 - This sickly looking forest seems to be completely alien, probably of an extra-dimensional origin.
[*] Mountains tinted a strange red
[*] Trees watching your every move
- Propane Lakes
 - Huge liquid propane lakes fill this desolate frozen landscape.
[*] Snapfrozen Mountains topped in thick snow
[*] Strange plants that almost look too fragile to touch
- Pyroclastic Conflagration
 - A desolate expanse of obsidian and solidified lava, with several active calderas bubbling menacingly.
[*] Hot spiked rock
[*] Even hotter trees
- Rocky Crags
 - This desertic landscape appears to be perpetually covered in an unnatural fog that seeps all light from the sun.
[*] Dark spiked rocks, the dull glow of the plant life barely breaks through the fog
[*] Plants that glow (currently not working)
- Tar Pits
 - Sun-baked mud, interspersed with patches of fertile grassy terrain.
[*] Lush green plant-life
- Idyllic Meadows
 - Product of ancient terraforming, these open grasslands were designed to be an utopian paradise: giant flowers provide both construction materials and sustenance, while an abundance of wildlife creates ample ranching and hunting possibilities.
[*] Beautiful flowers everywhere, small as dots and large as trees
- Miasmic Mangrove
 - Mangrove swamps, also known as mangals, are coastal wetlands found in tropical and subtropical regions.
[*] Lush green plant-life in a humid environment


[h1] Credits [/h1]
Odeum for the "World Map Beautification Project" mod
Sarg for the "Alpha Biomes" mod


[h1] Changelog [/h1]
14/06/2024 - 1.11: Incremented the version number to possibly fix a dependency warning when there is no dependency
01/05/2024 - 1.10: Fixed the Integration. Regrowth Core is not required, however will not conflict if added now
25/04/2024 - 1.9: Intigrated World Map Beautification Project dependancy to prevent the need to a separate mod
14/04/2024 - 1.8: Fixed a forest density issue
12/04/2024 - 1.7: Updated to support Rimworld 1.5 Anomaly Expansion
22/10/2022 - 1.6: Updated to support Rimworld 1.4 Biotech Expansion
28/06/2022 - 1.5: Added 2 new Biomes
21/01/2022 - 1.4: Fixed missing texture
9/11/2021 - 1.3:
[*] Added extra images.
[*] Added missing biome info
[*] Removed Preview images from mod to reduce space
22/08/2021 - 1.2: Corrected mod ID
22/08/2021 - 1.1: Update to 1.3
01/02/2021 - 1.0: Initial Release



  
  </description>
</ModMetaData>