<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Combat Update 1.4</name>
  <author>DaLLaN</author>
  	<packageId>Daniledman.CombatUpdate</packageId>
  <url>http://rimworldgame.com</url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.0</li>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
  <description>
You’re tired of the fact that your hunter with a high shooting skill can’t get into a deer with 5 cages, and the shooters with a low shooting skill do the whole turn out of the machine gun literally around the target, but not at the target itself, while standing a stone's throw from it ? Or did you notice that the installation of expensive prostheses and a significant increase in long-range and close combat skills have almost no effect? It seems strange to you that the speed of reloading weapons and the speed of aiming does not depend on anything? Then this mod is for you! It significantly increases the accuracy of firing of any ranged weapons, making the battles more transient and spectacular.

ATTENTION!!! - The mod does not require the start of a new game. Mod Combat Update is compatible with mods for new weapons. Any weapon will receive an increase in the chance of hitting and other bonuses from the mod. No additional compatibility patches are required.
ATTENTION x2 !!! - the mod affects not only the weapon and the player’s colonists, the enemy also began to shoot more accurately. Be prepared for more frequent injuries to your colonists in hassles.

What changes this small mod:

-Changes in the curve of calculating the chance of hitting a target depending on distance - the ranged skill better affects the chance, while the minimum threshold of accuracy is increased, which means that even colonists with zero shooting skills will hit the target more often, and colonists with high shooting skills and steep prostheses will become skillful arrows at all. At the same time, the maximum threshold for the dependence of the chance of getting on vision / work was increased from 200% / 150% to 300% / 300%. This means that fully equipping a colonist with good prostheses will have a stronger effect on his accuracy. It may even happen that with a distance the chance of hitting will not decrease, but here we must try to equip the colonist with everything necessary.

-The accuracy of all weapons is increased by 25% from the base chance when shooting close, at medium and long range (4-60 cells) and by 50% when shooting point-blank (1-3 cells). Now even the most krivoruky shooter will not constantly hit the target from a distance of 2-3 cells, but it looks very funny.

-The effect of weather on the chance of hitting is reduced by 50%. Now in rain, blizzard or fog, the overall chance of falling is not reduced as much as it was without the mod.

-The duration of reloading weapons now depends on the quality of the weapon. A better barrel reloads faster.
Cooldown is now multiplied by a factor: 1.1-0.75 (1.1 for terrible quality, 0.75 for legendary).

-Duration of aiming now also depends on the skill of the shooter. Aiming duration is now multiplied by a factor: 1.15-0.6 (1.15 - with the "Ranged - 0" skill; 0.6 - with the "Ranged - 20" skill).

I did not forget about long-range combat. It is worth considering that increasing the accuracy of ranged weapons will complicate the life of melee fighters. But this is not inevitable. Because melee also received improvements:

-Base melee chance increased and now more dependent on melee skills and prostheses. At the same time, the maximum threshold for the dependence of the chance of getting on vision / work was increased from 200% / 150% to 300% / 300%. This means that fully equipping a colonist with good prostheses will have a stronger effect on his accuracy in close combat.

- The chance of dodging in close combat has grown significantly and is more dependent on the skill of close combat and the beginnings of good prosthesis for the colonist. Now with a high melee skill and a set of archo-prostheses (or other strong prostheses from mods), you can achieve a 80% chance of dodging. The maximum threshold for the dependence of the chance of hitting from vision has been increased from 150% to 300%.

Мод значительно улучшает механику стрельбы, делая попадания успешными гораздо чаще.

  </description>
</ModMetaData>