<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
<name>Prayer Spots</name>
<author>LWM</author>
<packageId>LWM.PrayerSpots</packageId>
<supportedVersions>
  <li>1.0</li>
  <li>1.1</li>
</supportedVersions>
<modDependencies>
  <li>
    <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
    <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
    <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl> 
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
  </li>
</modDependencies>
<description>Place one or more prayer spots in your colony to direct pawns where to pray.

Pawns will, when they pray, pick a prayer spot instead of only going to their room (they will sometimes still go to their room.)

Note:  This mod does not add any prayer buildings of any sort.  However, if you have shrines/etc from other mods, this should allow you to specify where the pawns pray.

Uses:
 * Make pews for your church!
 * Pray at family shrines in your room!  (I think some japanese-themed mods add them as basic furniture?)
 * You can put prayer spots *anywhere*.  Don't be stupid.
 ** (except on geothermal vents - haven't figured that out yet)
 * Hey, if you want your faithful going into the ocean to worship Dagan, this mod lets you do it!
 
Future plans:
 * Meditation Spots
 * Allow meditating and praying in any spot
 * "temple"/"chapel"/"better name?" room designation
 * Mood boost from praying/meditating in a nice area
 * Mod Option to delete all prayer spots on the map (in case you lost a few under mountains or something?)
 * Mod Options to turn off any functionality? (probably via HugsLib)
 ** Disallow praying in rooms, so everyone goes to church to pray!

License: LGPL

GitHub: https://github.com/lilwhitemouse/RimWorld-PrayerSpot
 
Thanks to TOGFox for some initial work (which wasn't used in the end) and for some initial prodding (which was very useful) and support.
</description>
<url>https://github.com/lilwhitemouse/RimWorld-PrayerSpot</url>
</ModMetaData>
