<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Gotobarn</name>
  <packageId>Guezzy.Gotobarn</packageId>
  <author>busted_bunny</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/RecycleThis</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>
English :

The GotoBarn mod is a RimWorld modification that significantly improves animal behavior regarding temperature management. Unlike the vanilla game where animals only react to extreme temperature conditions when they're already suffering, this mod makes animals much more proactive in seeking comfortable temperatures. Animals will now actively look for shelter as soon as the temperature falls outside their comfort range, preventing them from reaching dangerous health conditions. This modification of the JobGiver_SeekSafeTemperature class ensures that animals will either wait in a safe temperature zone or move to a suitable location before they start suffering from temperature-related issues, making them more intelligent and self-preserving.

French :

Le mod GotoBarn est une modification pour RimWorld qui améliore considérablement le comportement des animaux concernant la gestion de la température. Contrairement au jeu de base où les animaux ne réagissent aux conditions de température extrêmes que lorsqu'ils souffrent déjà, ce mod rend les animaux beaucoup plus proactifs dans leur recherche de températures confortables. Les animaux chercheront maintenant activement un abri dès que la température sort de leur zone de confort, les empêchant d'atteindre des conditions de santé dangereuses. Cette modification de la classe JobGiver_SeekSafeTemperature assure que les animaux attendront dans une zone à température sécuritaire ou se déplaceront vers un endroit approprié avant de commencer à souffrir de problèmes liés à la température, les rendant plus intelligents et plus soucieux de leur préservation.
  
  
  
  
  </description>
  <modVersion IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">1.5.9</modVersion>
  
</ModMetaData>