<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Ben Lubar's Vanilla Expanded Patches</name>
	<author>Ben Lubar</author>
	<packageId>me.lubar.VanillaExpandedPatches</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>
		<![CDATA[A collection of small patches and quality of life changes for the Vanilla Expanded series and related mods.

Patches that apply to mods that are not installed are simply not applied; there is no need to install all of Vanilla Expanded to use this mod.

XML patches (X) are always active; Harmony patches (H) can be toggled in the settings.

Vanilla Expanded Framework

- (H) Item processors (wine barrels, etc.) that only accept one type of item no longer require that item to be on the map.

Vanilla Furniture Expanded - Security

- (X) Short wall has been moved to the Security tab (from the Structure tab).

Vanilla Furniture Expanded - Farming

- (H) Crops that can never be grown in planter boxes due to fertility are no longer shown as options.

Vanilla Furniture Expanded - Production

- (X) Assembly Bench can now use the syntheline recipes added by Dubs Rimefeller.

Vanilla Furniture Expanded - Art

- (X) Rugs are now a medieval technology (rather than Industrial).

Vanilla Weapons Expanded

- (H) Pawns incapable of violence can equip "tool" weapons added by this mod.
- To make pawns use fire extinguishers to extinguish fires, see https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2397915519

Vanilla Apparel Expanded

- (X) Apparel that only covers the neck (cape, scarf) is no longer considered clothing for nudity.
- (X) Glasses (glasses, sunglasses) are no longer considered clothing for nudity.
- (X) Hats that do not fully obscure the hair (fedora, summer hat, military beret, hard hat, baseball cap, chef's toque) are no longer considered clothing for nudity.
- (X) If both this mod and Ideology are installed, the "Pants At Most" precept for nudity is allowed for tribal faction ideoligions.

Vanilla Fishing Expanded

- (X) Fishing is not a violent work type (since slaughtering animals isn't violent, fishing isn't either).
- (H) Fishing zones show the number of cells they contain so you don't have to count.
- (X) Tackle boxes can now be made with leather-like materials, such as synthamide from Dubs Rimefeller and cosmic weave from Science Never Stops, not just animal leather.

Vanilla Cooking Expanded

- (X) If Vanilla Plants Expanded is not installed, makes it so canned fruit can still be stored and used.
- (X) Canned fish no longer counts as a non-fish meat type.
- (X) The "negligible (no effect)" stages of diabetes, high cholesterol, and high blood pressure are no longer displayed on the health tab.
- (X) If Android Tiers is installed, smokeleaf butter and cheese can be made from nutrient solution.
- (X) Canned goods are in the "desperate only" category (like fertilized eggs and some drugs), not the "meal bad" category (like nutrient paste).

Vanilla Factions Expanded - Medieval

- (X) Low rock wall has been moved to the Security tab (from the Structure tab).
- (X) Archery targets can be built by factions even if they are above the Medieval tech level.
- To make antiseptic smell unable to kill pawns on its own, see https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2639653385

Vanilla Factions Expanded - Insectoids

- (X) Royal insect jelly is no longer enabled by default as an ingredient for cooking.
- (H) Refugees in quests added by Royalty no longer spawn with royal jelly addictions.
- (H) The bio-engineering incubator now shows a preview of the insect that will be created by the specified options.
- (H) Ores mined by non-humans are no longer forbidden.

Vanilla Cooking Expanded - Sushi

- (X) Wasabi can be grown in hydroponics. The growth penalty from not having enough nearby natural water still applies.

Vanilla Brewing Expanded

- (X) Bar can now produce wort in addition to the alcohol precursor items added by this mod.

Vanilla Books Expanded

- This mod does not touch VBE. See https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2650429441 instead.

Vanilla Brewing Expanded - Coffees and Teas

- (X) If Android Tiers is installed, latte and black tea can be made from nutrient solution.
- (H) Lemons that drop off of lemon trees in the home area are automatically unforbidden.

Vanilla Factions Expanded - Mechanoids

- (H) Ores mined by non-humans are no longer forbidden.

Vanilla Apparel Expanded - Accessories

- (X) Quivers can now be made from leather-like materials, such as synthamide from Dubs Rimefeller and cosmic weave from Science Never Stops, not just animal leather.

Vanilla Factions Expanded - Ancients

- (X) If Dubs Bad Hygiene is installed, ancient water purifiers work like Save Our Ship 2 life support systems.

VFME - Simple Tofu

- (H) Tofu no longer counts as meat when deciding the food type of a meal.
]]></description>
	<url>https://git.lubar.me/rimworld-mods/vanilla-expanded-patches</url>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</packageId>
			<displayName>HugsLib</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/UnlimitedHugs/RimworldHugsLib/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VFESecurity</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VFEFarming</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VFEProduction</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VFEArt</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VWE</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VAPPE</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VCEF</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VCookE</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.MedievalModule</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VFE.Insectoid</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VCookESushi</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VBrewE</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VBrewECandT</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VFE.Mechanoid</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VAEAccessories</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VFEA</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
