<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

<ScenarioDef>
    <defName>SkeletonDrifter</defName>
	<label>Embarking 'Skeleton'</label>
	<scenario>
		<name>'Skeleton' Drifter</name>
		<description>You are what is often called a 'skeleton', a crude ancient precursor to the now far more advanced robotics of the modern age. You've spent years drifting through the stars, but now you've found yourself effectively stranded on this Rimworld with no easy way off. Whether you seize this chance to settle down, lead a nation, or become a mechanical tyrant, it is your choice.\n\nSkeletons have no need for food or sleep - but they are astonishingly rare, socially inept, mentally unstable, and mechanical.</description>
		<summary>A single 'skeleton' decides to embark on a new adventure. Very difficult.</summary>
		<playerFaction>
			<def>PlayerFaction</def>
			<factionDef>PlayerColonySkeleton</factionDef>
		</playerFaction>
			<parts>
				<li Class="ScenPart_ConfigPage_ConfigureStartingPawns">
					<def>ConfigPage_ConfigureStartingPawns</def>
					<pawnCount>1</pawnCount>
					<pawnChoiceCount>6</pawnChoiceCount>
				</li>
				<li Class="ScenPart_PlayerPawnsArriveMethod">
					<def>PlayerPawnsArriveMethod</def>
			        <method>Standing</method>					
				</li>
				<li Class="ScenPart_GameStartDialog">
					<def>GameStartDialog</def>
					<text>In your vast lifetime you've learned that nothing is permanent - not even you. You now find yourself alone and shunned on this obscure Rimworld without a way back into the stars, and knowing the desultory way of any given planet's inhabitants it may not be safe for a robotic individual like yourself.\n\nIn the time it may take to bide until you can leave the planet you could; start a new empire, found a new ideoligion, wander the world, or lead a peaceful existence.</text>
					<closeSound>GameStartSting</closeSound>
				</li>
				<li Class="ScenPart_ScatterThingsNearPlayerStart">
					<def>ScatterThingsNearPlayerStart</def>
					<thingDef>Steel</thingDef>
					<count>250</count>
				</li>
			</parts>

	</scenario>
</ScenarioDef>
  
</Defs>