<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Warcasket Nonlethal Weaponry</name>
	<author>BrassRobo</author>
    <packageId>BrassRobo.VanillaExpandedUnofficial.WarcasketNonLethal</packageId>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
    </supportedVersions>
	<description>A set of non-lethal weapons for Warcaskets, in case you'd prefer to take your enemies in alive. In general these have slightly higher accuracy, range and rate of fire to make up for only being useable by Warcaskets.

Dart Gun : Like the normal dart gun from Vanilla Expanded: Non-Lethal Weapons. It will knock out enemies after a short while.

Beanbag Thrower: A massive shotgun that fires 4 rubber bullets. Causes bash damage instead of sharp.

Taser Gun: Shoots twin bolts of electricity at a target. Stuns both organic and mechanoid enemies.

Stun Baton: A melee version of the Taser Gun. Has a risk of doing bash damage if you hit with the hilt instead of the head.

If either the Sparkling World Full or Sparkling Worlds Weaponry mods is installed, this mod includes two additional weapons making use of the new damage types introduced in those mods.

Pain Gun: The Glitterworld upgrade of the Taser. Doesn't stun the target but reduces their consciousness with repeated hits.

Pain Baton: A melee version of the Pain Gun.

This mod requires Vanilla Factions Expanded - Pirates to function.

Warcaskets and the original graphics used in this mod were created by the Vanilla Expanded team. The Sparkling Worlds mod was created by Albion.
</description>
	
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>OskarPotocki.VFE.Pirates</packageId>
      <displayName>Vanilla Factions Expanded - Pirates</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2723801948</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
	<li>
      <packageId>VanillaExpanded.VWENL</packageId>
      <displayName>Vanilla Weapons Expanded - Non-Lethal</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2454918354</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>OskarPotocki.VFE.Pirates</li>
	<li>VanillaExpanded.VWENL</li>
	<li>Albion.SparklingWorlds.Full</li>
	<li>Albion.SparklingWorlds.Weapons</li>
  </loadAfter>
	
</ModMetaData>