<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Drakken Laser Drill</name>
  <author>空曜</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <description>本Mod提供一种通过研究科技进行无限升级的巨型激光炮塔：德拉肯激光钻机（科技需求：电力）
This Mod provides a giant laser turret that can be upgraded infinitely through research technology: Drakken Laser Drill (technology need: Electricity)

1.特性：
A.无限射程
B.消耗电量造成伤害（初始：36/秒）【可挖矿】
C.通过研究科技无限升级蓄电量、伤害、护甲穿透
D.通过研究科技解锁2个主动技能（主动技能的充能：攻击时消耗的电量将等额增加主动技能充能）
E.永生程序：耐久归0时不会摧毁，转而进入修复状态，修复状态下无法攻击，耐久满一段时间后重启炮塔
F.可在Mod设置中调整部分数据


1.Characteristic：
A. Infinite range
B. Damage caused by power consumption (initial: 36/s) 【Mineable】
C. Unlimited upgrade of power storage, damage and armor penetration through research technology
D. Unlock 2 active skills through research and technology (charging of active skills: the power consumed during the attack will increase the charging of active skills by an equal amount)
E. Immortality Protocol: when the Hitpoint returns to 0, it will not be destroyed, but will enter the repair state, and cannot be attacked in the repair state. Restart the turret after Hitpoint fixed to Max
F. Some data can be adjusted in Mod settings


2.通过图标进行控制
A.攻击·框选：需要2次点击，第一次点击确定框选起始位置，第二次点击确认框选结束位置，确认完毕后对框选范围内所有建“筑物与生物”进行攻击（优先攻击生物）
B.攻击·所有敌人：点击后自动搜寻当前地图上所有的“敌人”（不会攻击野生动物）
C.自动：开启时，袭击事件发生时将自动攻击敌人（如果敌人通过空投舱抵达，则有10秒延迟）
D.攻击·鼠标位置：【加大输出功率，消耗3倍电力】确认攻击起始位置后，德拉肯激光钻机将跟随鼠标位置发射激光，对周边1格范围内所有物体造成伤害（小心友伤）（再次“左键”点击时：停止攻击。“右键”点击时：请不要这么做，如果点击了右键，则需要通过点击停止按钮来停止攻击）
E.停止：终止攻击动作，无法终止汇聚射线与脉冲炮
F.汇聚射线：【加大输出功率，消耗6倍电力】攻击选定路径上所有的物体（总共造成22倍基础伤害的伤害）（仅不会对己方造成伤害）
G.脉冲炮：【加大输出功率，消耗10倍电力】主激光攻击所选及周边2格位置上的所有物体，汇聚次激光并对行动路径上的敌人造成伤害，最后造成13格范围10倍基础伤害的爆炸（总共造成46倍基础伤害的伤害）
H.伤害控制：手动控制伤害输出量，7-12伤害时每+1伤害将额外增加一根次激光（装饰性）

2. Control by icon
A. Attack · Frame selection: two clicks are required. The first click is to confirm the box to select the starting position, and the second click is to confirm the box to select the ending position. After confirmation, attack all "Buildings and Pawn" within the frame selection range (priority to attack Pawn)
B. Attack · All enemies: click to automatically search all "Enemies" on the current map (wild animals will not be attacked)
C. Auto: When on, the enemy will be attacked automatically when the attack incident (if the enemy arrives through the drop pod , there will be a delay of 10 seconds)
D. Attack · mouse position: 【increase output power and consume 3 times of power】 After confirming the starting position of the attack, the Drakken Laser Drill will follow the mouse position to emit laser, causing damage to all objects within 1 grid around (be careful of friendly injury) (When clicking "left click" again: stop the attack. When clicking "right click": please do not do this. If you click the "right click", you need to click the stop button to stop the attack)
E. Stop: stop the attack action, unable to stop the Concentrated Beam and Pulse Cannon
F. Concentrated Beam: 【increase output power, consume 6 times of power】 attack all objects on the selected path (cause a total of 22 times of basic damage) (only cause no damage to your side)
G. Pulse Cannon: 【increase output power and consume 10 times of power】 The main laser attacks all objects in the selected and surrounding 2 grid positions, converges the secondary laser and causes damage to the enemy on the action path, and finally causes an explosion of 10 times of basic damage within the 13 grid range (46 times of basic damage in total)
H. Damage control: manually control the amount of damage output. For 7-12 damage, an additional secondary laser will be added for each+1 damage (decorative)



3.CE：理论上兼容，但我懒得去研究CE的伤害跟护甲代码，所以伤害以及护甲穿透的调整需要你自己去Mod设置里调整
3. CE: Theoretically compatible, but I'm too lazy to study the damage and armor code of CE, so you need to adjust the damage and armor penetration yourself in Mod settings



Xml + Dll ：空曜
贴图：空曜，TOT


Xml + Dll ：空曜
Texture：空曜，TOT
</description>
  <packageId>MYDE.DrakkenLaserDrill</packageId>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>