<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message1</defName>
		<EmailText>Hello, we are sincerely grateful for your long-term cooperation with us. We hope that our union will last a long time, and will work closely with you hand in hand. May we survive all the hardships, the ups and the losses, we will continue to stick together. We wish you growth and prosperity.
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>Friendly wish</Subject>
		<SenderAvaliable>Ally</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>90</MinRefiredDays>
		<Options>
			<li Class="EmailMessages.EmailMessageOption_GoodLuck"/>
		</Options>
		<Commonality>0.7</Commonality>
		<EarliestDay>44</EarliestDay>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
 
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message2</defName>
		<EmailText>We do not understand why you resist. You are just a miserable bunch of people who are just lucky to survive here and establish a settlement that will be destroyed by us sooner or later. We will not stop making raids on you, and why should we stop, there are a lot of us, but you are few and we will continue to send troops that are stronger than the previous ones until you die, but we can agree. And for the implementation of this contract you need only one condition, give up.
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>Useless Critters</Subject>
		<SenderAvaliable>Hostile</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>85</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.55</Commonality>
		<Options>
			<li Class="EmailMessages.EmailMessageOption_FuckYou">
				<ThreatPointsMultiplier>1.4</ThreatPointsMultiplier>
				<TicksToSend>14000</TicksToSend>
			</li>
		</Options>
		<EarliestDay>35</EarliestDay>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
	
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message3</defName>
		<EmailText>Hello, how are you?
Good, bad, whatever the main thing is that sooner or later you will get worse when you feel all the wrath of our faction, which will soon fall on you and pray better if you survive, and if you stay, you will feel all our pain that YOU brought down on our fighters on daughters and sons who have lost their parents, mothers and fathers who have lost their children because of what they cry at night, we know you do not care and we swear by our lives that we will kill you all and everyone who tries to protect you . We will make you suffer !!!
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>Hour of execution</Subject>
		<SenderAvaliable>Hostile</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>130</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.32</Commonality>
		<MessageWorker Class="EmailMessages.EmailMessageWorker_SendRaid"> 
			<TicksToSend>12000</TicksToSend>
		</MessageWorker>
		<MinReqGoodWill> 
			<min>-100</min>
			<max>-90</max>
		</MinReqGoodWill>
		<EarliestDay>35</EarliestDay>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
	
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message4</defName>
		<EmailText>Your resistance is negligible, it is more like the defense of a half-dead dog. If it were not for your allies, we would not leave a stone unturned from your settlement. Appeared incomprehensibly from where and build themselves from themselves it is unclear what.
We, in contrast to you, are holding back our words. Wait for the guests, sooner or later they will knock on your door, so much so that this will be the last thing you will hear in your worthless life.
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>Nature's mistake</Subject>
		<SenderAvaliable>Hostile</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>150</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.7</Commonality>
		<MinReqGoodWill> 
			<min>-100</min>
			<max>-100</max>
		</MinReqGoodWill>
		<EarliestDay>70</EarliestDay>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
 
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message5</defName>
		<EmailText>Damn bastards, who do you think you are? Do you think that you can resist us with such impunity? Your cheeky antics will soon end. You do not get out of this damned planet, do not even hope, you will stay here forever, die as the last of the creatures and rot on the ruins of his own settlement. This is the best outcome ...
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>Last message</Subject>
		<SenderAvaliable>Hostile</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>55</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.58</Commonality>
		<MinReqGoodWill> 
			<min>-100</min>
			<max>-100</max>
		</MinReqGoodWill>
		<EarliestDay>44</EarliestDay>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
	
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message6</defName>
		<EmailText>What kind of stubborn, idiotic and senseless resistance? Do you understand what you are doing? You directly intend to die with your entire settlement. Are you masochists? Why are you so eager to die? Just surrender, you will not resist us for a long time. Do not want to shame and raise the white flag? Then just disappear, go away, leave your settlement. Your settlement is an ugly pimple on the body of the planet
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>Nothingness</Subject>
		<SenderAvaliable>Hostile</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>160</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.55</Commonality>
		<MinReqGoodWill> 
			<min>-100</min>
			<max>-100</max>
		</MinReqGoodWill>
		<EarliestDay>70</EarliestDay>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
	
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message7</defName>
		<EmailText>Hello, comrades. We very much hope that our joint activities will ensure a bright future for all of us. Protection from enemy harmful effects is a top priority for us, and we are confident that you will help us in case of danger. We do not plan to stop support from our side at the moment. Good luck with your accomplishments. 
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>Primary tasks</Subject>
		<SenderAvaliable>Ally</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>110</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.54</Commonality>
		<EarliestDay>70</EarliestDay>
		<MessageWorker Class="EmailMessages.EmailMessageWorker_SendCaravan"> 
			<Days>2</Days>
			<TotalValue> 
				<min>800</min>
				<max>2000</max>
			</TotalValue>
		</MessageWorker>
		<MinReqGoodWill> 
			<min>50</min>
			<max>100</max>
		</MinReqGoodWill>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
	
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message8</defName>
		<EmailText>Hello, friends. We are glad that our people live in peace and do not try to destroy each other in a variety of sophisticated ways. Establishing relations with you, we hope for your help in case of danger. We advise you to take care of the construction of high-quality fortifications that can protect you from the invading bandits. Peace and prosperity for your colony. 
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>Friendly farewell</Subject>
		<SenderAvaliable>Ally</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>90</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.24</Commonality>
		<EarliestDay>76</EarliestDay>
		<MessageWorker Class="EmailMessages.EmailMessageWorker_SendCaravan"> 
			<Days>3</Days>
			<TotalValue> 
				<min>1200</min>
				<max>2000</max>
			</TotalValue>
		</MessageWorker>
		<MinReqGoodWill> 
			<min>50</min>
			<max>100</max>
		</MinReqGoodWill>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
 
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message9</defName>
		<EmailText>Good day, fiends. Your idiotic insistence and unwillingness to surrender makes us think of your mental inferiority. Sooner or later we will be able to break the will of your people, and they will finally understand that living under your flag is a bad idea. Soon our troops will come for you and do with you many wonderful things: shooting, hanging, quartering, burning. The great thing is that our life machines will be able to keep you alive until the very end.
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>We are your death</Subject>
		<SenderAvaliable>Hostile</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>99</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.45</Commonality>
		<EarliestDay>75</EarliestDay>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
	
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message10</defName>
		<EmailText>I look forward to saying that an explosive device has been installed in your settlement. I installed it also in other places, but you don’t need to know about it. Time is short, so I advise you to evacuate. Think carefully before you ignore my message, because you may suffer. Previous recipients were pleased with my gift ...
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>Bomb</Subject>
		<Options>
			<li Class="EmailMessages.EmailMessageOption_NiceJoke" />
		</Options>
		<SenderAvaliable>Neutral</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>200</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.65</Commonality>
		<EarliestDay>100</EarliestDay>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
	
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message11</defName>
		<EmailText>Good afternoon, although for you he is no longer so kind. Do not philosophize. In one of the rooms in your settlement, we laid an explosive device. It is odorless, which means your animals will not be able to detect it. The timer was activated as soon as you opened the letter. The bomb was laid a few days before, and we can activate it at any time. Good luck, your beloved neighbors.
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>Explosive device</Subject>
		<SenderAvaliable>Neutral</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>200</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.23</Commonality>
		<EarliestDay>140</EarliestDay>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
	
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message12</defName>
		<EmailText>Since your settlement appeared here recently, we must inform you about the mandatory registration in the area of our influence. Our faction will not touch you if you regularly pay 30% of your income monthly. In case of disobedience, I will be forced to inform you about the beginning of the war between us.
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>Monthly payments</Subject>
		<SenderAvaliable>Neutral</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>500</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.44</Commonality>
		<EarliestDay>20</EarliestDay>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
	
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message13</defName>
		<EmailText>The caravan of our faction took place not far from your settlement and did нnot return. We require an explanation and compensation. As I know, the caravan transported the blueprints. If you do not return them back, I will have to start the bombardment from the satellite above you. I hope you make the right decision.
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>Lost caravan</Subject>
		<Options>
			<li Class="EmailMessages.EmailMessageOption_Wtf" />
			<li Class="EmailMessages.EmailMessageOption_NiceCaravan" />
		</Options>
		<SenderAvaliable>Ally</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>200</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.77</Commonality>
		<EarliestDay>180</EarliestDay>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
	
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message14</defName>
		<EmailText>Greetings, {0}! How are you with the weather?
This is the third day {2} here in {1}.
Recently, the weather is very strange.
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>Weather</Subject>
		<MessageWorker Class="EmailMessages.EmailMessageWorker_Weather" />
		<SenderAvaliable>Ally</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>56</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.87</Commonality>
		<EarliestDay>15</EarliestDay>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
	
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message15</defName>
		<EmailText>Two mechanoids are riding in the Utopian world elevator, the first says:
“Your laces are loose!”
And the second answers:
- 100101011.1
Ah ha ha ha ha! Well, isn’t it funny? Well, scream!
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>Joke</Subject>
		<Options>
			<li Class="EmailMessages.EmailMessageOption_GoodJoke" />
			<li Class="EmailMessages.EmailMessageOption_BadJoke" />
		</Options>
		<SenderAvaliable>Ally</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>56</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.87</Commonality>
		<EarliestDay>15</EarliestDay>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
 
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message16</defName>
		<EmailText>Hello! Last night we saw strange lights in the sky above your settlement.
Our onlookers ran out to watch, but suddenly there was such a roar that everyone with fright hid around their homes.
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>Lights in the sky</Subject>
		<MessageWorker Class="EmailMessages.EmailMessageWorker_SpaceBattle" />
		<SenderAvaliable>Ally</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>76</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.4</Commonality>
		<EarliestDay>55</EarliestDay>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
 
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message17</defName>
		<EmailText>Do you think you have any chances? Yes, your {0} is just a miserable worm,
a {1} - generally a bag of bones! How can you even confront us?.
		</EmailText>
		<Subject>Threat</Subject>
		<Options>
			<li Class="EmailMessages.EmailMessageOption_WellOk" />
			<li Class="EmailMessages.EmailMessageOption_JustGetABullet" />
		</Options>
		<MessageWorker Class="EmailMessages.EmailMessageWorker_Threat" />
		<SenderAvaliable>Hostile</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>100</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.22</Commonality>
		<EarliestDay>90</EarliestDay>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
 
	<EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
		<defName>Message18</defName>
		<EmailText>10010110110111000010110010110111011010111010101101010010101001010010101010010101010010100010100</EmailText>
		<Subject>110110110</Subject>
		<Options>
			<li Class="EmailMessages.EmailOptionWorker_RandomComb1" />
			<li Class="EmailMessages.EmailOptionWorker_RandomComb1" />
			<li Class="EmailMessages.EmailOptionWorker_RandomComb1" />
			<li Class="EmailMessages.EmailOptionWorker_RandomComb1" />
		</Options>
		<SenderAvaliable>Hostile</SenderAvaliable>
		<MinRefiredDays>165</MinRefiredDays>
		<Commonality>0.1</Commonality>
		<EarliestDay>125</EarliestDay>
		<StaticFaction>Mechanoid</StaticFaction>
	</EmailMessages.EmailMessageDef>
	
</Defs>