<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>

    <HediffDef>
        <defName>GeneSeedMutated</defName>
        <hediffClass>GeneSeed.GeneSeedMutationHediffWithComps</hediffClass>
        <label>Gene Seed Alterations</label>
        <description>Gene Seed Alterations</description>
        <defaultLabelColor>(0.5, 0.7, 0.45)</defaultLabelColor>
        <makesSickThought>false</makesSickThought>
        <initialSeverity>0.1</initialSeverity>
        <maxSeverity>1</maxSeverity>
        <tendable>false</tendable>
        <isBad>false</isBad>
        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>2</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <comps>
            <li Class="HediffCompProperties_SeverityPerDay">
                <severityPerDay>-0.005</severityPerDay>
            </li>
        </comps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <becomeVisible>false</becomeVisible>
                <label>Neophyte</label>
                <painOffset>-0.0015</painOffset>
                <capMods>
                    <li>
                        <capacity>Breathing</capacity>
                        <offset>0.000</offset>
                    </li>
                </capMods>
            </li>
            <li>
                <becomeVisible>false</becomeVisible>
                <label>Astartes</label>
                <minSeverity>0.301</minSeverity>
                <painOffset>-0.0025</painOffset>
                <capMods>
                    <li>
                        <capacity>Breathing</capacity>
                        <offset>0.00</offset>
                    </li>
                </capMods>
            </li>
            <li>
                <becomeVisible>false</becomeVisible>
                <label>Praetorate</label>
                <minSeverity>0.601</minSeverity>
                <painOffset>-0.009</painOffset>
                <capMods>
                    <li>
                        <capacity>Breathing</capacity>
                        <offset>0.00</offset>
                    </li>
                </capMods>
            </li>
            <li>
                <becomeVisible>false</becomeVisible>
                <label>Primarch</label>
                <minSeverity>0.951</minSeverity>
                <painOffset>-0.01</painOffset>
                <statOffsets>
                    <Beauty>20</Beauty>
                    <Cleanliness>1</Cleanliness>
                    <SocialImpact>0.02</SocialImpact>
                    <CarryingCapacity>1.7</CarryingCapacity>
                    <MeatAmount>1.1</MeatAmount>
                    <ForagedNutritionPerDay>0.01</ForagedNutritionPerDay>
                    <Mass>1.1</Mass>
                </statOffsets>
                <capMods>
                    <li>
                        <capacity>Breathing</capacity>
                        <offset>0.0</offset>
                    </li>
                </capMods>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>

    <RecipeDef Name="AwesomeOrgans" Abstract="True">
        <defaultLabelColor>(0,195,230)</defaultLabelColor>
        <hediffClass>GeneSeed.GeneSeedMutationHediffWithComps</hediffClass>
        <tendable>false</tendable>
        <isBad>false</isBad>
    </RecipeDef>


    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_SecondaryHeart</defName>
        <label>Secondary Heart</label>
        <description>The Secondary Heart, also called the Maintainer, is the first and least difficult of the 19
            Astartes gene-seed organ implants a Space Marine Neophyte receives to transform him into a full Astartes. It
            resembles a smaller version of the human heart and is implanted in the chest cavity and connected to the
            rest of the Neophyte's circulatory and pulmonary systems near the original heart. Its function is to enhance
            the performance of an Astartes by supplying more oxygen and nutrients to the muscles by increasing blood
            flow well-beyond that capable for even the most fit normal human being. The Secondary Heart can often save
            an Astartes' life in combat. In the event of combat damage to or failure of the Space Marine's original
            heart, the Secondary Heart is usually capable of pumping enough blood through the Astartes' circulatory
            system to maintain survival until he can be treated by the Chapter's Apothecaries.</description>
        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <capMods>
                    <li>
                        <capacity>BloodPumping</capacity>
                        <offset>1</offset>
                    </li>
                </capMods>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>

    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_Ossmodula</defName>
        <label>Ossmodula</label>
        <description>The Ossmodula, also called the Ironheart, is the second of the 19 gene-seed organs implanted into a Space Marine Neophyte during the induction process to create a new Astartes. This implant, surgically placed alongside the Neophyte's pituitary gland at the base of the brain, thus becoming a part of the Space Marine's endocrine system, secretes a specially engineered form of human growth hormone. When the effects of this hormone are combined with a diet laced with microscopic ceramic-based minerals, they act to catalyse the rapid growth of an Astartes' skeletomuscular system which results in an Astartes' superhuman strength and massive size compared to a baseline human male.</description>
        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <statOffsets>
                    <CarryingCapacity>400</CarryingCapacity>
                    <Mass>100</Mass>
                </statOffsets>
                <capMods>
                    <li>
                        <capacity>Moving</capacity>
                        <offset>0.25</offset>
                    </li>
                </capMods>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>


    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <ignoreConfigErrors>true</ignoreConfigErrors><!--Immune to something unexpected-->
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_Biscopea</defName>
        <label>Biscopea</label>
        <description>The Biscopea, also called the Forge of Strength, is the 3rd of the 19 gene-seed organs implanted
            into a Neophyte Space Marine during the induction process to create a new Astartes. This organ enhances a
            Space Marine's physical combat ability and survivability to superhuman levels should he live to become a
            full Astartes of a Space Marine Chapter. When implanted into the chest cavity, usually at the same time as
            the Ossmodula is implanted at the base of the brain, this small, spherical implant bolsters skeletomuscular
            development and density throughout the Space Marine's body and regulates the Ossmodula's synthetic human
            growth hormone secretion levels. This initiates a growth process that ultimately causes the adolescent human
            male implanted with the organ to reach the massive height and gain the superhuman strength and muscle
            density of the Astartes. As noted above, the Biscopea is commonly implanted at the same time as the
            Ossmodula since it is necessary to successfully regulate the Ossmodula's hormonal secretions and it will
            also regulate the hormonal changes caused to the new Astartes' body by many of the other gene-seed implants.</description>
        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <statOffsets>
                    <CarryingCapacity>400</CarryingCapacity>
                    <Mass>100</Mass>
                </statOffsets>
                <capMods>
                    <li>
                        <capacity>Moving</capacity>
                        <offset>0.25</offset>
                    </li>
                </capMods>
                <makeImmuneTo>
                    <li>Frail</li>
                    <li>BadBack</li>
                </makeImmuneTo>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>

    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_Haemastamen</defName>
        <label>Haemastamen</label>
        <description>The Haemastamen, also known as the Blood Maker, is the 4th of the 19 gene-seed organs that are
            implanted into a Space Marine Neophyte to produce a new Astartes. Once implanted into a main blood vessel
            like the aorta, femoral artery or the vena cava, the Haemastamen alters an Astartes' blood's biochemical
            composition to carry oxygen and nutrients more efficiently. The actions of the Haemastamen turn a Space
            Marine's blood a brighter shade of red than that of normal humans because of its greatly increased
            oxygen-carrying capacity. It also acts to biochemically regulate the actions of the 2nd and 3rd gene-seed
            implants, the Ossmodula and Biscopea.</description>
        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <capMods>
                    <li>
                        <capacity>BloodPumping</capacity>
                        <offset>1</offset>
                    </li>
                </capMods>
                <makeImmuneTo>
                    <li>HeartArteryBlockage</li>
                </makeImmuneTo>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>



    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_LarramansOrgan</defName>
        <label>Larraman's Organ</label>
        <description>Larraman's Organ, also called the Healer, is the 5th of the 19 gene-seed organs that are implanted
            into a Space Marine Neophyte to produce a new Astartes. Shaped like the human liver but only the size of a
            golf ball, this gene-seed organ is placed within the chest cavity and manufactures the synthetic biological
            cells known as Larraman Cells that were named after one of the researchers in the Emperor of Mankind's
            gene-laboratories on Terra where the gene-seed for the first Space Marines was created under the Emperor's
            direction from His Primarchs' DNA. These biosynthetic cells serve the same physiological purpose for an
            Astartes as the normal human body's platelets, serving to clot the blood lost from wounds, but act faster,
            more efficiently and more effectively. When a Space Marine is wounded and incurs blood loss, Larraman Cells
            are released by his circulatory system, attached to the body's normal leukocytes (white blood cells). At the
            site of the injury, they form scar tissue in a matter of seconds, effectively preventing massive blood loss
            and infection of the wound. The action of this organ is one of the reasons that the Space Marines are seen
            as nearly invincible and so difficult to kill despite the terrible wounds they sometimes endure.</description>
        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <statOffsets>
                    <ImmunityGainSpeed>0.25</ImmunityGainSpeed>
                </statOffsets>
                <makeImmuneTo>
                    <li>MuscleParasites</li>
                    <li>FibrousMechanites</li>
                    <li>SensoryMechanites</li>
                    <li>Flu</li>
                </makeImmuneTo>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>




    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_Catalepsean</defName>
        <label>Catalepsean Node</label>
        <description>The Catalepsean Node, also called the Unsleeping, is the 6th of the 19 gene-seed organs that are
            implanted into a Space Marine Neophyte to produce a new Astartes. This organ is implanted into the back of
            the cerebrum, just above the brain stem. When deprived of sleep for a long period of time, the Catalepsean
            Node "cuts in" upon detecting a rise in the Astartes' stress and fatigue hormones. This allows the Astartes
            to consciously "switch off" sections of the brain sequentially, while remaining awake and alert. This
            ability comes at a price, as prolonged use of this ability can be hazardous, possibly inducing
            hallucinations or even psychosis. This implant bears a resemblance to an ancient scientific theory as to how
            cetaceans known as "Bottlenose Dolphins" "sleep": shutting off sections of their brain while remaining awake
            and alert through the active use of the other sections. Yet even the mighty Space Marines cannot go too long
            without actual rest. The longest any Space Marine has ever been on active combat duty without rest is 328
            solar hours, achieved by a squad of the Crimson Fists' Kill-team during the battle against the Orks for
            Rynn's World.</description>
        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <statOffsets>
                    <PsychicSensitivity>0.25</PsychicSensitivity>
                </statOffsets>
                <restFallFactor>0.20</restFallFactor>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>


    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <ignoreConfigErrors>true</ignoreConfigErrors><!--Immune to something unexpected-->
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_Preomnor</defName>
        <label>Preomnor</label>
        <description>The Preomnor, also called the Neutraliser, is the 7th of the 19 gene-seed organs that are implanted
            into a Space Marine Neophyte to produce a new Astartes. The Preomnor is essentially a second or
            "pre-stomach" spliced into the human digestive system above the original stomach that allows Space Marines
            to eat otherwise poisonous or completely indigestible materials. The Preomnor is capable of biochemically
            analysing ingested materials and neutralizing most known biochemical and inorganic toxins, and many others
            that remain unknown save for their toxic effects. Deadly poisons are either neutralised or isolated from the
            digestive tract by the Preomnor. The Preomnor can also be isolated from the rest of the digestive tract to
            deal with particularly toxic substances that a Space Marine may simply vomit back up later. Often these
            extracted toxins are rerouted and then molecularly stored in the Betcher's Gland for future usage by the
            Astartes.</description>

        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <hungerRateFactor>0.20</hungerRateFactor>
                <capMods>
                    <li>
                        <capacity>Metabolism</capacity>
                        <offset>1.0</offset>
                    </li>
                </capMods>
                <statOffsets>
                    <FoodPoisonChance>-100</FoodPoisonChance>
                </statOffsets>
                <makeImmuneTo>
                    <li>GutWorms</li>
                    <li>Blindness</li>
                </makeImmuneTo>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>

    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_Omophagea</defName>
        <label>Omophagea</label>
        <description>The Omophagea, also called the Remembrancer, is the 8th of the 19 genetically-engineered gene-seed
            organs that are implanted into a Space Marine Neophyte to produce a new superhuman Astartes. The Omophagea
            is implanted into the spinal cord and then wired into the central nervous system so that it is directly
            attached to the cerebral cortex and to the stomach. It allows the Astartes to gain part of an individual
            person's or creature's memory by eating its flesh. This special organ is implanted between the thoracic
            vertebrae and the stomach wall and is designed to absorb information and any DNA, RNA or protein sequences
            related to experience or memory. This implant thus allows a Space Marine to literally "learn by eating."
            Four new nerve bundles are also implanted connecting the spine and the stomach wall. The Omophagea transmits
            the gained information to the Astartes' brain as a set of memories or experiences. This enables the Space
            Marine to gain information, in a survival or tactical sense, simply by eating an animal indigenous to an
            alien world and then experiencing some of what that creature did before its death. It is the presence of
            this organ that is responsible for the various flesh-eating and blood-drinking rituals for which certain
            Space Marine Chapters are famous, as well as giving names to Chapters such as the Blood Drinkers and Flesh
            Tearers. Over time, mutations in this implant's gene-seed have given some Chapters an unnatural craving for
            blood or flesh.</description>
        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <statOffsets>
                    <GlobalLearningFactor>0.50</GlobalLearningFactor>
                    <ResearchSpeed>0.50</ResearchSpeed>
                    <PsychicSensitivity>-0.25</PsychicSensitivity>
                </statOffsets>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>

    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_MultiLung</defName>
        <label>Multi-Lung</label>
        <description>The Multi-lung, also called the Imbiber, is the 9th of the 19 genetically engineered
            gene-seed organs that are implanted into a Space Marine Neophyte to produce a new Astartes. The Multi-lung
            is a third lung implanted into an Astartes' pulmonary and circulatory systems in the chest cavity that is
            able to absorb oxygen from environments usually too poor in oxygen to allow normal human respiratory
            functioning. Breathing is accomplished through a sphincter implanted into the trachea, allowing all three
            lungs to be used at full capacity. In toxic environments, a similar muscle closes off the normal lungs, thus
            oxygen is absorbed exclusively by the Multi-lung, which then filters out the poisonous or toxic elements.
            The Multi-lung has highly efficient toxin dispersal systems.</description>
        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <capMods>
                    <li>
                        <capacity>Breathing</capacity>
                        <offset>0.5</offset>
                    </li>
                </capMods>
                <makeImmuneTo>
                    <li>Asthma</li>
                </makeImmuneTo>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>
    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <ignoreConfigErrors>true</ignoreConfigErrors><!--Immune to something unexpected-->
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_Occulobe</defName>
        <label>Occulobe Augmentation</label>
        <description>The Occulobe, also called the Eye of Vengeance, is the 10th of the 19 genetically-engineered
            gene-seed organs that are implanted into a Space Marine Neophyte to produce a new Astartes. This implant
            sits at the base of the brain after being implanted along the optic nerve and connected to the retina, and
            provides hormonal and genetic stimuli which enable a Space Marine's eyes to respond to the optic-therapy
            that all Neophytes must undergo in their Chapter's Apothecarium. These procedures, in turn, allow the
            Chapter's Apothecaries to make adjustments to the growth patterns of the eyes and their light-receptive
            retinal cells. The result is that Space Marines have visual acuity that is far superior to that of baseline
            humans and they can see in low-light conditions and near-darkness almost as well as in bright daylight.</description>
        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <statOffsets>
                    <ShootingAccuracyPawn>0.50</ShootingAccuracyPawn>
                    <MeleeHitChance>0.50</MeleeHitChance>
                </statOffsets>
                <capMods>
                    <li>
                        <capacity>Sight</capacity>
                        <offset>0.5</offset>
                    </li>
                </capMods>
                <makeImmuneTo>
                    <li>Cataract</li>
                    <li>Blindness</li>
                </makeImmuneTo>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>


    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <ignoreConfigErrors>true</ignoreConfigErrors><!--Immune to something unexpected-->
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_LymanEar</defName>
        <label>Lyman's Ear</label>
        <description>The Lyman's Ear, also called the Sentinel, is the 11th of the 19 genetically-engineered gene-seed
            organs that are implanted into a Space Marine Neophyte to produce a new Astartes. Not only does this
            implant's improved inner ear structure make a Space Marine immune to dizziness or motion sickness but it
            also allows Space Marines to consciously filter out and greatly enhance certain sounds over the capabilities
            of normal human hearing. The Lyman's Ear completely replaces one of a Space Marine's original ears. It is
            externally indistinguishable from a normal human ear in size and shape. Lyman's Ear is named after one of
            the scientists who worked in the Emperor's gene-laboratories on Terra in the 30th Millennium who aided in
            the project to produce the first Primarchs and Astartes using the Emperor's own genome as the starting
            point.</description>
        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <statOffsets>
                    <MeleeDodgeChance>0.50</MeleeDodgeChance>
                </statOffsets>
                <capMods>
                    <li>
                        <capacity>Hearing</capacity>
                        <offset>0.5</offset>
                    </li>
                </capMods>
                <makeImmuneTo>
                    <li>HearingLoss</li>
                    <li>Blindness</li>
                </makeImmuneTo>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>




    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_SusanMembrane</defName>
        <label>Sus-an Membranes</label>
        <description>The Sus-an Membrane, also called the Hibernator, is the 12th of the 19
            genetically-engineered organs created from a Space Marine Chapter's gene-seed that is implanted into a
            normal human man to transform him into a Neophyte of an Adeptus Astartes Chapter. Initially implanted within
            the Neophyte's cranium, this membrane eventually merges with the recipient's cerebrum, becoming a full part
            of his neural architecture. The organ's functions are ineffective without follow-up chemical therapy and
            training by a Chapter's Apothecaries, but with sufficient practice and instruction a Space Marine can use
            this implant to enter a state of suspended animation, consciously or as an automatic reaction to extreme
            trauma, keeping the Space Marine alive for Terran years, even if he has suffered otherwise mortal wounds.
            Only the appropriate chemical therapy or hypnotic auto-suggestion can revive a Space Marine from this state.
            The longest recorded period spent in suspended animation was undertaken by Battle-Brother Silas Err of the
            Dark Angels Chapter, who was revived after 567 standard years in Sus-an hibernation.</description>

        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <statOffsets>
                    <MedicalPotency>1.1</MedicalPotency>
                </statOffsets>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>




    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <ignoreConfigErrors>true</ignoreConfigErrors><!--Immune to something unexpected-->
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_Melanochrome</defName>
        <label>Melanochrome</label>
        <description>The Melanochrome, also called the Skinshield, is the 13th of the 19 genetically-engineered
            gene-seed organs that are implanted into a Space Marine Neophyte to produce a new Astartes. This hormonal
            implant is attached to the human lymphatic system and controls the amount of melanin in a Space Marine's
            skin. Exposure to high levels of sunlight will result in the Astartes' skin naturally darkening to
            compensate. It also protects the Space Marine from other forms of electromagnetic radiation. Different
            levels of radiation cause variations of skin colour in different Chapters due to mutations in the
            Melanochrome organ's gene-seed. This can be related to the unusually pale skin of the Blood Angels and their
            Successor Chapters and the dark black skin and red eyes of the Salamanders.</description>

        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <makeImmuneTo>
                    <li>Carcinoma</li>
                </makeImmuneTo>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>


    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_OoliticKidney</defName>
        <label>Oolitic Kidney</label>
        <description>The Oolitic Kidney, also known as the Purifier, is the 14th of the 19 genetically-engineered
            gene-seed organs implanted within a Space Marine Neophyte to create a new Astartes. The organ is implanted
            within the new Astartes' abdominal cavity and it becomes a part of the Space Marines' excretory system, an
            emergency detoxification organ that allows a Space Marine to survive exposure through the respiration,
            tactile contact or ingestion of poisons, toxins and gases that are too powerful for even his rugged immune
            system to normally process without this organ's help. However, this detoxification process renders the
            Astartes unconscious once it begins, so it can be very dangerous if required during combat. Under normal
            circumstances, the Oolitic Kidney also acts as a regulatory organ for the Astartes physiology, maintaining
            the efficient action of the Space Marine's advanced circulatory system and the proper functioning of his
            other organs, implanted or natural.</description>
        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <capMods>
                    <li>
                        <capacity>BloodFiltration</capacity>
                        <offset>0.5</offset>
                    </li>
                </capMods>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>


    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_Neuroglottis</defName>
        <label>Neuroglottis</label>
        <description>The Neuroglottis, also called the Devourer, is the 15th of the 19 genetically-engineered gene-seed
            organs implanted into a Space Marine Neophyte to create a new Astartes. The organ is implanted within the
            Astartes' upper nasal passages and after it is functioning, chewing, tasting or smelling a substance allows
            a Space Marine to biochemically test it for toxicity and nutritional content, essentially determining if the
            substance is edible or poisonous. The organ also allows the Space Marine to identify extremely subtle odours
            with the same fidelity as the average canine bred for tracking, allowing him to even track his quarry by
            smell or taste alone.</description>
        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <hungerRateFactor>0.80</hungerRateFactor>
                <capMods>
                    <li>
                        <capacity>Metabolism</capacity>
                        <offset>0.2</offset>
                    </li>
                </capMods>
                <statOffsets>
                    <FoodPoisonChance>-100</FoodPoisonChance>
                </statOffsets>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>


    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_Mucranoid</defName>
        <label>Mucranoid</label>
        <description>The Mucranoid, also called the Weaver, is the 16th of the 19 gene-seed organs implanted within an
            adolescent Space Marine Neophyte to create a new Astartes. This organ is implanted within the central
            nervous system and responds to specific chemical stimuli in the environment, causing the Space Marine to
            secrete a waxy protein substance similar to mucus through his pores that seals his skin. The gland's
            operations must first be activated by an external chemical treatment, usually self-administered, before it
            will activate. Space Marines are cocooned in this way before they enter suspended animation, and the process
            can even protect them from the harshness of the vacuum and other extremes of temperature, particularly
            deeply frigid environments.</description>

        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <statOffsets>
                    <CarryingCapacity>400</CarryingCapacity>
                    <Mass>100</Mass>
                </statOffsets>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>


    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_BetchersGland</defName>
        <label>Betcher's Gland</label>
        <description>The Betcher's Gland, also known as the Poison Bite, is the 17th of the 19 genetically-engineered
            gene-seed organs that are implanted into a Space Marine Neophyte to produce a new Astartes. Consisting of
            two glands that are implanted into multiple locations inside a Space Marine's mouth, including the inside of
            the lower lip, in the salivary glands or in the hard palette, these two glands working in tandem transform
            an Astartes' saliva into a corrosive, blinding acid when consciously triggered. This allows a Space Marine
            to spit a wad of corrosive acid with the effect of blinding, wounding or even killing an enemy outright.
            These implants' more common use is to aid in the digestion of unusually difficult or impossible things to
            digest, such as cellulose. In the gene-seed of several Primarchs, like that of Rogal Dorn, this organ has
            atrophied and is no longer as effective or has simply ceased to function entirely in the Astartes of the
            Chapters that use those Primarchs' gene-seed.</description>
        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <comps>
            <li Class="HediffCompProperties_VerbGiver">
                <tools>
                    <li>
                        <label>spit</label>
                        <capacities>
                            <li>Bite</li>
                        </capacities>
                        <hediff>BetcherHurt</hediff>
                        <power>18</power>
                        <cooldownTime>2</cooldownTime>
                    </li>
                </tools>
            </li>
        </comps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <statOffsets>
                    <MeleeHitChance>0.50</MeleeHitChance>
                </statOffsets>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>

    <HediffDef>
        <hediffClass>HediffWithComps</hediffClass>
        <defName>BetcherHurt</defName>
        <label>Poisoned by Betcher's Gland</label>
        <description>Betcher's Poison</description>
        <labelNoun>Poisoned by Betcher's Gland</labelNoun>
        <battleStateLabel>blind</battleStateLabel>
        <maxSeverity>1</maxSeverity>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <painOffset>0.24</painOffset>
                <partEfficiencyOffset>-0.9</partEfficiencyOffset>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <comps>
            <li Class="HediffCompProperties_SelfHeal">
                <healAmount>0.02</healAmount>
            </li>
        </comps>
    </HediffDef>


    <HediffDef ParentName="AwesomeOrgans">
        <defName>AwesomeOrgans_BlackCarapace</defName>
        <label>Black Carapace</label>
        <description>The Black Carapace, also known as the Interface, is the last and one of the most important of all
            the 19 gene-seed organ implants a Space Marine Neophyte will receive as he is transformed from a normal,
            adolescent human male into a superhuman Astartes. This neuroreactive, black organic fibrous material is
            implanted directly under the skin of the Neophyte's torso. Points are then cut through the Carapace by an
            Apothecary using surgical tools that allow a Space Marine to directly interface his central nervous system
            with his Power Armour's cybernetic systems. After a few solar hours, the material hardens and invasive
            synthetic fiber bundles that will serve as connection points for neurons grow inward and interlink with the
            newborn Astartes' central nervous system. Note that a Space Marine needs the Black Carapace to use his Power
            Armour to its maximum capabilities, but the armour itself does not need this implant in order to function.
            The Sisters of Battle, for example, as well as some Inquisitors, also wear Power Armour. However, since
            their central nervous systems are not linked directly to their armour's Machine Spirit (artificial
            intelligence) as a Space Marine's would be, their Power Armour is markedly less efficient at providing
            protection or allowing them to manoeuvre in combat than that of an Astartes.</description>
        <addedPartProps>
            <partEfficiency>1.1</partEfficiency>
        </addedPartProps>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <statOffsets>
                    <MoveSpeed>3.00</MoveSpeed>
                    <WorkSpeedGlobal>0.25</WorkSpeedGlobal>
                    <PsychicSensitivity>0.50</PsychicSensitivity>
                    <EnergyShieldEnergyMax>5</EnergyShieldEnergyMax>
                    <StuffEffectMultiplierArmor>2</StuffEffectMultiplierArmor>
                </statOffsets>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </HediffDef>


</Defs>