<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>CaravanOptions</name>
	<author>Torann</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.0</li>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>torann.CaravanOptions</packageId>
	<modDependenciesByVersion>
		<v1.1>
		  <li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		  </li>
		</v1.1>
		<v1.2>
		  <li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		  </li>
		</v1.2>
		<v1.3>
		  <li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		  </li>
		</v1.3>
		<v1.4>
		  <li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		  </li>
		</v1.4>
		<v1.5>
		  <li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		  </li>
		</v1.5>
    </modDependenciesByVersion>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
		<li>jecrell.jecstools</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<description>Version 1.2.0	
Ever felt like it takes too long to walk across the road to a neighbor village to ask for a cup of sugar?  This mod is for you!

Caravan Options adds mod settings that adjust caravan rates applied on the world map:
-Global movement speed multiplier
-Separate movement reductions per road type
-Adjust travel speed bonus for light weight caravans
-Allows movement when caravan capacity limit is exceeded
-Adjust foraging rates
-Allow caravan speed to be determined by the average pawn movement speed

How this mod works:
All variables start with the default game values and there is a reset button if you wish to revert any point.
Mod applies adjustments at run-time with harmony patches, so this mod can be added, removed, or adjust configurations at any point without issues.

Default tile values apply a 50% reduction for all road types - now you can adjust the costs as you see fit. A dirt trail can be adjusted to provide
less of a movement bonus as an asphalt highway.

If a caravan is carrying very little weight, it will travel at an increased speed - this can be adjusted to provide more (or less) of a bonus travel speed.

If a caravan exceeds max carrying capacity, it normally stops dead in its tracks.  This can be adjusted to allow caravans to continue to move
above capacity limits, but at speeds below 100%.

Lastly, if you just feel that caravan movement rates are too slow (or too fast), you can adjust a global multiplier to change caravan movement speeds.

All options, or none, can be applied as desired.

All pawn travel speeds, capacity limits, and game behavior is left intact - the mod only adjusts multipliers of existing values, which means this mod is compatible with any mod that adjusts or adds biome speeds, pawn capacities, or new or modified road types.	
	</description>
</ModMetaData>