<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<Chi_TraA.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#75ffcc&gt;Scholars of profound learning&lt;/color&gt;</Chi_TraA.degreeDatas.0.label>
<Chi_TraA.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has received traditional Confucian education. The traditional concept of family and country makes [PAWN_pronoun] a stronger sense of responsibility, and [PAWN_pronoun] can be stronger when facing pain. [PAWN_pronoun] will not humiliate others, on the contrary, others will learn more about Confucianism and Taoism in the conversation with him, and the spirit will be nurtured. \n\n Although [PAWN_nameDef] sleeps longer, [PAWN_pronoun] learns faster and is more determined. \n\nWomen are less likely to acquire this trait due to the influence of traditional concepts. (Because ancient China was a patriarchal society)</Chi_TraA.degreeDatas.0.description>
<Chi_TraB.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#20ccff&gt;Skilled craftsman&lt;/color&gt;</Chi_TraB.degreeDatas.0.label>
<Chi_TraB.degreeDatas.0.description>Song Li Kefei "Luoyang Garden": "Today Luoyang is a good craftsman; criticizes the red and judges the white; according to other woods; competes with the good fortune."\n\n[PAWN_nameDef] is such a skilled craftsman, from hand-made to large Architecture is the unique skill of [PAWN_pronoun].</Chi_TraB.degreeDatas.0.description>
<Chi_TraC.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#20ccff&gt;Butcher ox man&lt;/color&gt;</Chi_TraC.degreeDatas.0.label>
<Chi_TraC.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has liked to eat big fish and meat since childhood, which makes it very good at slaughtering. [PAWN_pronoun] is very fast at slaughter and [PAWN_pronoun] is like a humanoid machine that knows how to get more meat from a carcass. \n\nAt the same time, in the long-term slaughter process, [PAWN_pronoun] also learned which toxic substances will remain in the slaughter, so [PAWN_pronoun] will be more careful when handling cooking tasks, and the risk of food poisoning is also Reduced a lot.</Chi_TraC.degreeDatas.0.description>
<Chi_TraD.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#20cc20&gt;Meticulous&lt;/color&gt;</Chi_TraD.degreeDatas.0.label>
<Chi_TraD.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] works very meticulously, every little detail is done in place, which makes [PAWN_pronoun] rarely appear food, such as [PAWN_pronoun] is difficult to produce toxic food, at the same time, [PAWN_pronoun] was successfully built The rate is also high. \n\nOn the other hand, [PAWN_pronoun] has mastered some knack for refining medicine and other miscellaneous work, which can help him a lot.</Chi_TraD.degreeDatas.0.description>
<Chi_TraE.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#20cc20&gt;Rejuvenation&lt;/color&gt;</Chi_TraE.degreeDatas.0.label>
<Chi_TraE.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] knows the importance of race against time, [PAWN_pronoun] learned the techniques of dressing up wounds for the wounded as quickly as possible or quickly curing various diseases. \n\n[PAWN_pronoun] has snatched countless lives from death, and [PAWN_pronoun]'s hard work spirit has also been recognized by others.</Chi_TraE.degreeDatas.0.description>

<Chi_ExtraC.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#cc50bb&gt;Wonderful Rejuvenation&lt;/color&gt;</Chi_ExtraC.degreeDatas.0.label>
<Chi_ExtraC.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] Due to his own experience, [PAWN_pronoun]'s medical skills are very superb, which makes it really worthy of the reputation of "Bian Que reincarnation". At the same time, long-term learning experience also makes [PAWN_pronoun] also have a strong talent in pharmacy and learning. \n\nIndividuals who usually have a "Reincarnation Bianque" background story (the background story is in the extra part) tend to have this trait. Of course, this trait will also appear on random characters with a very low probability. \n\nIn addition, [PAWN_nameDef] has noble medical ethics, [PAWN_pronoun] rarely demeans or humiliates others, and others naturally choose to be close to [PAWN_pronoun].</Chi_ExtraC.degreeDatas.0.description>


<Chi_ExtraD.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#cc50bb&gt;Vigorous as the wind&lt;/color&gt;</Chi_ExtraD.degreeDatas.0.label>
<Chi_ExtraD.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has developed the concept of high speed and high efficiency under the strict management system. [PAWN_pronoun] The idea of completing tasks at high speed is not only reflected in the dinner table, but also in work and combat. \n\nUsually the characters with the background story of "Jianrui Camp Soldier or Jianrui Camp Commander" in the extended part will have this trait, and this trait will also appear randomly on other characters with a low probability.</Chi_ExtraD.degreeDatas.0.description>

<Chi_ExtraE.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#cc50bb&gt;Proficient in first aid&lt;/color&gt;</Chi_ExtraE.degreeDatas.0.label>
<Chi_ExtraE.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] knows the importance of racing against time, whether it's emergency or pharmaceutical. [PAWN_pronoun] learned the techniques of dressing up wounds for the wounded or quickly curing various diseases as quickly as possible. \n\n[PAWN_pronoun] has snatched countless lives from death, and [PAWN_pronoun]'s hard work spirit has also been recognized by others.</Chi_ExtraE.degreeDatas.0.description>

<Chi_ExtraF.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#cc50bb&gt;Abide by the conduct&lt;/color&gt;</Chi_ExtraF.degreeDatas.0.label>
<Chi_ExtraF.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a sincere and kind person, especially when doing business, [PAWN_pronoun] will not choose to conceal or deceive others because of petty gain, so [PAWN_pronoun] can often gain the respect of the other party in the transaction.</Chi_ExtraF.degreeDatas.0.description>

<Chi_ExtraG.degreeDatas.0.label>&lt;color=#cc50bb&gt;Resolutely&lt;/color&gt;</Chi_ExtraG.degreeDatas.0.label>
<Chi_ExtraG.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has a strong collective consciousness, so [PAWN_pronoun] is dedicated to the colony all the time. For [PAWN_pronoun], work speed and work efficiency are very important. Therefore, when facing various basic tasks, [PAWN_pronoun] can quickly find the breakthrough points of these basic tasks and make breakthroughs quickly, so [PAWN_pronoun] often can Complete and understand these basic tasks faster than others.</Chi_ExtraG.degreeDatas.0.description>
</LanguageData>