<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<!--== キャットタワー ==-->
	<!--== "鑑賞" == -->
	<ExC_CatTower_Display_Label>appreciation</ExC_CatTower_Display_Label>

	<!--== "展示したキャットタワーを鑑賞します。" == -->
	<ExC_CatTower_Display_Message>Appreciation of the cat tower on display.</ExC_CatTower_Display_Message>

	<!--== "展示できるフィギュアを所持していません。" == -->
	<ExC_NoFigurineInInventory>This colonist does not possess any figures that can be displayed.</ExC_NoFigurineInInventory>

	<!--== "白ねこのフィギュアを展示しました。" == -->
	<ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Shiro>A white cat figure was on display.</ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Shiro>
	<ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Kuro>A black cat figure was on display.</ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Kuro>
	<ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Ash>A ash cat figure was on display.</ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Ash>
	<ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Mike>A calico figure was on display.</ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Mike>
	<ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Chatora>A red tabby figure was on display.</ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Chatora>
	<ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Sabatora>A silver tabby figure was on display.</ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Sabatora>
	<ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Kijitora>A brown tabby figure was on display.</ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Kijitora>
	<ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Creamtora>A cream tabby figure was on display.</ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Creamtora>
	<ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Point>A pointed cat figure was on display.</ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Point>
	<ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Siamese>A siamese cat figure was on display.</ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Siamese>
	<ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Bicolor>A bicolor cat figure was on display.</ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Bicolor>
	<ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Tortoise>A tortoiseshell cat figure was on display.</ExC_DisplayedFigurine_Tortoise>

	<!--== 白ねこのフィギュアは既に展示しています。 ==-->
	<ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Shiro>The white cat figure is already on display.</ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Shiro>
	<ExC_AlreadyFigurine_kuro>The black cat figure is already on display.</ExC_AlreadyFigurine_kuro>
	<ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Ash>The ash cat figure is already on display.</ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Ash>
	<ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Mike>The calico figure is already on display.</ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Mike>
	<ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Chatora>The red tabby figure is already on display.</ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Chatora>
	<ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Sabatora>The silver tabby figure is already on display.</ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Sabatora>
	<ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Kijitora>The brown tabby figure is already on display.</ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Kijitora>
	<ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Creamtora>The cream tabby figure is already on display.</ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Creamtora>
	<ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Point>The pointed cat figure is already on display.</ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Point>
	<ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Siamese>The siamese cat figure is already on display.</ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Siamese>
	<ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Bicolor>The bicolor cat figure is already on display.</ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Bicolor>
	<ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Tortoise>The tortoiseshell cat figure is already on display.</ExC_AlreadyFigurine_Tortoise>



	<!--== キャットタワー完成後 ==-->
	<ExC_PreVictoryMessage>You guys have completed your cat figure collection.
Then, a man came to your colony claiming to be a wealthy cat lover.

"Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
 What a great collection of figures!
 Give it to me! Please!
 I'll give you the price!
 If you like, I can get you a spaceship to get off this planet!"

You can get off this planet with these cats, or you can...
You can turn down the offer and continue living with the cats.

!!ATTENTION!!
If you accept this offer, all the colonist will be on their way!
Be careful, especially if you're playing in commit mode!</ExC_PreVictoryMessage>


	<ExC_VictoryMessage>You boarded the spaceship you received and took off from this cats' paradise.
The loss of the collection was a blow, but the cat is there.
Figurines can be made at any time.

With this in mind, you entered the cold sleep device with your beloved cats
and began your return journey back to your original planet.
</ExC_VictoryMessage>

	<ExC_ContinueButton>No (continue game)</ExC_ContinueButton>
	<ExC_VictoryButton>Yes (victory game)</ExC_VictoryButton>

</LanguageData>
