<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Rachek_RSA>Ritual Size Attenuation</Rachek_RSA>
  <Rachek_RSA_UncappingModeLabel>Size Uncapping Mode</Rachek_RSA_UncappingModeLabel>
  <Rachek_RSA_UncappingModeTooltip>How rituals will scale up when providing extra participants beyond vanilla caps.

{0}
  </Rachek_RSA_UncappingModeTooltip>
  
  <Rachek_RSA_None>None</Rachek_RSA_None>
  <Rachek_RSA_Scaled>Scaled</Rachek_RSA_Scaled>
  <Rachek_RSA_Bonus>Bonus</Rachek_RSA_Bonus>

  <Rachek_RSA_ZeroPercentWarningLabel>Warning: Disabling participation requirements is both unbalanced and not fully supported. Some ritual types will always require at least one participant in order to function.</Rachek_RSA_ZeroPercentWarningLabel>
  <Rachek_RSA_ZeroPercentModeWarningLabel>Warning: Customizing size uncapping is disabled while the population percentage is 0%.</Rachek_RSA_ZeroPercentModeWarningLabel>
  <Rachek_RSA_ZeroPercentForcedModeTooltip>Disabled while the population percentage is 0%.</Rachek_RSA_ZeroPercentForcedModeTooltip>

  <Rachek_RSA_None_Description>None: Ritual sizes are capped at the vanilla size, while scaling down as needed.</Rachek_RSA_None_Description>
  <Rachek_RSA_Scaled_Description>Scaled: Ritual sizes scale up and down with colony size.</Rachek_RSA_Scaled_Description>
  <Rachek_RSA_Bonus_Description>Bonus: Ritual sizes scale up and down with colony size. Additional participants beyond the vanilla cap provide some bonus quality.</Rachek_RSA_Bonus_Description>
  
  <Rachek_RSA_PopulationPercentageLabel>Population Percentage Requirement: {0}</Rachek_RSA_PopulationPercentageLabel>
  <Rachek_RSA_PopulationPercentageTooltip>The minimum number of participants required for rituals to reach full participation, relative to your colony size.\n\nDefault: 75%</Rachek_RSA_PopulationPercentageTooltip>

  <Rachek_RSA_BonusLabel>Maximum Bonus Quality: +{0}</Rachek_RSA_BonusLabel>
  <Rachek_RSA_BonusTooltip>The maximum bonus quality that can be added by extra participants, as a percentage of the base participation quality.\n\nDefault: 25%</Rachek_RSA_BonusTooltip>

  <Rachek_RSA_ShowAdvancedLabel>Advanced</Rachek_RSA_ShowAdvancedLabel>

  <Rachek_RSA_AdvancedWarningLabel>Warning: Here there be maths. You probably shouldn't need to change this. It's only available for those who want to tweak the bonus interpolation curve to suit their needs.</Rachek_RSA_AdvancedWarningLabel>

  <Rachek_RSA_BonusExponentLabel>Bonus Population Exponent: {0}</Rachek_RSA_BonusExponentLabel>
  <Rachek_RSA_BonusExponentTooltip>The exponent used in the interpolation function when calculating bonus quality. Additional colonists generally provide diminishing returns, up to the population requirement. The higher the exponent, the less colonists are needed to effectively reach the highest bonus quality.\n\nDefault: 2.0</Rachek_RSA_BonusExponentTooltip>
  <Rachek_RSA_InterpolationFunction>1.0 - (pow(1.0 - x, {0})</Rachek_RSA_InterpolationFunction>
</LanguageData>