<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<LanguageData>
    <Coomalope.label>Testolope</Coomalope.label>
    <Coomalope.description>A horrid abomination of genetic engineering, the testolope grows a large sack of testosterone on it's back. It can be "milked" for raw testosterone - very gently.</Coomalope.description>
    <CoomRefining.label>Testosterone Refining</CoomRefining.label>
    <CoomRefining.description>Refine raw testosterone gathered from a testolope into usable chems.</CoomRefining.description>
    <RawCoom.label>Raw Testosterone</RawCoom.label>
    <RawCoom.description>Raw testosterone harvested from a testolope. Tastes horrible, but still provides some of the substance's strengthened effects.</RawCoom.description>
    <Coom.label>Testosterone</Coom.label>
    <Coom.description>Refined testosterone, created by the finest scientific minds in the Gymbro community.</Coom.description>
    <RawCoomHigh.label>Raw testosterone high</RawCoomHigh.label>
    <RawCoomHigh.labelNoun>Poisoned by raw testosterone high</RawCoomHigh.labelNoun>
    <RawCoomHigh.description>This person has ingested raw testosterone. They are currently regretting it, but have increased damage resistance and pain tolerance.</RawCoomHigh.description>
    <RawCoomHigh.label>Testosterone high</RawCoomHigh.label>
    <RawCoomHigh.labelNoun>Ingested testosterone</RawCoomHigh.labelNoun>
    <RawCoomHigh.description>This person has injected testosterone. They are more durable, resistant to pain and faster.</RawCoomHigh.description>
    <RawCoom.label>ingested raw testosterone high</RawCoom.label>
    <RawCoom.description>So primal, so alive!</RawCoom.description>
    <RawCoom.label>ingested raw testosterone high</RawCoom.label>
    <RawCoom.description>So primal, so alive!</RawCoom.description>
    <Coom.label>testosterone high</Coom.label>
    <Chemical_coom.label>testosterone high</Chemical_coom.label>
    <Chemical_coom.description>Because of an testosterone addiction, this person needs to regularly consume testosterone to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</Chemical_coom.description>
    <coomAddiction.label>testosterone addiction</coomAddiction.label>
    <coomAddiction.description>A chemical addiction to testosterone. Long-term presence of testosterone has caused neurological adaptations at the cellular level, so the brain can no longer function properly without the drug.
        \nWithout regular doses of testosterone, withdrawal symptoms will begin. However, extended abstinence will force the brain to adapt back to its normal state, resolving the addiction.</coomAddiction.description>
</LanguageData>