<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>Evil Tactician's RimWorld Tweaks</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>ETRT.RimWorldTweaks</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1500293791</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ETRT_2_3_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.3.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>1.4 Compatibility Added.
		
Quick update for RimWorld 1.4.

|Patch notes:
- Removed Anime tree build radius patch, as it wasn't working even in 1.3.
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ETRT_2_2_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Added the ability to sow grass in growing zones.
		
A very small addition, mainly useful for Animal Pens. I highly recommend the mod "Smart Farming" from Owlchemist for it's ability to toggle no petty jobs and avoid your pawns constantly resowing. As always, this can be turned off in the Vanilla Framework Expanded mod settings.

|Patch notes:
- Added ability to sow grass in growing zones.
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ETRT_2_1_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>|img:newsimages/ET_Pemmican|caption:Integrated the functionality of my latest mod: Practical Pemmican.
		
As with all tweaks now, this can be independently disabled via the Vanilla Expanded Framework settings.

|The safest way to disable any tweaks is to load RimWorld, change settings, restart RimWorld and then load your save. Any tweaks you were already using in your save may cause an error on loading, but most of my tweaks are save to disable or enable mid-save.

|Patch notes:
- 1 Pemmican counts as 1 portion, no more crafting or eating batches of 16 Pemmican.
- Pemmican Stack limit changed to 10. (Can be independently switched back to 75)
- Recipes and values tweaked accordingly, entirely vanilla friendly!
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ETRT_2_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Major Rewrite of the mod and most of the patches and content it contains.
		
Please note that &lt;color=orange&gt;Vanilla Expanded Framework&lt;/color&gt; is now a requirement, the mod will not function without it.
This was a tough decision to make, but it was ultimately the right way forward as it allows users to pick and choose which tweaks they want active in their game. I chose this Framework to handle this because it is used by the majority of people who use RimWorld mods and it avoids me having to write and bundle code which may break in future RimWorld updates.

|img:newsimages/ET_Toggable|caption:In order to access these settings, please go into the mod settings for Vanilla Expanded Framework. They are listed in one of the tabs.

Note that disabling (or enabling) tweaks &lt;b&gt;requires a restart of RimWorld&lt;/b&gt; to take effect. This enables users to disable parts of the mod which conflict with their mod list or which they simply do not wish to use. I have gone through the code thoroughly to ensure patches are applied only if specific tweaks are enabled, but do let me know if I missed something.

|Patch notes:
* Now using HugsLib features to deliver this kind of news.
* Vanilla Expanded Framework is now required.
* Room Size Tweaks have been adjusted in line with other mods.
* Muffalo's now give milk again as they did in older RimWorld versions.
* Hay will no longer spoil, but it will deteriorate when not roofed.
* (Royalty) Minify and Move the Anime Tree.
* (Royalty) Embroidered Hood which satisfies noble requirements.
* (Royalty) Prestige Helmets have scaling Social and Negotiation Bonuses.
* (Ideology) Tribal Apparel can now be used in Ideoligions.
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ETRT_1_3_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>1.0 - 1.2 Compatibility moved to Legacy version.
		
Please note that compatibility for RimWorld 1.0 to 1.2 has been moved to a Legacy version of this mod which you can find on the Workshop.
		
This was done to enable me to rewrite parts of the mod from the ground up and enable functionality people have asked for since a very long time. The existing mod contained a lot of tweaks which are now part of Vanilla, so it was good to do a major tidy.
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

</Defs>