<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
     <MG_Horse.label>Mengwu Horse</MG_Horse.label>
     <MG_Horse.description>The horse breed bred by the Mughal tribe after careful breeding, compared with ordinary horses, it is faster, has a higher IQ, and is less wild. Because the supply of pasture in the Mughal area is relatively tight, its eating frequency will also increase. lower. \n\nFor the people of the Mughal tribe, the Mughal horse is an indispensable partner in the nomadic life of the nomads, and it is also the favorite horse breed of the Mughal cavalry. \n\nMogulma is most common in grassland areas, and it is also distributed in forest areas such as temperate and frigid zones.</MG_Horse.description>

     <MG_TiaoShu.label>Mogul Leaping Bunny</MG_TiaoShu.label>
     <MG_TiaoShu.description>The jumping rabbit, which was originally an endangered species in the old Shenzhou area, has rejuvenated its second spring after being introduced to the marginal world. The Mongolian herdsmen in the Shenzhou area like to keep this cute animal as a pet. In the Mengwu Totem There is also an image of a jumping rabbit, which shows its importance to the Mughal people. \n\nWild jumping rabbits are mostly distributed in semi-desert areas, and their food requirements are very low. In addition, they are also distributed in forest areas.</MG_TiaoShu.description>

     <MG_TuSun.label>Rabbit mantle</MG_TuSun.label>
     <MG_TuSun.description>Protected animals native to the cold regions of China can adapt to a relatively cold and barren environment, and eat less food, but they are already on the verge of extinction in the old China. Therefore, under the promotion of the Mumbai Biological Conservation Organization, the rabbit mantle was introduced to the edge world. \n\nAfter being introduced to the border world, the manul has maintained similar habits as before. It still chooses to prey on small animals such as rats. Its survival ability has also been improved. In addition, it has become more humane now. More suitable as a pet.</MG_TuSun.description>

     <MG_TuBoShu.label>Mongolian Woody Groundhog</MG_TuBoShu.label>
     <MG_TuBoShu.description>Rodents, mainly distributed in the semi-arid grasslands of China, are widely distributed on the old Shenzhou planet. Such lovely creatures have also been brought to the edge of the world by Mongolian biologists. Groundhog like to dig holes and can adapt to the cold. They are widely distributed in areas with abundant rainfall. \N n Some Mongolian people like to keep it as a pet, while some Mongolian people like to eat it as a game.</MG_TuBoShu.description>

     <Mengwu_Wanyangjiao.label>Naughty Sheep Horn Bow</Mengwu_Wanyangjiao.label>
     <Mengwu_Wanyangjiao.description>A kind of composite bow used by the Mengwu tribe. This kind of bow is very lethal. In addition, because of its exquisite design, users can use it to hurt enemies at a long distance.     </Mengwu_Wanyangjiao.description>

     <Arrow_MengwuYangGongJian.label>Naughty Sheep Horn Arrow</Arrow_MengwuYangGongJian.label>

     <Mengwu_Gong.label>Mengwu Short Bow</Mengwu_Gong.label>
     <Mengwu_Gong.description>It is a kind of bow and arrow that Mongolian and Wu people like to use in the early development of the tribe. It is simple to make, but its lethality is also average.     </Mengwu_Gong.description>

     <Arrow_MengwuGongJian.label>Mengwu Short Arrow</Arrow_MengwuGongJian.label>

     <MG_TengGeQingGong.label>Tengger Charge Light Bow</MG_TengGeQingGong.label>
     <MG_TengGeQingGong.description>Different from ordinary electric charge weapons, the Mughal scientists of Glittering World retained the traditional Mongolian style when designing electric charge weapons. They believed that the tradition of "bending the bow and shooting carvings" could not be changed, even if it was the most advanced weapon design. \n\nThe Tengger light bow uses charged arrows. At the same time, due to its light design, the user can quickly deal devastating blows to units with low armor during battle.</MG_TengGeQingGong.description>

     <Bullet_DianHeJian.label>Tengger Charged Arrow</Bullet_DianHeJian.label>
     
     <MG_TengGeNu.label>Tengger Charged Crossbow</MG_TengGeNu.label>
     <MG_TengGeNu.description>Different from ordinary electric charge weapons, the Mughal scientists of Glittering World retained the traditional Mongolian style when designing electric charge weapons. They believed that the tradition of "bending the bow and shooting carvings" could not be changed, even if it was the most advanced weapon design. \n\nThe armor-piercing performance of the Tengri crossbow is very strong. The Mughal people often use this powerful electric crossbow when fighting against the heavenly soldiers with powerful armor or in long-distance combat. For them, no matter how powerful it is Even his armor couldn't withstand a few charged crossbow bolts.</MG_TengGeNu.description>     

     <Bullet_DianHeNuJian.label>Tengger Charged Bolt</Bullet_DianHeNuJian.label>

     <Mengwu_Sabre.label>Mughal Iron Saber</Mengwu_Sabre.label>
     <Mengwu_Sabre.description>One of the most common weapons used by the Mughals, because of its curved design, is not easy to get entangled in hair, and for those unarmed and defenseless civilians or livestock, this saber will give They deliver devastating blows.</Mengwu_Sabre.description>

     <Mengwu_Machete.label>Mughal Steel Scimitar</Mengwu_Machete.label>
     <Mengwu_Machete.description>The sharp scimitars forged by the Mughal tribe using the Chinese ironmaking technique are usually used by cavalry and herdsmen. This kind of scimitar has just the right arc, and it will not be shaken off even if it hits hard armor. For the colonists in the agricultural areas of China It is said that the cold light reflected by the scimitar is often one of the signs of nomadic invasion and killing.</Mengwu_Machete.description>

     <Mengwu_Bulu.label>Mumbur</Mengwu_Bulu.label>
     <Mengwu_Bulu.description>A melee hunting tool made of wood and steel. Of course, with the development of the times and the spread of Shenzhou forging technology, this kind of blue can not only easily break the bones of animals, but also its powerful hammer head. Can break through those heavy armors without any trouble</Mengwu_Bulu.description>

     <MG_GeLiDao.label>Blade of Tengri</MG_GeLiDao.label>
     <MG_GeLiDao.description>It is a powerful melee weapon carefully designed by the Mughal scientists of Shining World and manufactured with the most advanced forging technology. its power. \n\nCompared with the monomolecular sword, it is more powerful, but slightly less armor-piercing.</MG_GeLiDao.description>

     <MG_NaiDouFu.label>Milk Tofu</MG_NaiDouFu.label>
     <MG_NaiDouFu.description>A dairy product made of animal milk and a small amount of vegetarian food. It tastes sour and sweet. It is an indispensable food in the life of Mughal people. Milk tofu can be preserved for a long time. In some colder regions of the marginal world, milk tofu is usually It will be used as rations for the colonists during the winter. Such delicious and nutritious food is perfect as a reserve food. \n\nThis food belongs to the Mughal dry food, and the colonists can get a small mood bonus after eating it.</MG_NaiDouFu.description>
     
     <MG_RouGan.label>Mughal jerky</MG_RouGan.label>
     <MG_RouGan.description>The jerky made by the Mughals using traditional pickling methods is their main food and one of the symbols of herdsman culture. The Mughal jerky has a long shelf life, is simple to make, and has a good taste when used practically. essential dry food. \n\nThis food belongs to the Mughal dry food, and the colonists can get a small mood bonus after eating it.</MG_RouGan.description>     

     <MG_GuoZiGan.label>Dried Mughal Fruit</MG_GuoZiGan.label>
     <MG_GuoZiGan.description>Dried fruits made by the Mughal people after drying fresh fruits are usually used as desserts after meals or for standing dry food. Dried fruits retain the fresh taste of fruits and have a long shelf life. Even without cold storage, they can be stored for a long time. The price is very good high. \n\nThis food belongs to the Mughal dry food, and the colonists can get a small mood bonus after eating it.</MG_GuoZiGan.description>
     
     <MG_ZhongArmor.label>Mughal Heavy Armor</MG_ZhongArmor.label>
     <MG_ZhongArmor.description>The heavy armor forged by the Mughal people using Shenzhou forging technology has excellent protective performance. Although wearing it will slow down the movement speed a little, it is not a problem for the muggy soldiers with strong physique\n\nMongolian With the help of such armor, Wu soldiers can easily defeat those medieval civilizations that dare to offend them.</MG_ZhongArmor.description>

     <MG_QingArmor.label>Mughal Yuanjia</MG_QingArmor.label>
     <MG_QingArmor.description>The lightweight armor forged by the Mughal people using Shenzhou forging technology has better protective performance and will not affect the speed of movement after wearing it, so it is favored by the Mughal recruits. \n\nWhen facing some weak weapons, it can effectively offset the damage from these weapons, but when facing some weapons with strong armor-piercing ability, this armor will be slightly inferior.</MG_QingArmor.description>

     <MG_HuJian.label>Mughal Iron Shoulders</MG_HuJian.label>
     <MG_HuJian.description>The Mughal people forged the steel shoulder guards using the Shenzhou iron smelting technique. The Mughal army usually used this shoulder guard with heavy armor. The shoulder guards not only retained the traditional culture of the Mughal people in terms of shape design, And the protection performance and cost performance are also very good. \n\nFor the Mughals, a blacksmith who can forge iron is also very important. Without their superb skills, there would be no such armor with excellent protection performance.</MG_HuJian.description>


     <MG_HelmetQingTouKui.label>Moug Lightweight Helmet</MG_HelmetQingTouKui.label>
     <MG_HelmetQingTouKui.description>The helmet worn by the Mughals in combat has good protection performance and does not affect the wearer's sight. This helmet is light in material, easy to make, and suitable for mobile combat.</MG_HelmetQingTouKui.description>

     <MG_HelmetZhong.label>Mughal Heavy Iron Helm</MG_HelmetZhong.label>
     <MG_HelmetZhong.description>The heavy helmets made by Mughal blacksmiths imitated the equipment of the Imperial Guards of China. The Imperial Guards of China have always been the most troublesome opponents of the Mughals. The bows and arrows of the Mughals are difficult to penetrate their thick armor. \n\nIn order to gain the upper hand in the battle against the Chinese civilization, the Mughals also began to equip a large number of such heavy armors. Although it is a bit bulky, it has excellent protective performance.</MG_HelmetZhong.description>

     <MG_QClothing.label>Mughal robe</MG_QClothing.label>
     <MG_QClothing.description>A set of clothing most commonly used by the Mughal people in their nomadic life. It is more convenient to make. At the same time, the Mughal people used the cloth weaving technology of the Shenzhou colony when designing this set of clothing, making the Mughal robe durable and more convenient. In addition, the muggle symbols on the clothing also make the social characteristics of this clothing more obvious.</MG_QClothing.description>

     <MG_QinChaMianJu.label>Kipchak Mask</MG_QinChaMianJu.label>
     <MG_QinChaMianJu.description>The mask worn by the priests of the Mughal tribe. This mask is usually a symbol of mystery and nature in the Mughal tribe. The Mughal priests usually wear this mask to perform sacrificial ceremonies. For the Mughal people, it is Tenge in the symbol.</MG_QinChaMianJu.description>

     <MGTableA.label>Mughal Table (1x2)</MGTableA.label>
     <MGTableA.description>The table made by the Mughal people imitated the craftsmanship of Chinese carpenters, and the traditional Mughal symbols were engraved on the top of the table, which symbolized the heroic and generous culture of the Mughal people. \n\nThe Mongolian table is usually placed in the yurt by the herdsmen, as a dining table or a place for sacrificial ceremonies, and its decorative effect is good.</MGTableA.description>

     <MGTableB.label>Mughal Table (2x4)</MGTableB.label>
     <MGTableB.description>The table made by the Mughal people imitated the craftsmanship of Chinese carpenters, and the traditional Mughal symbols were engraved on the top of the table, which symbolized the heroic and generous culture of the Mughal people. \n\nThe Mongolian table is usually placed in the yurt by the herdsmen, as a dining table or a place for sacrificial ceremonies, and its decorative effect is good.</MGTableB.description>

     <MGRug_A.label>Mughal Rug (1x2)</MGRug_A.label>
     <MGRug_A.description>Carpets printed with traditional Mughal patterns are generally placed in yurts by Mughal people. This is an indispensable part of Mughal interior decoration. This kind of carpet is easy to clean, not easy to be contaminated with dust, and clean and simple. \n\nSome Mughal palace nobles will also collect special animal leather to make this kind of carpet to show their noble status.</MGRug_A.description>

     <MGRug_B.label>Mughal Rug (2x4)</MGRug_B.label>
     <MGRug_B.description>Carpets printed with traditional Mughal patterns are generally placed in yurts by Mughal people. This is an indispensable part of Mughal interior decoration. This kind of carpet is easy to clean, not easy to be contaminated with dust, and clean and simple. \n\nSome Mughal palace nobles will also collect special animal leather to make this kind of carpet to show their noble status.</MGRug_B.description>

     <MG_NaiJiu.label>Milk wine</MG_NaiJiu.label>
     <MG_NaiJiu.description>A kind of fine wine that is abundant in the nomadic areas of Shenzhou, and it is one of the favorite drinks of Mughal people at dance parties. In the marginal world, Mughal people usually mix dairy products and a small amount of vegetarian food together to make milk wine. In the nomadic culture, milk wine can be made directly on the brewing stand without the fermentation process. Although the workmanship is a little rough, the faint milky fragrance of milk wine is the embodiment of the bold and unconstrained culture of the Mughal people. The "half wine, half food" wine is highly praised by the herdsmen. \n\nLike other Chinese wines, milk wine also has health bonuses, addiction and tolerance mechanisms, but milk wine is often less addictive than ordinary beer and other alcoholic beverages.</MG_NaiJiu.description>
     <MG_NaiJiu.ingestCommandString>Drink {0}</MG_NaiJiu.ingestCommandString>
     <MG_NaiJiu.ingestReportString>Drink {0}</MG_NaiJiu.ingestReportString>



</LanguageData>