<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Caravan Activities Framework</name>
	<author>Temmie3754, Bambaryła</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>temmie3754.caravanactivities</packageId>
	<description>
			Welcome to Caravan Activities Framework!

			It's an easy to use XML-based framework that allows you to add Caravan Activities by adding simple XML objects. For adding new stuff, refer to existing activities as well as the FrameworkGuide.txt.
			
			Framework possibilities:
			* You can define an activity for a caravan to be able to perform on the world map
			* Each new activity adds a new gizmo
			* Each activity can have many Options to choose from
			* Options are risks and outcomes
			* Activities can be limited to particular biomes; roads, rivers and base proximity - base proximity can be further limited by base-faction's tech level
			* Each activity incurs a cooldown on the tile it's performed on, and it's customizable.
			* Each of the Options can be limited to particular skill levels
			* Each of the Options may or may not require specific items
			* Each of the Options may specify items that boost the outcome
			* Each of the Options has good and bad outcomes defined for it. Good outcome happens once at the end of activity. Bad outcomes are rolled every day of the activity.
			* Outcomes can include items, relationship changes, ideology changes, colonist injury or death, pollution change.

			Activities defined by default are:
			* Offer help to a nearby faction base for goodwill and silver
			* Steal resources from a nearby faction base, risking death and injury
			* Chop down some trees for wood, risking injury and death
			* Forage some plants
			* Hunt some animals, risking injury and death
			* Mine some resources, risking injury and death
			This list will be expanded whenever I find a new idea and somet time to add it :)


			Compatibility:
			* VF is compatible
			* SRTS is not compatible
			* Aerocraft Framework - I have no idea
	</description>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>