<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>

    <name>BondageBedTorture Furniture Addon 1.4 - Retexture and More</name>

    <author>Mr. Mauer, Gerrymon96</author>
	<supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>BondageBedTorture.FurAdd2.Gerrymon</packageId>
	<modDependencies>
    <li>
        <packageId>Mlie.BondageBedTorture</packageId>
        <displayName>BondageBed Torture (Continued)</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2846468041</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
	<li>
        <packageId>vanillaexpanded.vfemedical</packageId>
        <displayName>VFE - Medical Module</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/1718191613</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
    </modDependencies>
	<loadBefore>
	</loadBefore>
	<loadAfter>
	<li>Mlie.BondageBedTorture</li>
	<li>vanillaexpanded.vfemedical</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<incompatibleWith>
	</incompatibleWith>
	<description>
This is the 1.4 compatibility update for the BondageBed Torture - Furniture Addon by Mr. Mauer, originally for my personal use so I took some liberty to change the textures and items. The mod run MOSTLY fine even with red errors here and there. I'll do my best if there's any bug/glitch, but since my modding knowledge only consist of copy-pasting XMLs, I can't promise everything will be solved in timely manner (or ever)... so I apologize in advance. Please, always backup your saves in-case mods go wrong.

Change notes (version 0):
- untouched from the original: prisoner pole, operating table and beheading block.
- Pillory texture replaced.
- TrueCross texture replaced, name changed into Binding Cross.
- TortureCross texture replaced, name changed into Saltire Cross.
- New description for most of the furnitures.
- replace all of Hanging Cage L with new Round Cage.
- replace all of Hanging Cage R with new Bar Cage.
- all bondage furnitures now have comfort of 0.09, making bound prisoners eventually uncomfortable.
- all bondage furnitures now have terror value between 30-40 for those that have ideology.

Known errors:
- Weird graphical stacking because of how the game render things.
- Cannot put bondage furnitures outdoor, will fails to bind prisoner. Inherent issue from Bondage Bed mod.
- Some prisoner sometimes produces error "Tried to get sleeping slot pos with index 1, but there are only 1 sleeping slots available.". Need more checking.
- Since these basically are glorified sleeping spots, some furnitures like pillory are rendered on where the pawn usually sleeps, so any re-tex/animation/races mods that changed pawn's size will probably look weird.
- For whatever reasons, if the bound prisoner fell off the furniture and was brought back to their prisoner bed, right click their bondage furniture to remove the "bound" status.

Credits:
- BondageBedTorture Furniture Addon 1.3 by Mr.Mauer (https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2109234248)
- Some art inspiration from the leftover/unused graphic data inside COF's Execute Expand (https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2869133661)

	</description>
</ModMetaData>
