<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

  <TipSetDef>
    <defName>Corp_CorporateTips</defName>
    <tips>
		<!-- Nobles -->
      <li>All but the lowest rank are able to call for mercenary support in times of need.  In addition, each rank can call the previous ranks' level of mercenaries in addition to their own better one.</li>
      <li>Like royals, higher ranking executives get pickier with their food choices.</li>
	  <li>Corporate members require their own bedrooms and 'throne rooms' just like Royals - however, they require vastly different things inside them, focusing more on technology and comfort.</li>
	  <li>Junior Executives and Executives, not to mention the unobtainable ranks above that, require rediculously well-furnished bedrooms and offices.</li>
	  <li>Starting at Operations Manager, corporate members require three-piece suits, which cover the middle and outer layers of the torso, arms, and legs.  They can still wear shirts and pants underneath!</li>
	  <li>Although the tooltips say they can wear parkas and power armor, they actually can't.  I don't know why it says that, but I've double checked and tested the code.</li>
	  <li>Because of what layers the Three-Piece Suit utilizes, corporate members cannot wear armor - you can of course, temporarily force them into armor instead of their suits, but they'll be unhappy for it.</li>
	  <li>Corporate members can use any sort of weapon - but because they can't wear armor with their suits, the best they can utilize is shield belts.  Keep them out of the line of fire! Let others die for them.</li>
	  <li>Unlike Royals, corporate members require increasing qualities of clothing as they rank up, ending with Excellent quality clothing at Executive-rank.  Better train your tailors!</li>
		
		<!-- Implants -->
		<li>As they rank up, corporate members are rewarded with multiple implants - the crown jewel of which is the coveted Neurocomputer, a microcomputer that enhances quite a number of brain functions, at the cost of psychic sensitivity and a weakness to EMP.</li>
		<li>Although they don't require bionics, all corporate ranks starting from Operations manager are rewarded various bionic parts.  By the time they reach the Executive rank, they'll be sporting a full set of bionic body parts.  Shnazzy!</li>
		<li>You can downgrade a Neurocomputer implant much like you can downgrade a psychic amplifier, and none of the corporate ranks technically require its use.  It also isn't illegal to put it into someone else!</li>
		<li>When choosing what implants to give your corporate members, focus on ones that improve social impact and beauty, as they're the only ones who can trade with the lucrative corporate orbital trade ships.</li>












		<li>Rimworld: Megacorps is fully compatible and integrated with War Crimes Expanded and RimCuisine 2! (Coming soon)</li>
		<li>RimCuisine 2 is better than VGP.  #Changemymind</li>
		<li>Thank you for using the MegaCorp mod, made by me, Crustypeanut! Did you know I also made War Crimes Expanded and RimCuisine 2?</li>
   </tips>
  </TipSetDef>
  
</Defs>