<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

  <HediffDef ParentName="DiseaseBase">
    <defName>MetasynapticNode</defName>
    <label>Metasynaptic Node</label>
    <description>Some Spelopede variants possess unique metasynaptic processes to feed a colony of tiny organisms. Upon being threatened, Spelopede release this colony around them to form a cloud of protection against ranged attacks. Unfortunately, this is one-time use ability as Spelopede must spend at least a year to re-establish another swarm acceptable for combat.</description>
    <isBad>false</isBad>
    <stages>
      <li>
        <partEfficiencyOffset>0</partEfficiencyOffset>
      </li>
    </stages>
  </HediffDef>

  <HediffDef ParentName="DiseaseBase">
    <defName>Broodling</defName>
    <label>Megascarab Spores</label>
    <description>Megascarab can carry spores of its own species. When implanted in a corpse, it is immediately consumed to produce additional hostile Megascarabs. Number of Megascarabs created is dependent on mass of the corpse. These Megascarabs have also been found to avoid active combat, increasing their chances of utilizing combat casualties mid-battle. This evolution initially had uncontrolled proliferation which ended up indirectly harming the colony by ruining the econsystem. Aforementioned initial variant is now believed to be extinct as Insectoid colony systematically incorporated those with more milder behaviour over time. Now spore-based reproduction are only utilized as hostile response, and hive sends out a pheromone that arrests all proliferation when there are more than 80 Megascarabs in the area.</description>
    <isBad>false</isBad>
    <stages>
      <li>
      </li>
    </stages>
  </HediffDef>

  <HediffDef ParentName="DiseaseBase">
    <defName>ChitinousPlating</defName>
    <label>Chitinous Plating</label>
    <description>Unlike other Insectoids which have developed support abilities, Megaspiders have evolved to gain powerful armours befitting of their role as main offensive unit. Megaspider variant with Chitinous Plating are slower than normal Megaspider, but feel no pain and gain +40% blunt armor and +20% sharp armor.</description>
    <isBad>false</isBad>
    <stages>
      <li>
        <capMods>
          <li>
            <capacity>Moving</capacity>
            <offset>-0.25</offset>
          </li>
        </capMods>
        <statOffsets>
          <ArmorRating_Blunt>0.4</ArmorRating_Blunt>
          <ArmorRating_Sharp>0.2</ArmorRating_Sharp>
        </statOffsets>
        <painFactor>0</painFactor>
      </li>
    </stages>
  </HediffDef>

  <!-- 1.2 Additions -->
  <HediffDef ParentName="DiseaseBase">
    <defName>HivemindNetwork</defName>
    <label>hivemind network</label>
    <description>Greater utilization of psylink abilities in Rimworld has caused mutant strain with greater connection to hivemind to be selected into prominence. This hivemind network prevents mental interference, and pollutes psionic plane with broadcast of multifarious Insectoid consciousness that reduce entropy limit of all psykers in surrounding area to near 0. Therefore although Hivemind Network cannot prevent activation of psionic abilities, it serve as effective deterrent by significantly increasing the consequences of doing so. This psychic contamination disappears in about a hour after killing the offending creature.</description>
    <isBad>false</isBad>
    <stages>
      <li>
        <statOffsets>
          <PsychicSensitivity>0</PsychicSensitivity>
        </statOffsets>
      </li>
    </stages>
  </HediffDef>

  <HediffDef ParentName="DiseaseBase">
    <defName>HivemindFeedback</defName>
    <label>hivemind feedback</label>
    <labelNoun>hivemind feedback</labelNoun>
    <description>Contamination of surrounding psionic plane with Insectoid consciousness. Relatively harmless except to humanoid psionics, whose entropy limit is decreased as a result. Caused by presence of Insectoid variant with Hivemind Network health condition in the map.</description>
    <isBad>false</isBad>
    <comps>
      <li Class="HediffCompProperties_Disappears">
        <disappearsAfterTicks>2500~2500</disappearsAfterTicks>
      </li>
    </comps>
    <stages>
      <li>
        <!-- <statFactors>
					<PsychicEntropyMax>0.2</PsychicEntropyMax>
				</statFactors> -->
      </li>
    </stages>
  </HediffDef>

</Defs>
