<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>

<Chi_Storyteller_B.label>Referring to official scholars - Li Zi Qing</Chi_Storyteller_B.label>
<Chi_Storyteller_B.description>As a traditional scholar-bureaucrat, Li Ziqing regarded the spread of Confucianism and Taoism as an important task. In order to allow the colonists to have more energy to cultivate their bodies and minds and implement the concept of "benevolence and justice", he would do his best to reduce those people who are uncomfortable. The frequency of crazy diseases and some adverse events, similarly, the intensity and frequency of attacks will be kept at a moderate level by him. Merchant ships and caravans will also be more willing to come to your colony to trade with you. \n\nOn the other hand, in Li Ziqing’s worldview, he firmly believes that “the sky is perpetual, not for the Yao to survive, not to perish”, regardless of whether your colony is under threat of heavy attacks and is about to perish, or Enjoy the prosperity of "the sound of the phoenix flute, the light of the jade pot, and the fish and dragon dance overnight." He will choose to watch silently and not interfere with everything. He believes that everything is arranged by nature and heaven, whether it is good or bad.</Chi_Storyteller_B.description>

<Chi_Storyteller_C.label>Out of the valley warbler - Du Fuxue</Chi_Storyteller_C.label>
<Chi_Storyteller_C.description>As a musician, Du Mixue's every piece of music is beautiful, like the sound of nature. Her singing voice, like a golden oriole, is an indispensable business card for her. \n\nShe likes to see the sight of the city. The more guests she visits, the more interested she will be to play more exciting music, so she likes to arrange more visitors, travelers passing through your colony, and the same, visiting The caravan will also increase slightly, and she will also slightly reduce the frequency of annoying miscellaneous incidents, diseases, and small threats. She believes that in such an atmosphere, your colony can also write the most gorgeous and moving chapter. \n\nUnder Du Mixue’s arrangement, there will be more requests for missions, and at the same time, help from friendly forces will be more frequent, and the frequency of attacks will be at a moderate level. She feels that appropriate challenges are also perfect" An indispensable part of the chapter.</Chi_Storyteller_C.description>


</LanguageData>