<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>DIY Humans</name>
	<author>Carnagion</author>
	<packageId>Carnagion.DIYHumans</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ogliss.Ykara.HarvestEverything</packageId>
			<displayName>Harvest Everything!</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2007485974</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadBefore/>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ogliss.Ykara.HarvestEverything</li>
		<li>Smuffle.HarvestOrgansPostMortem</li>
		<li>fluffy.thebirdsandthebees</li>
		<li>Dylan.CSL</li>
		<li>DankPyon.Medieval.Overhaul</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<incompatibleWith/>
	<description>Too many involuntary organ donors lying around? Not enough volunteers for your doctors to practice surgery on? Or maybe you're looking for new ways to commit war crimes in-game? DIY Humans is here to solve all your problems.

	FEATURES

Pawns can stitch together various body parts at a butcher table to "create" a human from scratch, if they have the required Medicine skill level.

The recipe requires a small amount of human meat and all the body parts found in a regular human, i.e. 2 eyes, 2 ears, a nose, a jaw, 2 arms, 2 legs, a heart, 2 lungs, 2 kidneys, a liver, a stomach, a spine, and a brain.

The end result will be a fully-formed human, no different from any other "normal" humans. Furthermore, the skills of the crafted human are multiplied by a value depending on the crafter's medical skill.

However, there is a possibility that the newly created human experiences an extreme mental break immediately. There is also a possibility of one or more infections on a random body part, again depending on the medical skill of the creator.

	MOD SUPPORT

DIY Humans adds new features and functionalities if certain mods are loaded:

	- Harvest Organs Post Mortem
	The recipe to create a human will be performable on autopsy tables instead of butcher tables.

	- The Birds and the Bees
	The recipe to create a human will require genitalia.

	- Children, School, and Learning
	Crafted humans will not generate as newborns, but as full-fledged adults instead.

	- Rim of Madness - Bones
	The recipe to create a human will require human bones.

	- Medieval Overhaul
	The recipe to create a human will not require human leather.

Note that these mods are not requirements or dependencies, they just activate additional features if loaded.

	FAQ

1. Why. Just why.
A. Why not? [insert trollface emoji]

2. Is this mod compatible with:
	- Combat Extended?
	A. I don't know. Don't ask. Find out for yourself if you dare to.

	- Expanded Prosthetics and Organ Engineering?
	A. Yes, it should be.

	- Rah's Bionics and Surgery Expansion?
	A. Yes, it should be.

	- "The forbidden mod"?
	A. I don't know, but you need to go to horny jail.

	- Any other mods that expand upon the medical system or add more warcrime-y stuff?
	A. I see no reason why there should be any incompatibilities, unless the other mod removes body parts or changes their defNames.

3. Is it safe to add to an ongoing save?
A. Yes, absolutely. However, it is good practice to make a backup of the save file before adding it, just in case something unexpectedly goes wrong.

4. Is it safe to remove from ongoing saves?
A. Why would you ever want to remove this mod? Are you not entertained? (Jokes aside, yes it should be safe. Also, be sure to make a backup of the save file, just in case something unexpectedly goes wrong.)

	CREDITS

Thanks to:
- Ykara and Ogliss, for making (and updating) Harvest Everything!
- mikester112 on the RimWorld Discord server, without whose idea this shitty mod would never have been made.

RimWorld is owned by Tynan Sylvester.

	DOCUMENTATION

This mod's files and source code can be found at https://github.com/Carnagion/DIYHumans.
	</description>
</ModMetaData>