<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

<!--============== 3 shades of cloth ==============-->
	<ResearchProjectDef>
		<defName>ComfyTech</defName>
		<label>Basic Furniture</label>
		<description>Meditation for some is a time of bliss for others its a time of intese thinking on various subjects like poetry "Roses are red, violets are blue, I'm schizophrenic, and so am I". And as one of colonist was almost achieving a state of becoming one with himself, he fell asleep, dreaming, of more butt friendly places where he can sle... mediate.</description>
		<baseCost>560</baseCost>
		<tab>FurnitureTinkering</tab>
		<techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
		<prerequisites><li>Electricity</li></prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>0</researchViewX>
			<researchViewY>0</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef>
		<defName>ComfyTechTierII</defName>
		<label>Furniture Designs</label>
		<description>The winter is coming, or so they heard. But it wasnt after than few days later that they ware all out of socks. Even the dirty ones. After few minutes of cerfully wathiching each others feet in silence, they all agreed it had to be the work of mole-squirrels. And a need for new storing spots was voiced.</description>
		<baseCost>200</baseCost>
		<tab>FurnitureTinkering</tab>
		<techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
		<prerequisites><li>ComfyTech</li></prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>1</researchViewX>
			<researchViewY>0</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef>
		<defName>ComfyTechTierIII</defName>
		<label>Small Utilities Designs</label>
		<description>"Housework can't kill you, but why take a chance?" was written on some old  flayer from Slack Top Furniture Utilities, which just stick to one of colonist face.</description>
		<baseCost>350</baseCost>
		<tab>FurnitureTinkering</tab>
		<techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
		<prerequisites><li>ComfyTechTierII</li></prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>2</researchViewX>
			<researchViewY>0</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<!--============== Table-fuu ==============-->

	<ResearchProjectDef>
		<defName>TableDesign</defName>
		<label>Tables Designs</label>
		<description>After a long debate about the meaning of life and threat assessment of the squirrels, one colonist decided to develop new table types, so they don't need to chat so often, or in most cases, at all.
		
With this research, your colonists won't need to share coffee cups.</description>
		<baseCost>100</baseCost>
		<tab>FurnitureTinkering</tab>
		<techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
		<prerequisites><li>ComfyTech</li></prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>1</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

</Defs>