<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <packageId>RabiSquare.RealisticOreGeneration</packageId>
    <name>[SR]Realistic Ore Generation</name>
    <author>Shadowrabbit,engager6,3HST有限公司</author>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.3</li>
        <li>1.4</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
        <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
        <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
        <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
    </loadAfter>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
    <description>        Did you ever used the vanilla long range scanner and found it silly that is's just placing ore lump on the open guarded by mechanoids? Had you ever thought why all rimworld's world map tiles have exactly the source resource distributions? If you did, then Realistic Ore generation is a mod for you. Mod overhauls vanilla resource generation mechanic and give more functionality to long range scanner.
        
        Now any world tile will have it's unique resource distribution for both: surface and underground ores, but now you can also find those from distance, using long range scanner functionality! Mod includes new world UI tile info tab showing you the resource distributions if this data is available. Another big change is change in the deep scanner, that will no longer be able to generate endless lumps of any resource: deep resources will now be exaustible taking more and more time to deep scanner find them, until that will become completely unreasonable.

        Now you will have more reason to do some world map interaction: set up mining outposts on rare undergroud resource deposits, sending out mining expeditions to scavenge world tiles for mineable gold, e.t.c. Mod can also be a used for ramping up difficulty and realism, by making resources globaly scarce, turning world map interaction and expeditions to a necessity for survival or sustained tech development.

        Realistic Ore generation contains a range of customisation settings allowing player to set up resource generation in way he wants and, also, fully suports new resources and ores added by other excellent mods, like Vanilla Materials expanded - metals or Gemstones.  Give a big shout to ShadowRabbit for his excellent work!
    </description>
</ModMetaData>