<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>A RimWorld of Magic - Psionic Lich</name>
	<author>NetzachSloth</author>
	<url/>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>NetzachSloth.ARoM.PsionicLich</packageId>
	<description>Psionic Lich: Psionic liches are undead psionics users—usually psions, but sometimes psionic monsters—who have interred their mentality into the necrotic tissue of their once-living bodies, thus preserving their existence indefinitely.

A psionic lich appears in some ways as it did in life: Its flesh remains pliant, soft, and warm to the touch. However, it has no heart, and no blood flows through its veins—it is psionic power that animates the flesh. If you cut a psionic lich, its veins are empty of blood, though stray sparks of power flash briefly. Its eyes are always completely silvered and glowing with a faint radiance. A psionic lich wears clothing for simple modesty or disguise, not to protect it from the environment. Thus, many wear only simple leggings, tunics, and sandals, if that. Psionic liches speak Common plus any other languages they knew in life.

After performing the ritual, the pawn will be rendered unconscious for a few days while the transformation takes place.

(source: https://phaeselis.fandom.com/wiki/Psionic_Lich )
(source: https://www.d20pfsrd.com/bestiary/monster-listings/undead/ )
(source: https://phaeselis.fandom.com/wiki/Psion )

For class abilities, I picked things that I thought fit both the psionic lich and psion pages listed above.

I chose a little bit from each scion specialty; generalist is a thing.

Clairsentience: Prediction
Metacreativity: Philosopher's Stone
Psychokinesis: Psionic blast and psionic barrier
Psychometabolism: Shadow and Augmentation (For this one, I might replace Shadow with Bestow Might)
Psychoportation: Blink and Summon
Telepathy: They get bonuses to social, negotiation, and trade. (With ideology they also get bonuses to conversion and suppression)

Psionic Lich: Life steal is similar to their negative energy touch attack. Shroud and Wave of Fear for the psionic lich's fear aura. And Recall is learnable (from chronomancer scroll) as a way to mimic a Lich's phylactery.

They get penalties to both max mp and sp, and a slight resistance to magic; I might lower or raise these, I haven't decided. Right now, they're at 50 for the penalties, and 25 for the resistance.

They get +100% Phsyic Sensitivity; I might change this to 2x factor instead of the 100 point offset I currently have it on.

They are marked as undead, so fog of torment heals the Psionic Lich, and the Heal spells damage them.

Let me know what you think.

Uses Torann's A RimWorld of Magic - Custom Class Editor Add-on.
	</description>
	<modDependencies/>
	<loadBefore/>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
		<li>jecrell.jecstools</li>
		<li>Torann.ARimworldOfMagic</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>