<ModMetaData>
	<name>Dune Equipment</name>
	<author>Between The Borders</author>
    <packageId>BetweenTheBorders.DuneEquipment</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.1</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>Equipment from the Dune Universe\n\n
NOTICE!!\n
If you are unfamiliar with the Dune universe, be advised that Lasgun + Shield = very bad day.\n\n

Some equipment for the Dune universe.\n\n

Crysknife: A Freman weapon made from the tooth of a worm, stabilized to not deteriorate in transit or storage. Can only be made from a worm's tooth, making it dependant on trading at this time.\n
Kindjal: A classic short blade familiar to any noble of the Landsraad.\n
Stillsuit: A suit designed to recycle water; when water is not an issue, it still provides unmatched protection from temperature.\n
Glowglobe: A general term, represented here by automated suspensor-equipped machines, which can be trained to follow a certain pawn, providing a mobile light source.\n
Lasgun: The lasgun used to be a primary weapon of militaries until the invention of the personal shield. The interaction of a lasgun and shield typically ends in an atomic reaction obliterating the target, the shooter, and anything around them.\n\n

The mechanisms behind the Glowglobes are clumsy, balance is still preliminary, and while the Glowglobes did not provide an appreciable performance hit in testing, I am still somewhat worried.\n\n

Hugslib requirement due to the mod options allowing people to turn Lasgun/Shield interactions on and off. I know people would've been disappointed on both sides if I made the decision for you\n
 
Suggestions for future content is welcome, I think I'm going to go back over the existing mods for a polish pass before I make anything new.\n\n


Thanks for all the support!\n\n

All RimWorld mod sources uploaded to https://github.com/faragher/ (but it may take a while after release)\n\n


Dune and all its related IPs are, of course, property of Frank Herbert, his descendants and licensees. No infringement intended, etc.  


</description>
	<url>https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561197980482234/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100</url>

<modDependencies>
	<li>
		<packageId>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</packageId>
		<displayName>HugsLib</displayName>
		<downloadUrl>https://github.com/UnlimitedHugs/RimworldHugsLib/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>
	</li>
</modDependencies>
<loadAfter>
	<li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>


