<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Kenshi Cuisine</name>
  <author>Supersonic</author>
  <packageId>Super.Kenshicuisine</packageId>
  <supportedVersions>
	<li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/AndroidQuazar/VanillaExpandedFramework</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
	</loadAfter>
  <description>Kenshi Cuisine!
This mod adds a great new variety of plants, food items, alcohol, and a new production chain for creating bread.

Should be compatible with other cooking mods, and able to be added / removed mid save if desired

Let's start from the ground up to understand how it all works

First , this adds a new terrain type "Tilled Sand" which will allow the player to create growing patches for wheatstraw and cactus on sand. It is 25% fertility, so it will not work for growing anything aside from the newly added wheatstraw and prickly pear cactus, or the vanilla saguaro cactus.

This mod also adds new plants, including Wheatstraw, Prickly Pear Cactus, and Greenfruit. Wheatstraw has little terrain sensitivity, and Prickly Pear Cactus has none. Greenfruit is highly sensitive to terrain fertility.

Once you've grown some wheatstraw, you can mill it into Strawflour at either a crafting spot, or butcher table. From there, you can insert it into either a wood fueled or electric powered bread oven. Bread can be eaten on its own, and is essentially an easily accessible analogue to nutrient paste (without as much nutrition efficiency). Cooked bread is also a reagant for our more advanced food items.

The advanced food items include food cubes, gohan, meatwraps, and dustwiches. All four of these food items will apply a well fed hediff of varying strength due to their high nutrition input cost.

This mod also adds two new alcohols, which are essentially analogues to beer, worth slightly less, and are a little bit easier to produce. Simply insert raw rice into a sake barrel, or raw wheatstraw into a grog barrel!</description>
</ModMetaData>