<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<DA1_Build_Titie.label>Statue of Teacher Old Li</DA1_Build_Titie.label>
<DA1_Build_Titie.description>This statue is engraved with the words "Chongqing No.8 Middle School Teacher Li Tie". This language is really obscure for us. However, we can still feel from this statue that this marginal artist named Dajian adores the sculpture figures. Similarly, this sculpture also gives us a unique aesthetic feeling from different planets. \n\nThe following is excerpted from Dajian's Diary: "a bright smile is full of loving care, and a strong voice shows its unique charm. Talking with Mr. Li Tie, you will be infected by his calm and modest temperament. "As a teacher, you should care for your students from the bottom of your heart and try your best to discover their potential." He has been teaching for more than 30 years. As the head of mathematics teaching and research group of Chongqing No.8 Middle School, senior teacher of middle school, one of the first batch of famous teachers in Chongqing, backbone teacher of Chongqing, and excellent teaching and research group leader of Chongqing, Mr. Li Tie said and even did so. " Brother tie, the eternal God!(just a joke for Leage of Legends in China.Don't take it seriously)</DA1_Build_Titie.description>

<DA1_Build_Litie_Working.label>Statue of Teacher Old Li(in sculpture)</DA1_Build_Litie_Working.label>
<DA1_Build_Litie_Working.description>The statue of Teacher Li Tie in sculpture. What you see now is the school emblem of Chongqing No.8 Middle School.</DA1_Build_Litie_Working.description>

<Da1_AliceType_A.label>Alice sculpture-A</Da1_AliceType_A.label>
<Da1_AliceType_A.description>Designer:Fox.\n\nThis sculpture depicts a beautiful girl. Unfortunately, businessmen in the rimworld can't appreciate this unique beauty, so it's not a wise choice to sell it. However, it's worth noting that when it's placed in a room, it seems to generate more aesthetic benefits than small sculptures of the same size. \n\nThe following comments are excerpted from an anonymous connoisseur named "group friends who ask for the whole life" (we don't find the meaning of this word in the edge Dictionary).\n\nwith light sadness, light yearning and deep missing, this Baroque exotic sculpture is surrounded by layers, gently touching the complex and regular patterns of the sculpture with fingertips Li, it seems that Lu Du is quietly knocking on a period of green time. Although Baroque's unique pursuit of luxury makes sculpture seem a little cumbersome, I see a kind of aristocratic elegance, a courage to break the rules. Closing my eyes and listening to the sculpture quietly, I seem to hear a beautiful music, the slow and comfortable melody around Liang Huan seems to be the artist's warm call for life thousands of years ago. The sound, long time can not be dispersed in the heart, melodious music overflowed every inch of my heart. It seems that it's not only a sculpture, but also a song. This song is rarely known in the marginal world. I have the honor to hear it in the music theater. It's called to Alice.\n\nBetween the notes and their concertos, it's not hard to hear that there is a series of special rhythms. Counting them carefully, 16 times of appearing in the high and low parts reappear a kind of delicate emotion. There seems to be a wonderful woman in the music. The algae like black hair is curled up with crystal lustrous hair ornaments, the lip color is moist like water, and the skin color of white snow is crimson, which seems to be broken by blowing. She leaned on the willow slender branches, catkins falling, she pursed her lips, read a piano score. Sometimes, the soft spring breeze disturbed her black silk. She still covered it lightly with her hands and looked through the music with a smile. She is beautiful and moving like spring, but there is no lack of shyness when spring comes quietly. Beethoven was worried, gone and thought about this woman. When he wrote this song to express his deep feelings, he had endless thoughts in his heart, such as the mellow and bitter coffee. I think, this sculpture, perhaps depicting the beauty of Alice. \n\nI don't think this is the beauty called "Earth". It should be the most brilliant light in the whole universe. I've been drunk in the deep call of a thousand years ago. Savor carefully, I realized the edge of the world, such as sculpture like cold temperature behind a trace of kindness, a trace of innocence.</Da1_AliceType_A.description>

<Da1_AliceType_B.label>>Alice sculpture-B</Da1_AliceType_B.label>
<Da1_AliceType_B.description>Type B for Alice sculpture</Da1_AliceType_B.description>

<Chi_Cooker.label>Chinese traditional fuel stoves</Chi_Cooker.label>
<Chi_Cooker.description>Through the advanced imitation technology made of efficient firewood stove, in the scientist big Jian's design, this kind of stove is very fuel saving, and can slightly improve the working speed. In addition, hay, combined fuel can also be used as fuel. In Dajian's diary, it is mentioned that this is a traditional cooking tool of "Earth China". In addition, the stove will convert some particles in the air into electric energy and store them in the internal battery. When there is no electric power supply, its internal power supply structure can also maintain its operation. However, due to the low power of the internal power supply structure, under such conditions, although the stove has a low power consumption, it is easy to operate However, it is still able to work, but the working speed is reduced by about 60% compared with the normal state.\n\nWe don't know which dust he referred to by "Earth" in the galaxy of stars, and the appearance of this stove is really strange. But such cooking equipment, even in the shining world, is an amazing invention.</Chi_Cooker.description>

<Chi_Cooker_New.label>Modern Chinese stoves</Chi_Cooker_New.label>
<Chi_Cooker_New.description>The modern Chinese stove made by advanced imitation technology is mentioned in Dajian's diary as a traditional cooking tool of "Earth China". Taking the traditional stove as the prototype, he improved the internal structure and work efficiency of the stove. At the same time, for the sake of environmental protection, the stove has also become an electric drive. \In addition, the stove will convert some particles in the air into electric energy and store them in the internal battery. When there is no power supply, the internal power supply structure can also maintain its operation. However, due to the low power of the internal power supply structure, the stove can still work under such conditions, but the working speed is reduced by 60% compared with the normal state about. \n\nWe don't know which dust he referred to by "Earth" in the galaxy of stars, and the appearance of this stove is really strange. But such cooking equipment, even in the shining world, is an amazing invention.</Chi_Cooker_New.description>

<Chi_RiceMaker_Old.label>Manual rice pestle</Chi_RiceMaker_Old.label>
<Chi_RiceMaker_Old.description>This is a traditional production tool used to husk rice. Driven by manpower, the shelf life of the husked and fermented glutinous rice flour is longer and its nutritional value is better than that of ordinary rice. At the same time, raw food and some raw materials can also be mashed and mixed here to form a hot pot base. It's worth mentioning that you can also mash some raw food into a slightly higher nutritional value, longer shelf life, lower poisoning rate, flammability and mood punishment. For example, potatoes can be mashed into potato powder here for preservation. \n\nBecause this kind of strange craft from the earth is not popular in the marginal world, the market value of these rough processed raw food is very low, but it is also a good way to control wealth. After all, it's right to use incense. \n\nIn the absence of power supply, the workers can also work by manpower, but the efficiency is lower than that of electric operation. In addition, the workers can also get good fighting benefits while working. (even if it's cooking, it's also individual work.) \Note: this job has low priority in cooking task, so it's better to assign a person to do it</Chi_RiceMaker_Old.description>

<Chi_RiceMaker.label>Electric rice pestle</Chi_RiceMaker.label>
<Chi_RiceMaker.description>This is a traditional production tool used to husk rice. Driven by the electric mechanical device, it can pass through. Its performance and efficiency are much higher than those of manual pestle. The shelf life of shelled and fermented glutinous rice flour is longer, and its nutritional value is better than that of ordinary rice. At the same time, raw food and some raw materials can also be mashed and mixed here to form a hot pot base. It's worth mentioning that you can also mash some raw food into a slightly higher nutritional value, longer shelf life, lower poisoning rate, flammability and mood punishment.\n\nFor example, potatoes can be mashed into potato powder here for preservation.</Chi_RiceMaker.description>

<Chi_BaoZiMaker.label>Chinese steamer</Chi_BaoZiMaker.label>
<Chi_BaoZiMaker.description>This steamer is used to make and cook steamed buns or baozi. The steamed buns and baozi often taste delicious, crisp, tender and juicy, and consumers can often get a strong sense of satiety, which can reduce their hunger rate for a period of time. Glutinous rice flour is also used to make steamed buns.\n\nSame as traditional stoves, they use water vapor in the air to extract a small amount of electricity to maintain their work in the absence of power supply, but the working speed is much slower than that of power on.</Chi_BaoZiMaker.description>

<Chi_RenRouMaker.label>Human flesh processor</Chi_RenRouMaker.label>
<Chi_RenRouMaker.description>This is a special machine used to eliminate the characteristics of human flesh. It can remove the peculiar smell of human flesh in a very short time and process it into a special kind of processed meat. The taste of this kind of meat is similar to that of pork. It tastes like pork. Even if it is eaten raw, it is not so easy to be poisoned, and the mood punishment is lower. \n\n"It's crazy, this device, why can someone make such a crazy thing, for...".. (bloodstain) "can work even without power supply, but the working speed is very slow. In addition, the market value of this device is relatively high and relatively expensive. Please use it carefully.</Chi_RenRouMaker.description>

<Chi_CiYao.label>Ceramic kiln</Chi_CiYao.label>
<Chi_CiYao.description>The manual records such ancient words: "ceramic kiln is made of refractory materials, which is used to burn products. It is a necessary facility in ceramic molding. With thousands of years of ceramic firing history, mankind has accumulated rich kiln making styles and technical experience. " \The following is excerpted from Dajian's Diary: "ha ha, these craftsmen in the marginal world don't know how advanced and durable the ceramic tiles and tiles made in ceramic kilns are! It's a pity that it's hard for me to get rid of these transmissions now, eh. " \n\nIt's hard to know who brought this thing here. It looks strange, maybe like a sphere. It should come from a different planet. Through further research, we found that we can forge rough cut stone bricks inside. Yes, the two materials are very good! \It can work even without power, but the working speed is very slow. After studying technology, you can make exquisite ceramic or porcelain pieces with stone bricks here. Believe me, it's much better than rough cut stone! \n\nIt should be noted that only quartz bricks can be forged and baked inside, but other stone bricks can also be transformed into quartz bricks with better performance after studying the stone brick conversion process.</Chi_CiYao.description>

<Chi_QingHuaCiA.label>Blue and white porcelain-A</Chi_QingHuaCiA.label>
<Chi_QingHuaCiA.description>A carefully designed and carved blue and white porcelain, which is fragile and valuable, can greatly enhance the beauty of the room.\n\nCan be placed on the table.</Chi_QingHuaCiA.description>

<Chi_QingHuaCiB.label>Blue and white porcelain-B</Chi_QingHuaCiB.label>
<Chi_QingHuaCiB.description>A carefully designed and carved blue and white porcelain, which is fragile and valuable, can greatly enhance the beauty of the room.\n\nCan be placed on the table.</Chi_QingHuaCiB.description>

<Chi_Pingfeng.label>Chinese classic screen</Chi_Pingfeng.label>
<Chi_Pingfeng.description>A classical decorative screen, can be connected together, very beautiful, can block the view, but can not be sold as a commodity (because it is too troublesome to carry.) \n\nThe following is an excerpt from Dajian's Diary: "nothing is more appropriate than putting a few screens in the spare space of the room."</Chi_Pingfeng.description>

<ShiYing.label>Quartzite</ShiYing.label>
<ShiYing.description>A kind of quartzite with low durability and easy mining. I don't know what caused the color of its rock shape to become so strange in the rimworld. \n\nQuartz is a mineral composed of silica with the chemical formula of SiO2. The pure quartz is colorless and transparent, and has various colors due to the presence of trace pigment ions, dispersed inclusions or color centers. The fracture surface is glassy and greasy. Hardness 7, no cleavage, shell fracture. 65. It is piezoelectric. \n\nIt's very possible to produce quartz block after mining. Don't forget that high school chemistry talked about the role of quartz and other silicate minerals in silicate block!</ShiYing.description>

<SmoothedShiYing.label>Smooth quartz</SmoothedShiYing.label>
<SmoothedShiYing.description>The polished quartzite is beautiful and generous. It's better than the original polished rock.</SmoothedShiYing.description>

<ChunkShiYing.label>Quartzite Chunk</ChunkShiYing.label>
<ChunkShiYing.description>Quartz is a kind of mineral that easily becomes liquid when heated or pressed. It is also a very common rock forming mineral, which can be found in all three types of rocks. Because it crystallizes the latest in igneous rocks, it usually lacks a complete crystal plane and is mostly filled in the middle of other pre crystallized rock forming minerals.\n\nIn 2145, with the help of a special geographical science and technology, it began to become a part of the rock layer of rimworld. We only know that this technology should have come from a planet called Earth. \n\nThis mineral looks beautiful, and even if it is placed indoors, it will not affect the beauty and cleanliness.</ChunkShiYing.description>

<BlocksShiYing.label>Fine Quartzite blocks</BlocksShiYing.label>
<BlocksShiYing.description>The color of the refined quartz after processing becomes a little strange due to the influence of the special environment of the edge world. Its beauty is better than the original stone, but the durability is slightly low and the protection performance is poor. It is suggested that it can be used as indoor building stone brick or further processed into porcelain in the kiln. \n\nThe processing time of the brick is a little longer, but the output is more, and the impact of indoor storage on the aesthetic is minimal. \n\nIn addition, businessmen in rimworld don't like this kind of thing from other planets, so don't expect to sell it. And the wealth value of this kind of goods is low. (of course, you can buy it) because of its excellent performance, the additional workload of the colonists in building or manufacturing with it as raw material would be slightly lower than that of the original stone brick. At the same time, because of its light weight, the opening speed of the door with it as the raw material will be faster, and the rest efficiency of the bed with it as the raw material will be better than that of the original stone bed. \n\nHowever, because of its material, it is not recommended to use it as a weapon, because the cooling time of weapons made of this material will be slower.</BlocksShiYing.description>
<BlocksShiYing.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>Quartz</BlocksShiYing.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>


<Chi_JingJuZhanTai.label>Beijing Opera projector</Chi_JingJuZhanTai.label>
<Chi_JingJuZhanTai.description>A Beijing Opera projector needs a lot of materials to build, and it is difficult to build. It has a unique projection function and influence function, and has a high degree of beauty. \n\nIt has two functions: the outer ring and the inner ring. When you are in the big circle of the outer ring, you can hear the beautiful tune of Beijing Opera and get a good mood. (as for the sound effects, I'm still trying to figure out how to do it) and the inner circle is a TV like viewing range, "put a chair here and then sit on it to enjoy our quintessence of Peking Opera." The artist Dajian wrote. In the inner circle, you can have an entertainment activity of "watching Beijing Opera", which is a new type of entertainment with high efficiency and full fun. \n\nBeijing opera, known as "National Opera", is widely spread throughout the country. The Peking opera performance system named after Mei Lanfang is regarded as the representative of the Oriental drama performance system and one of the three major performance systems in the world. Beijing Opera is an important form of traditional Chinese culture, in which a variety of artistic elements are used as symbols of traditional Chinese culture. \n\nAn artist named "Dajian" compiles its content into a video tape and makes it into a projector to spread it to the marginal world. Because Beijing Opera is very wonderful, you just need to sit down and watch it for a while to meet your entertainment needs. Enjoy it!</Chi_JingJuZhanTai.description>

<Chi_Tangyuan.label>Tangyuan</Chi_Tangyuan.label>
<Chi_Tangyuan.description>A bowl of well cooked TangYuan and it needs to be made on a traditional stove. Its nutritional value is slightly higher than the original exquisite food, and pawns will have a special mood after eating it. It is worth mentioning that people of any class will not refuse this delicious food. \n\nTangyuan, also known as "tangtuan" and "fuyuanzi", is one of the representatives of traditional snacks of Han nationality. The skin of Tangyuan is made of glutinous rice flour. The white glutinous rice flour can nourish the lung, which is suitable for the five color tonic theme of "white nourishing the lung". So after enjoying the dumplings, you can get a small breathing and movement bonus. At the same time, tangyuan is also the most characteristic food of Chinese Traditional Festival Lantern Festival, which expresses the ancient people's yearning and expectation for a happy life. \n\nHey, don't just enjoy the delicious dumplings, remember to go home often!</Chi_Tangyuan.description>

<WorkedRawRice.label>glutinous rice flour</WorkedRawRice.label>
<WorkedRawRice.description>Glutinous rice flour is the main raw material of traditional dishes such as dumplings and steamed buns, and can also be used as the raw material of other cooking foods.</WorkedRawRice.description>

<WorkedRawPotato.label>Dried potatoes</WorkedRawPotato.label>
<WorkedRawPotato.description>This is a kind of potato jerky made by pressing, pounding and drying in the pestle. It is easy to keep and has a long shelf life.\n\nAlthough the market value of potato jerky is low, it is a good choice to make potato jerky if you want to suppress wealth and save food.</WorkedRawPotato.description>

<WorkedRawMaize.label>Dried corn</WorkedRawMaize.label>
<WorkedRawMaize.description>This is a kind of corn jerky made by pressing, pounding and drying in the pestle. It is easy to keep and has a long shelf life.\n\nAlthough the market value of corn jerky is low, if you want to suppress wealth and save food, it is a good choice to make corn jerky.</WorkedRawMaize.description>

<WorkedRawMixture.label>Mixed plant stems</WorkedRawMixture.label>
<WorkedRawMixture.description>A mixture of raw plant stems, mashed in a pestle and dried in the air. It serves as a raw vegetarian and has the same nutritional value as the same raw food, but it has a longer shelf life and you can sell it wholesale for a big profit.</WorkedRawMixture.description>

<DaJian_LaoGanMa.label>Old Godmother</DaJian_LaoGanMa.label>
<DaJian_LaoGanMa.description>Dajian wrote in his diary: "it saved me! It's it, it's it, my hero, godmother! Every time I find the food in the canteen hard to swallow, I will have a spoonful, my faith! Well, yes, I don't eat chili, but it doesn't prevent me from eating old godmother! " \n\nThis unique product needs spicy oil as raw material, which can be planted on the land. The market value of Laoganma is fair, with a long shelf life, and it can replace meat as the raw material for cooking food. Colonists will have a special mood after enjoying the food containing Laoganma ingredients. \n\nIn 1984, with her unique frying technology, Ms. Tao Huabi introduced a unique flavor of food seasoning, which made the majority of customers enjoy talking about. After mass production in 1996, it quickly became a sales hot spot in China. Laoganma is the largest hot pepper production enterprise in China. It mainly produces more than 20 series products, such as flavor Douchi, flavor chicken oil hot pepper, spicy vegetables, flavor sufu, etc. In 2135, it was brought to the edge world by the artist Dajian, and soon the old godmother became popular all over the planet. \n\nIn addition, because long-term consumption of Laoganma is easy to lead to uric acid, the priority of Laoganma as meat raw material will be lower when choosing raw materials for work.</DaJian_LaoGanMa.description>

<LaJiao.label>Spicy oil</LaJiao.label>
<LaJiao.description>This is the harvested spicy oil, which can be sold or further processed into old godmother. Although it can be eaten raw under necessary conditions, it tastes bad, believe me.</LaJiao.description>

<ChuLiRou.label>Processed meat</ChuLiRou.label>
<ChuLiRou.description>This is processed meat by human meat processing machine. It tastes better raw than ordinary meat, but it can provide slightly lower nutritional value than the original meat. \n\nThe following is excerpted from Dajian's Diary: "my wish is world peace, no more killing and war."</ChuLiRou.description>

<Chi_Huntun.label>Wonton</Chi_Huntun.label>
<Chi_Huntun.description>A bowl of wonton cooked elaborately warms your heart in the chilly winter. It needs to be made on a traditional stove. Its nutritional value is equal to that of luxury food, and villains will have special mood and health benefits after eating it. Even the top princes and nobles would not refuse the temptation of this kind of food. \Wonton is one of the traditional pasta of the Han nationality in China. It is filled with thin flour and usually cooked with soup. It comes from the north of China. Wonton is rich in nutrition, sweet in fragrance, unique flavor and appetizing. It's said in ancient times that it can suppress ghosts and evils. In fact, the combination of chaos skin and stuffing, meat and vegetable is reasonable. It has the effect of calming the nerves and calming the nerves. It is more nutritious and suitable for all ages. Therefore, after eating wonton, there will be a small conscious addition. \n\nDumplings and wonton are round and round in every festival. I hope you don't forget their original meaning!</Chi_Huntun.description>

<Chi_JiaoZi.label>dumplings</Chi_JiaoZi.label>
<Chi_JiaoZi.description>A bowl of well cooked dumplings can warm your heart in the chilly winter. It needs to be made on a traditional stove. Its nutritional value is equal to that of luxury food, and villains will have special mood and health benefits after eating it. Even the top princes and nobles would not refuse the temptation of this kind of food. \n\nJiaozi originated from jiaozi in ancient times. Jiaoer, formerly known as Jiaoer, is an ancient traditional pasta of the Han nationality. It has a history of more than 1800 years. Zhang Zhongjing, who was born in Dengzhou, Nanyang in Eastern Han Dynasty, first invented it as a medicine. It is a kind of traditional food, also known as dumpling, which is deeply loved by the Chinese people. It is a staple food and local snack in northern China, and also a festival food. There is a folk song called "big cold, small cold, eat dumplings for the new year.". "Dumplings are usually made of dough and water. \Dumplings and wonton are round and round in every festival. I hope you don't forget their original meaning!</Chi_JiaoZi.description>

<Chi_RouBaoZi.label>Baozi</Chi_RouBaoZi.label>
<Chi_RouBaoZi.description>A super large meat bun, edge artist Dajian once described: "this kind of bun and steamed bread are essential for the student party like me to have a full stomach in the morning. Although the steamed bun in the canteen is just like that, it's full! After all, time is too short for me to enjoy it \n\nAfter eating steamed stuffed bun, pawns will have a sense of fullness plus. Steamed stuffed bun is a staple food with strong sense of fullness, and it is also an indispensable food in people's life. It is wrapped by noodles and stuffing, or made of plain stuffing. The prepared steamed stuffed bun has thin skin, lots of stuffing, soft and delicious. You can also make all kinds of patterns. Charmingly naive, animal, plant, flower, all kinds of patterns, for people to taste.</Chi_RouBaoZi.description>

<Chi_ManTou.label>Steamed buns</Chi_ManTou.label>
<Chi_ManTou.description>A super large steamed bread, edge artist Dajian once described: "this kind of steamed bun and steamed bread are necessary for the student party like me to have a full stomach in the morning. Although the steamed bread in the canteen is just like that, it's full! After all, time is too short for me to enjoy it.\n\nPawns will have a satiety bonus after enjoying steamed bread\n\nSteamed bread, also known as "ManTou", "Mo" and "MoMo", is one of the traditional Chinese pasta. It is said that it was invented by Zhuge Liang, Prime Minister of Shu Han in the Three Kingdoms. It is a kind of food steamed with fermented flour. Steamed bread with wheat flour as the main raw material is one of the staple food of Chinese people.</Chi_ManTou.description>

<Chi_HuoGuo.label>HotPot</Chi_HuoGuo.label>
<Chi_HuoGuo.description>A delicious hot pot that can be kept at the internal temperature after being processed and then ready to eat needs to be made in a traditional stove. \n\nThe edge artist BenLong wrote on its stone carving: "yes, hot pot is delicious, but I hope there will be more clear soup. The area of Yuanyang pot will be larger and people will be thinner." \n\nThe villain has a good mood and health bonus after enjoying the hot pot. \n\nHot pot is called "antique soup" in ancient times. It gets its name from the sound of "Gudong" when food is put into boiling water. It is an original Chinese food with a long history and suitable for all ages. According to textual research, there was hot pot in the Warring States period, when people used pottery pots as pots. By the Song Dynasty, the way of eating hot pot was very common among the people. In the recipe of shanjiaqinggong written by Lin Hong in the Southern Song Dynasty, there was an introduction of eating hot pot with friends. In the Yuan Dynasty, hot pot spread to Mongolia and was used to cook beef and mutton. By the Qing Dynasty, hot pot was not only popular among the people, but also became a famous "palace dish" made of pheasant and other game.</Chi_HuoGuo.description>

<Chi_BaoBing.label>Chinese Griddle Cake</Chi_BaoBing.label>
<Chi_BaoBing.description>A pancake with meat or vegetables. It looks small, but it's absolutely full. After enjoying, I have a good mood and a small amount of blood circulation bonus. Can meet the needs of any class except the count. \n\n"Every time I see pancakes, I will drool, even though I have just finished my meal," the marginal artist Dajian wrote in his diary \n\nIn the past, pancakes used to be the festival food of Qingming Festival. On the morning of Qingming Festival, they went up to the mountain to worship their ancestors, and after they came home, they were very popular, People always use pancakes as lunch, and their material life is diversified. Influenced by the custom of ancestor worship in Hong Kong, people prepare sacrifices such as "roast golden pig", "roast duck", "roast goose" and "cake".</Chi_BaoBing.description>

<Chi_ChaoFan.label>Fried rice with egg</Chi_ChaoFan.label>
<Chi_ChaoFan.description>An egg fried rice, although it is called "egg" fried rice, you can also make meat fried rice and vegetable fried rice. It has simple combination and rich collocation. Like pancakes, you have a good mood and a small amount of blood circulation bonus after enjoying, which can meet the needs of any class except the count. \"Fried rice with eggs is my love!" wrote the marginal artist Dajian in his diary Although we don't know what "love" means, we can feel the artist's fanatical worship of "fried rice with eggs" from the lines. \n\nFried rice with eggs is a common dish. The earliest records can be found on the bamboo slips unearthed from Mawangdui Han tomb in Changsha, Hunan Province in 1972. According to the research of experts, "egg cot" is a kind of food made of sticky rice and eggs. Some people speculate that this may be the predecessor of egg fried rice. Eggs are rich in protein, not only that, but also vitamin A and B.</Chi_ChaoFan.description>

<Plant_LaJiao.label>Capsicum oleiferum</Plant_LaJiao.label>
<Plant_LaJiao.description>This is a kind of spicy oil crop, which can be harvested after maturity. It is a necessary material for making old godmother.</Plant_LaJiao.description>

<Plant_YinXing.label>ginkgo tree</Plant_YinXing.label>
<Plant_YinXing.description>Ginkgo biloba is a deciduous tree of ginkgo family. Ginkgo biloba appeared hundreds of millions of years ago. It is the oldest relict plant among gymnosperms left behind by the Quaternary glacial movement. The living Ginkgo biloba is rare and scattered. There are few old trees over 100 years old. All other plants of the same class have been extinct. Therefore, Ginkgo biloba has the reputation of living fossil. There are 26 varieties and varieties: Ginkgo biloba, Ginkgo biloba, Ginkgo biloba, Ginkgo biloba and so on. \n\nThis kind of tree was brought to rimworld by the "China tree research" spacecraft in 2123 ad. it is a kind of "living fossil" tree with high cost performance, and has been widely used in edge forestry. They usually grow in temperate and frigid forests.</Plant_YinXing.description>

<Plant_WuTong.label>Wutong tree</Plant_WuTong.label>
<Plant_WuTong.description>Wutong China, Wutong, Wutong, a plant of the genus Indus, alias Wutong, Tung Ma, also belong to large deciduous trees, up to 15 meters, trunk straight, bark green, smooth. It is native to China and cultivated in all provinces. \n\n Wutong grows fast and looks good. Wood is suitable for making musical instruments. Bark can be used for paper making and ropes, seeds can be eaten or pressed (of course not in games). Because of its smooth trunk and beautiful leaves, it is a famous ornamental tree species. China's ancient legend that Phoenix "non Wutong does not live". Wutong Wutong is a popular form of China's ancient culture. Feng Zikai's homonym "Wutong tree" is a good article. Wutong has been introduced to many countries such as Europe and America as ornamental tree species. \n\nIn 2135 ad, it was spread to rimworld by the scientific research ship "first love" (as for why it is called "first love", it is said that it is related to a man named Dajian). Now it is distributed in temperate and frigid forests.</Plant_WuTong.description>

<CiPian.label>Porcelain bricks</CiPian.label>
<CiPian.description>This is a ceramic piece made by firing stone bricks, and it will not affect the aesthetics when stored indoors. People in the fringe world usually like to think of it as a usable precious metal material.\n\nThis material is light, beautiful and fireproof, and it has strong air permeability. However, it will appear extremely fragile in the face of external impact, and the durability of articles made of it is low, but it is suitable as a material for indoor construction, because the building made of it is easy to construct and has high aesthetics. At the same time, this is also the raw material for blue and white porcelain vase decoration.\n\nIf necessary, it can also be processed into sharp and fragile melee weapons. As a dagger, its attack speed is even faster than fiberglass.</CiPian.description>
<CiPian.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>Porcelain bricks</CiPian.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>

<MineableCiPian.label>Buried Porcelain bricks</MineableCiPian.label>
<MineableCiPian.description>There used to be a huge ceramic building buried in this place, but it has been turned into a pile of tiles under the erosion of sand. You can get some useful tiles by mining this kind of mineral.</MineableCiPian.description>

<BlocksTaoZhuan.label>Pottery bricks</BlocksTaoZhuan.label>
<BlocksTaoZhuan.description>This is a ceramic brick. It is made of stone bricks in a ceramic kiln. Its architectural performance is better than that of ordinary stone bricks and quartz bricks. The bed made of it can also get a small increase in rest efficiency. It is a relatively excellent structural brick. Of course, you can also use it as furniture. Even if it doesn't look as charming as porcelain, it's easy to make pottery Single, full of historical beauty. \n\nLike ordinary stone bricks, they can't be used for sale (because no one uses them in the marginal world). \n\nthe following is excerpted from Dajian's Diary: "if one day these tribesmen can learn to use pottery, they won't be so backward. I really don't know what they are thinking, primitive and barbaric." \n\nLike quartz brick, it is not recommended to be used as weapon material because of its material characteristics. At the same time, the construction time using it as building material is relatively short, and the durability and aesthetics are also improved. \n\nSame as quartz brick, it has a lower wealth value, so it is not a very "dangerous" thing to store a large number of such bricks.</BlocksTaoZhuan.description>
<BlocksTaoZhuan.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>Pottery</BlocksTaoZhuan.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>


<PanDa_Leather.label>Panda leather</PanDa_Leather.label>
<PanDa_Leather.description>It's panda skin. Its thermal insulation performance is acceptable. Its beauty and market value are very high, almost equal to that of striking animal skin. However, this kind of panda skin is also very rare and has poor protection performance. It is not recommended to be used as armor..\n\nYou'd better not hunt rare wild animals, or something bad will happen.\n\nNo business, no killing,remember that.</PanDa_Leather.description>

<AEXP_Panda.label>Temperate giant panda</AEXP_Panda.label>
<AEXP_Panda.description>This strange and intelligent creature was brought to the edge world by a group of spaceships called "Chinese foreigners" in 2100 ad, and multiplied in the edge world. \n\nThe giant panda is the only mammal in Carnivora, Ursidae, giant panda subfamily and giant panda genus. Its body color is black and white. It has round cheeks, big black circles, chubby body, eight character walking style and sharp claws like a scalpel. It's one of the most lovely animals in the world. \n\nThe giant panda has a high IQ and a slow forgetting speed after training. However, due to its precious meat and leather, it is often hunted and killed by human beings in the marginal world, and now it is on the verge of extinction. No business, no killing. Please treat giant pandas kindly!</AEXP_Panda.description>
<AEXP_Panda.race.meatLabel>Panda meat</AEXP_Panda.race.meatLabel>

<PanDa_JiDi.label>Polar Panda</PanDa_JiDi.label>
<PanDa_JiDi.description>This is a polar variant of giant pandas. We don't know how they evolved to a state that can adapt to polar regions, but it is undeniable that they hardly need food and are extremely cold-resistant. In addition, its fighting ability is stronger than ordinary pandas. Hey, don't mess with it!</PanDa_JiDi.description>
<PanDa_JiDi.race.meatLabel>Panda meat</PanDa_JiDi.race.meatLabel>

<PanDa_ReDai.label>Tropical panda</PanDa_ReDai.label>
<PanDa_ReDai.description>This is a tropical variant of the giant panda. Facts have proved that the giant panda has a strong ability to evolve. The fringe biologist Frolg first discovered this kind of hair in a place called "Stupid Dragon Fox Rainforest" in 2341. But creatures that are similar in appearance and habits to the giant panda but are different. \n\nThrough some mutation, this creature has a larger appetite and can digest all kinds of food. In addition, its fighting ability cannot be underestimated, and some people think that it is the most powerful species in the panda family. \n\nBecause it has less hair, it is not a wise choice to keep it in places such as ice fields. \n\nYou will definitely ask why this creature grows a kind of horns. This is really strange. According to a reporter named "Udon", it may be that Frolg has mutated and modified this species. But who knows.</PanDa_ReDai.description>
<PanDa_ReDai.race.meatLabel>Panda meat</PanDa_ReDai.race.meatLabel>

<RongYuan.label>Rim Salamander</RongYuan.label>
<RongYuan.description>Salamanders are also known as salamanders. There are about 400 species of salamanders in the world, belonging to 10 families under the order Curidae. Salamanders are tailed amphibians, similar in body shape to lizards, but without scales on the body, and are also good ornamental animals, including northern newts, salamanders, and large cryptic salamanders (a large aquatic salamander). Most of them inhabit freshwater and marsh areas, mainly temperate regions of the northern hemisphere. They rely on their skin to absorb moisture, so they need a humid living environment. After the environment reaches below zero degrees Celsius, they will enter a state of hibernation. \n\nCan tolerate colder climates and is slightly larger than the baby fish, which may be specially affected by the edge world. They have the same fighting ability as large lizards and need to eat almost the same food. They are commonly found in wet swamp areas. Forest areas are also distributed in small amounts. \n\n(A "hibernating" health status will be updated later), the newt has been breeding for several years after being taken to the fringe world by a scientist named "Domaru" in 2278. In addition, they can live up to a hundred years.</RongYuan.description>

<WaWaYu.label>Giant Salamander</WaWaYu.label>
<WaWaYu.description>Giant salamander (commonly known as baby fish) is a tailed amphibian of the Cryptogillidae family and the genus Giant salamander. It is large and flat, with a total length of 582 to 834 mm and a head and body length of 310 to 585 mm. The maximum length can reach more than 200 cm. The head is large, flat and broad, and the head length is slightly larger than the head width. Adult salamanders usually live in caves and stone caves in deep pools of streams and rivers below 1000 meters above sea level. They are more common in caves above and below the beach mouth. They have a wide range of feeding habits, mainly crabs, frogs, fish, shrimps and aquatic insects. , And its larvae for food. \n\nIt is mainly distributed in humid swamps, but in order to adapt to different climates, this animal seems to have developed heat tolerance in the fringe world and may appear in the desert.</WaWaYu.description>

<JinSiMonkey.label>Golden monkey</JinSiMonkey.label>
<JinSiMonkey.description>The golden snub-nosed monkey has soft hair and an upturned nose. There are 6 species of Burmese snub-nosed monkey, Nujiang snub-nosed monkey, Sichuan golden snub-nosed monkey, Yunnan golden snub-nosed monkey, Qian golden snub-nosed monkey, and Vietnamese golden snub-nosed monkey. Except for the Burmese golden monkey and the Vietnamese golden monkey, they are all rare animals unique to China. . \n\nGolden snub-nosed monkeys live in dense alpine forests. They feed on wild fruits, bamboo shoots, and moss. They also like to eat meat such as bird eggs. The habitat is high above sea level, and the long hairs on the body can be cold-resistant. The 6 species are all rare and endangered species on the Red Species List. \n\nIn the game, the golden monkey is also a high IQ, omnivorous and precious animal. Brought to the marginal world by the "Earth Golden Monkey Protection" spacecraft in 2357 AD, the golden monkeys have gained a broader habitat and are reborn as a result. It is easy to tame and does not eat much, but it is weaker than ordinary monkeys. Please take care to protect it! \n\nThe comfortable temperature of the golden monkey is between 0 and 35 degrees. Please be careful to keep it warm or cold.\n\nMarket value is also a connotation.(A player in Leage of Legends,he was in LPL,konwn as "clearlove")</JinSiMonkey.description>

<EggWaWaYu.label>Eggs of giant salamander (unfertilized)</EggWaWaYu.label>
<EggWaWaYu.description>The eggs of the giant salamander are unfertilized and precious. They can be eaten raw, but the taste is poor.</EggWaWaYu.description>

<EggShouJingWaWaYu.label>Eggs of giant salamander (fertilized)</EggShouJingWaWaYu.label>
<EggShouJingWaWaYu.description>The eggs of the giant salamander have been fertilized and are more precious. If all goes well, it should be able to hatch a giant salamander larva. It can be eaten raw, but it tastes bad.</EggShouJingWaWaYu.description>

<EggRongYuan.label>Salamander eggs (unfertilized)</EggRongYuan.label>
<EggRongYuan.description>Salamander eggs are unfertilized and precious. They can be eaten raw, but they taste bad.</EggRongYuan.description>

<EggShouJingRongYuan.label>Salamander eggs (fertilized)</EggShouJingRongYuan.label>
<EggShouJingRongYuan.description>The eggs of the salamander have been fertilized and are more precious. If all goes well, it should be able to hatch a salamander larvae. It can be eaten raw, but it tastes bad.</EggShouJingRongYuan.description>

<EggHongJinJi.label>Red belly brocade eggs (unfertilized)</EggHongJinJi.label>
<EggHongJinJi.description>This is the egg of an unfertilized golden pheasant whose market value is slightly higher than that of ordinary eggs. It can be eaten raw, but it tastes bad.</EggHongJinJi.description>

<EggShouJingHongJinJi.label>Red belly brocade eggs (fertilized)</EggShouJingHongJinJi.label>
<EggShouJingHongJinJi.description>This is the egg of golden pheasant that has been fertilized, and its market value is higher than that of ordinary eggs. If all goes well, it should be able to hatch a golden pheasant larva. It can be eaten raw, but I suggest you cook it a little bit.</EggShouJingHongJinJi.description>

<HongJinJi.label>Golden Pheasant (wild)</HongJinJi.label>
<HongJinJi.description>Golden pheasant, also known as golden chicken, is a medium-sized chicken with a body length of 59-110cm. The tail is very long, about 38-42cm. The male bird has a gorgeous feather color and a golden yellow silk crown on the head. The upper body is golden yellow except for the dark green on the back. The back neck is covered with orange-brown fan-shaped feathers with black edges, forming a shawl-like shape. The lower body is dark red, and the tail feathers are dark brown, covered with laurel yellow spots. The female bird's head and neck are dark brown, and the rest of the body feathers are brownish yellow, covered with dark brown insect-like spots and horizontal spots. The feet are yellow. The characteristics of the wild are very obvious. The plumage colors complement each other. The red, orange, yellow, green, blue and purple are full of brilliance. It is a well-known ornamental bird at home and abroad. It is an endemic bird species in China. The core area of ​​the species distribution is in the Qinling area of ​​Gansu and southern Shaanxi, China. \n\nIt was brought to the fringe world by the "Livestock" spacecraft in 2340 and became a native species, and its cost-effectiveness was higher than other livestock animals. \n\nThis kind of chicken also appears in the wild. It usually appears in areas with mild climates. It can also be raised as a livestock. The food intake is slightly larger than that of domestic chickens, but the egg production and slaughter meat volume are much higher. In addition, don't underestimate the combat effectiveness of their groups! \n\nThe wild golden pheasant needs to be fertilized to lay eggs. It is difficult to domesticate it as a domestic chicken that does not lay eggs.</HongJinJi.description>

<TuJi.label>Chinese native chicken</TuJi.label>
<TuJi.description>Chinese native chicken, a kind of poultry. Different from caged broilers. Among them, the "hillside free-range chicken" is the best. The rooster has a large and red crest and is aggressive and aggressive, and the hen has a very small crest.\n\nNative chickens are also called grass chickens and dumb chickens. They are domesticated and domesticated from ancient times. They have never undergone any crossbreeding or optimized breeding. They have been fed by natural foraging or combined with rough feeding for a long time. They have strong wild foraging and survival ability. . It has the characteristics of resistance to rough feeding, strong nesting and disease resistance, and the meat is delicious. Eggs are very popular in urban and rural markets, and the price of eggs is also higher than that of ordinary eggs, with high nutritional value. The chicken tastes delicious, the egg quality is excellent, and the nutrition is rich, and the market demand prospects are broad. And because most of them are stocked in forests or orchards, which are closer to the requirements of green and environmental protection, they are more favored by consumers. For farmers who have certain conditions, the cost of raising chai chicken is relatively low, and it is suitable for family breeding. The cycle is longer, generally about 6 months in adulthood. \n\nChina is the first country in the world to raise chickens. As far back as the Neolithic Age, archaeologists discovered the skeletons of original chickens, which have a history of 7,000 years. In the oracle bone inscriptions unearthed in Yinxu, there are also the words "chicken" and "chi", which are the pictophonetic characters "xi" next to the "bird", which means the bird holding the rope. \n\nThis kind of creature will not appear in the wild. After long-term cultivation, this kind of native chicken has more meat than ordinary chickens and has a higher egg-laying profit. But this kind of chicken is very popular in the market, so their price is not low.</TuJi.description>
     
<EggTuJi.label>Soil eggs (unfertilized)</EggTuJi.label>
<EggTuJi.description>This is an unfertilized native egg. The market price is similar to that of a regular egg. It can be eaten raw, but the taste is poor.</EggTuJi.description>

<EggShouJingTuJi.label>Soil eggs (fertilized)</EggShouJingTuJi.label>
<EggShouJingTuJi.description>This is a fertilized native egg, and the market price is similar to that of an ordinary egg. If all goes well, it should be able to hatch a native chicken larva. It can be eaten raw, but I suggest you cook it a little bit.</EggShouJingTuJi.description>

<SZ_MaJiangZhuo.label>Mahjong table</SZ_MaJiangZhuo.label>
<SZ_MaJiangZhuo.description>An entertainment facility unique to China. It is affected by its quality and has better aesthetics. It provides a new type of entertainment: playing mahjong. At the same time, it provides a higher entertainment effect. Your villain will love this entertainment! \n\nMahjong is a kind of puzzle game invented by the Han nationality. Mahjong is a kind of entertainment equipment. It is a small rectangular box made of bamboo, bone or plastic, with patterns or words engraved on it. Each set is 136 pieces. The four-person domino game is popular in the Chinese cultural circle. The rules of the game are slightly different in different regions. Mahjong's card styles mainly include "bing (wenqian)", "tiao (suozi)", "wan (wanguan)" and so on. In ancient times, mahjong was mostly made of bone and bamboo back. It can be said that mahjong tiles are actually a combination of playing cards and dominoes. Compared with other forms of dominoes, Mahjong’s gameplay is the most complicated and interesting. Its basic gameplay is simple and easy to use, but there are many variations. The combination and combination vary from person to person, making it one of the most attractive in Chinese history. One of the forms of gambling.</SZ_MaJiangZhuo.description>

<Chi_ChuiGuJi.label>Grain blower</Chi_ChuiGuJi.label>
<Chi_ChuiGuJi.description>A grain blowing machine, which is usually used to hull rice to make it millet. This kind of machine is usually operated by hand and is widely used in rural areas. At the same time, its design has a certain degree of appreciation. But with the development of the times, this ancient machine has gradually faded out of people's field of vision. \n\nFortunately, in the fringe world, this kind of machine has been well preserved and used. After improving the internal structure, this kind of machine has also given new vitality. \n\nIn addition, when this machine is used in conjunction with the pounding rice pestle, the work efficiency of the pounding rice pestle can be improved. Eating crude glutinous rice flour is not a good thing.</Chi_ChuiGuJi.description>

<Leather_DongBeiHu.label>South China tiger skin</Leather_DongBeiHu.label>
<Leather_DongBeiHu.description>The skin of South China tiger. I don't suggest you kill this rare animal to get its skin. After all, "man is doing it, and heaven is watching it." But it is undeniable that its skin is very precious and can provide a certain degree of cold resistance, that is, its air permeability is not very good, so its heat resistance is poor</Leather_DongBeiHu.description>

<LaoHu_HuaNan.label>Southern China tiger</LaoHu_HuaNan.label>
<LaoHu_HuaNan.description>As an endangered alien species introduced to the rimworld, because the ecological environment of the marginal world has not been destroyed on a large scale and there are abundant animal communities, this kind of animal, which is almost extinct on the earth, is reborn here. \n\nThe head of South China tiger is round, the ears are short, the limbs are thick and powerful, the tail is long, the chest and abdomen are mixed with many milky white, the whole body is orange yellow and covered with black horizontal lines. There are short and narrow stripes on the fur, the spacing of stripes is larger than that of Bengal tiger and Siberian tiger, and diamond stripes often appear on the body side. \Different from its close relative, Amur tiger, it is smaller and can tolerate hotter environment, but it is not as cold tolerant as Amur tiger. \n\nIn the wild, it is a rare but dangerous predator, and its combat ability cannot be underestimated.</LaoHu_HuaNan.description>
<LaoHu_HuaNan.race.meatLabel>Southern China tiger meat</LaoHu_HuaNan.race.meatLabel>

<MaJiangYi.label>Song dynasty long cane chair</MaJiangYi.label>
<MaJiangYi.description>A traditional Chinese rattan chair that can provide high comfort and a certain degree of beauty. Generally used with mahjong tables, Peking opera projectors or other entertainment facilities and can improve the entertainment effectiveness of these entertainment facilities. Of course, it is also a good choice to put it in other places (such as at the dining table). \n\nThe materials, handwork and technology of rattan weaving are mainly based on traditional Chinese craftsmanship, making rattan products full of ancient southern style, less modern style, and usually more popular among middle-aged people. Wicker chairs are not only simple but not lacking in taste, but also emphasize the artistry in their shapes. Representative Chinese peacock-shaped, chicken-heart-shaped, sun-shaped and other wicker chairs are typical. \n\nSpecific entertainment facilities used in conjunction with wicker chairs can make up to four wicker chairs in the range to provide them with entertainment bonuses.</MaJiangYi.description>

<AiJiu.label>moxa stick</AiJiu.label>
<AiJiu.description>Moxibustion, the moxibustion method in traditional Chinese acupuncture therapy, is a natural remedy that ignites moxa sticks and moxa sticks made from moxa leaves, and smokes and roasts the acupoints of the human body to achieve health care and cure diseases. Moxibustion sticks can be made in a manual processing shop or on a drug laboratory. \n\nThis kind of moxibustion stick can be used by yourself, or it can be used to help patients. After use, it can relieve pain and improve blood circulation and breathing efficiency. Generally lasts 12 hours. At the same time, it can also provide a certain degree of comfort. \n\nIn addition, it should be noted that this moxibustion stick will be specially affected in the marginal world, so if it is used frequently, it will have certain side effects. It is generally recommended to use it at most once a day.</AiJiu.description>
<AiJiu.ingestCommandString>use {0}</AiJiu.ingestCommandString>
<AiJiu.ingestReportString>use {0}</AiJiu.ingestReportString>
<AiJiu.ingestReportStringEat>use {0} to relax</AiJiu.ingestReportStringEat>

<AiYe.label>Mature wormwood leaf</AiYe.label>
<AiYe.description>It is harvested from mature moxa grass, which can be further processed into moxibustion sticks that can relieve the body and pain, and can also be sold as raw materials.</AiYe.description>

<Plant_AiYeZuoWu.label>High quality wormwood plant</Plant_AiYeZuoWu.label>
<Plant_AiYeZuoWu.description>Wormwood is a perennial herb or slightly semi shrubby plant with strong aroma. The main root is obvious, slightly thick and long, with a diameter of 1.5 cm, and many lateral roots. There are often transverse underground rhizomes and vegetative branches. \n\nThis kind of wormwood has been selected and bred by colonists for many centuries, and its growth speed and yield are better than those of wild wormwood plants.</Plant_AiYeZuoWu.description>

<Plant_YeShengAiCao.label>Wild wormwood</Plant_YeShengAiCao.label>
<Plant_YeShengAiCao.description>Wormwood is a perennial herb or slightly semi shrubby plant with strong aroma. The main root is obvious, slightly thick and long, with a diameter of 1.5 cm, and many lateral roots. There are often transverse underground rhizomes and vegetative branches. \n\nThis is a wild wormwood. Although it grows slowly in the wild and has strict requirements on the growing environment, it is still a precious wild resource.</Plant_YeShengAiCao.description>

<QiChe_First.label>Semi-organic car</QiChe_First.label>
<QiChe_First.description>The edge of the locomotive is printed with: "Designed by the edge engineer forlg on April 30, 2021". \n\nThis is a brand new, only mechanical armor shell structure, but there is a semi-organic car with a certain organic structure. Because it contains some organic matter inside, its corpse will still rot, but the good news is, Its attributes are very high, and its value is also very objective. Whether it is used as a transport tool or as an armored meat shield during battle, it can play a significant role. At the same time, it can participate in expeditions and assist your colonists in consigning large amounts of supplies. \n\nAlthough it can be like the machine family without rest or eating, it has some organic structure inside, so it is still willing to eat some food as snacks, so you can train it by using some ingredients . \n\nAssembling such a powerful locomotive requires a lot of materials. In addition, after adding the riding module, it can be used as a powerful vehicle. After "killing" it and disassembling the limbs will only obtain the materials needed for assembly The core of pseudo-personality will not be returned when dismantling half of it. So please be cautious when making these decisions. \n\nIt also contains a device driven by a pseudo-personality core, which makes it highly intelligent and can also generate some emotions.</QiChe_First.description>

<QiCheLingJian_First.label>Semi organic automobile assembly package</QiCheLingJian_First.label>
<QiCheLingJian_First.description>(Texture making) Semi-organic car assembly package, "printed on it: April 2021, designer: engineer forlg", and comes with assembly tutorials using the latest holographic technology, even for users who do not understand engineering at all Both can easily carry out the assembly process. \n\nThe assembly process takes several hours. Please ensure that your assembler has sufficient energy to complete this work. \n\nIn addition, if the assembled semi-organic car is organically disassembled on the slaughter table, only half of the raw materials will be returned, so please be considerate when using this assembly package. In addition, this is also a very good trading product that does not pay back.</QiCheLingJian_First.description>

<LaoHu_Bai.label>White tiger</LaoHu_Bai.label>
<LaoHu_Bai.description>The white tigers are almost extinct on the earth, but thanks to the help of wildlife protection organizations, the last few white tigers were sent to the fringe world and have been reborn under long-term protection, even though the wild white tigers that now thrive in the fringe world still Rarely. \n\nThe white tiger's genes have also undergone some changes under the influence of the marginal world environment. It is now larger than an ordinary tiger and can resist more damage. Similarly, due to its special appearance, the price of this animal is also very considerable. \n\nThis animal is now mainly living in boreal forests or boreal swamp areas in the marginal world, and there are also a few distributions in temperate and tundra tundra. \n\nThe white tiger is also one of the four great beasts in traditional Chinese culture. Tiger and white, body like snow, no miscellaneous hair, glaring eyes, short ears, four legs and five claws, long tail, can soaring clouds, and howling is brisk.</LaoHu_Bai.description>
<LaoHu_Bai.race.meatLabel>White tiger meat</LaoHu_Bai.race.meatLabel>

<Chi_JueBei.label>Decorative Baron cup</Chi_JueBei.label>
<Chi_JueBei.description>A sculptural decorative jug cup, of course, it cannot be used as a wine glass, but we can still experience the humanistic style of the Western Zhou Dynasty from the appearance of this jug cup. Its beauty and market value are very impressive, and it can be used for decoration or as a commodity. \n\nJue is also called jue cup, and ancient drinking vessels are also a large category of bronze wares in our country. According to historical records, people of noble status used princes as a kind of reward given to the princes when the emperor enshrined the princes in ancient times. Later, "jue" became the abbreviation of "jue", and "adding officials to jue" came from this. With the Jue Cup in hand, it takes full advantage of the time and place, and it means to overcome difficulties, to be invincible, to be appointed as an official, and to celebrate the victory. In the Hyundai Jue Cup is mainly used in business public relations activities, it is a good choice to send to bosses, leaders, business partners, etc.</Chi_JueBei.description>

<Chi_SanXingDuiDiaoSu.label>Sanxingdui style tiger</Chi_SanXingDuiDiaoSu.label>
<Chi_SanXingDuiDiaoSu.description>This sculpture is a "tiger" sculpture designed in the art style of Sanxingdui. It has a unique shape. The entire building highlights a head-up movement, symbolizing the thriving meaning. Whether it is tribal civilization or industrial age colonies, they like this exotic style, so take it It is easy to sell for a good price. \n\nSanxingdui Ancient Ruins is located on the south bank of the Duck River in the northwest of Guanghan City, Sichuan Province. It covers an area of 12 square kilometers and has a history of 5,000 to 3,000 years. It is the largest and longest ever discovered in the southwestern region so far. The ancient city, ancient country, and ancient Shu cultural sites with the richest cultural connotations. The most complete preserved east, west, and south city walls and the inner city walls of Moon Bay are currently available. The Sanxingdui site is known as one of the greatest archaeological discoveries of mankind in the 20th century, showing that the Yangtze River Basin, like the Yellow River Basin, belongs to the matrix of Chinese civilization and is known as the "source of the Yangtze River civilization."</Chi_SanXingDuiDiaoSu.description>

<MaJiangYi_Short.label>Cane chair of Song Dynasty (short)</MaJiangYi_Short.label>
<MaJiangYi_Short.description>A traditional Chinese rattan chair that can provide high comfort and a certain degree of beauty. The short wicker chair is different from the long wicker chair. It cannot provide entertainment for specific entertainment, but it is a good and space-saving choice to put it in a restaurant or other studio that lacks aesthetics. \n\nThe materials, handwork and technology of rattan weaving are mainly based on traditional Chinese craftsmanship, making rattan products full of ancient southern style, less modern style, and usually more popular among middle-aged people. Wicker chairs are not only simple but not lacking in fun, and their shapes emphasize the artistry. The more representative ones are Chinese-style peacock-shaped, chicken heart-shaped, sun-shaped and other wicker chairs. \n\nSpecific entertainment facilities used in conjunction with wicker chairs can make up to four wicker chairs in the range to provide them with entertainment bonuses.</MaJiangYi_Short.description>

<XiangQiTable.label>Chinese chess table</XiangQiTable.label>
<XiangQiTable.description>An exquisite chess table, just like Western poker or chess tables, chess is also one of the traditional Chinese puzzle games. The villain can get good and more efficient entertainment and intellectual income when playing chess. Similarly, the chess table With beautiful and generous design, it can also be used as a very good artwork. \n\nChinese chess originated in China. The famous British scholar Dr. Joseph Needham clearly pointed out in his book "The History of Chinese Science and Culture" that chess is also a Chinese creation. He analyzed in detail the relationship between ancient Chinese games-Liubo and astronomy, elephant art, and mathematics. He said: "Only in China, the prevalence of yin and yang theory led to the emergence of the embryonic form of chess and the invention of divination with astronomical properties. It then developed into a game with military implications."</XiangQiTable.description>


<Chi_DengYingNiuRou.label>Dengying Meat</Chi_DengYingNiuRou.label>
<Chi_DengYingNiuRou.description>Dengying Beef was originally made of beef, but after spreading to the marginal world, Dengying Meat has more methods. Chicken, pork or other meat types can also be processed by the chef to achieve the best taste. Dengying Meat is a famous traditional dish, which requires oily seeds and meat as raw materials. It has an excellent taste and can be stored for a long time as beef jerky. It is also an excellent trading product.</Chi_DengYingNiuRou.description>

<Chi_MeiCaiKouRou.label>Preserved Meat With Vegetables</Chi_MeiCaiKouRou.label>
<Chi_MeiCaiKouRou.description>This traditional Hakka dish has been widely praised by various colonies since it was promoted to the fringe world. Although the practice of this dish in the fringe world is different, Mei Cai is definitely an indispensable part. The preparation of this dish requires It consumes a lot of materials, but its taste and bonus are also very impressive. Mei Cai Kou Po is easy to spoil, so be sure to keep it fresh! \n\nMei Cai Kou Po, the food is the first Mei Cai Kou Po, the shape is unique, generous and decent, the color is red and oily, the soup is thick and delicious, the meat is fat but not greasy, and the food is soft and mellow. Mei Cai is golden in color, has a tangy aroma, sweet and refreshing, not cold, not dry, not humid, not hot, it absorbs the oil and soup of the pork belly, the flavor is immediately enriched, and the pork belly has the fragrance of Mei Cai, which complements each other.</Chi_MeiCaiKouRou.description>


<Plant_HybridRice.label>hybrid rice</Plant_HybridRice.label>
<Plant_HybridRice.description>Hybrid rice, thanks to the unremitting efforts of agronomists, has a slightly higher market value than ordinary rice, and is less perishable. Its nutritional value is equivalent to that of rice and can be used as raw materials for many dishes“ In the fragrance of rice flowers, we can hear the sound of frogs</Plant_HybridRice.description>

<RawZaJiaoShuiDao.label>Hybrid Rice</RawZaJiaoShuiDao.label>
<RawZaJiaoShuiDao.description>Hybrid rice, thanks to the unremitting efforts of agronomists, has a slightly higher market value than ordinary rice, and is less perishable. Its nutritional value is equivalent to that of rice and can be used as raw materials for many dishes“ In the fragrance of rice flowers, we can hear the sound of frogs</RawZaJiaoShuiDao.description>

<MeiCai.label>High quality Mei Cai</MeiCai.label>
<MeiCai.description>This is the harvested plum. It can be stored for a long time after being dried and salted. Its nutritional value is much higher than that of ordinary crops. It is suitable for making traditional famous dishes or as a raw material for other delicacies. \n\nMei Cai is a traditional specialty of the Hakka region. It is golden in color, scented, sweet and refreshing. It is neither cold nor dry nor damp nor hot. It is known as a "righteous" dish and has a long reputation. It will soon be spread to the marginal world. Won the favor of the public.</MeiCai.description>

<Plant_MeiCai.label>Plum vegetable crops</Plant_MeiCai.label>
<Plant_MeiCai.description>Vegetable crops can be harvested after ripening. Mei Cai is an essential raw material for making Mei Cai buckle meat. Also, because its harvest is also recognized by the public, it can also be used as an excellent vegetarian raw material. \n\nMei Cai crops can be cultivated in hydroponic tanks. It has high harvest yield and good nutritional value. It is an excellent crop. The disadvantage is that it has a long growth cycle and is also fertile to the land. The requirements of the plant are high, the planting speed is slow, and it needs careful care.</Plant_MeiCai.description>


<JunYongTaoCi.label>Military ceramics</JunYongTaoCi.label>
<JunYongTaoCi.description>The military ceramics made by mixing civil ceramics and glass fiber reinforced plastics in a ratio of 4:5 need to be produced on a precision assembly table. \n\nIt can not only provide excellent protection and durability for equipment and buildings, but also provide good aesthetics. It is one of the most advanced materials. You can use it as a furniture material or make it As a material for protective facilities. In addition, after testing, sharps made of this material are also particularly known as hands. \n\nBecause of the excellent performance of ceramics, this material can also withstand high temperatures. In addition, it also inherits the characteristics of ceramics, and furniture made from it can provide some cleanliness. However, due to its complex structure, buildings using it as a material will also spend more energy during construction. \n\nThis material will also accumulate in large quantities underground, so you can use drilling to dig it.</JunYongTaoCi.description>

<Plant_YinXingGuoShu.label>Artificial cultivation of ginkgo fruit trees</Plant_YinXingGuoShu.label>
<Plant_YinXingGuoShu.description>This is a genetically changed variant of the ginkgo tree after artificial cultivation. It produces almost no wood. This kind of tree can only be artificially planted, and its growth rate will be slower. After artificial cultivation, its aesthetics is also very high. \n\nHowever, ginkgo biloba is regularly produced in large quantities. Ginkgo biloba is a plant material that can be sold or processed into ginkgo wine (ginkgo wine will effectively prevent asthma and other diseases within a week after being quoted). \n\nGinkgo is a deciduous tree of the Ginkgo family and the genus Ginkgo. Ginkgo appeared hundreds of millions of years ago. It is the oldest relict plant among gymnosperms left over from the Quaternary Glacier Movement. Ginkgo biloba is rare and scattered, and hundreds of years old trees are rare. All other plants in the class have been extinct, so ginkgo has the reputation of living fossil. There are 26 varieties and varieties: yellow leaf ginkgo, tower ginkgo, split ginkgo, weeping ginkgo, and variegated ginkgo. \n\nThis kind of tree was brought to the marginal world by the spacecraft "Chinese Tree Research" in 2123 AD. It has high aesthetics, short growth period, and acceptable wood harvest. It is a very cost-effective "living fossil" tree. It has been widely promoted in marginal forestry. It usually grows in temperate and frigid forests.</Plant_YinXingGuoShu.description>

<BaiGuoJiu.label>Ginkgo Wine</BaiGuoJiu.label>
<BaiGuoJiu.description>Gingko wine is a medicinal drink made by mixing ginkgo biloba and herbal medicines. It is generally made on the brewing table. Because of its mild toxicity and poor taste, it is only used as a preventive drug (especially for gastrointestinal problems). Poor colonists must use it with caution). Because ginkgo wine has special effects, colonists can prevent heart disease, Alzheimer’s disease, asthma, and drowsiness within one month after enjoying ginkgo wine, and can get minimal Awareness bonus. However, because of its slight toxicity and poor taste, colonists will also receive a small amount of emotional punishment. \n\nDue to the loss of some raw materials during the production process, it is not recommended to be sold as a commodity. (Because the profit margin of ginkgo wine as a commodity is very low)\n\nThe natural plant ingredients of ginkgo wine completely retain the effect of the effective ingredients in ginkgo. It is rich in amino acids, regulates blood lipids, improves memory, removes free radicals in the body, and improves Symptoms such as numbness of hands and feet, backaches and backaches. Ginkgo biloba, known as the "living plant fossil", contains the main components of flavonoid glycosides, diterpene lactones, various trace elements (such as chromium, potassium) and other elements, rich in amino acids, vitamins, etc., totaling more than 160 active ingredients .</BaiGuoJiu.description>

<DengLong_Red.label>Lantern (red)</DengLong_Red.label>
<DengLong_Red.description>Lanterns usually need wood and cloth as well as a small amount of steel to make, it can provide good beauty, and provide comfort and beauty bonus for bed or other furniture, generally a room can connect two lanterns of the same color. And because it uses a design similar to the permanent light, so it does not need electricity or fuel to provide lighting. Lanterns have three kinds of lighting colors, no matter which color of lanterns are placed indoors, they will be beautiful and generous\ Chinese lanterns, also known as lanterns, are ancient traditional handicrafts of the Han nationality. Originated in the Western Han Dynasty, every year around the Lantern Festival on the 15th day of the first lunar month, people hang red lanterns to create a festive atmosphere.</DengLong_Red.description>

<DengLong_White.label>Lantern (White)</DengLong_White.label>
<DengLong_White.description>Lanterns usually need wood and cloth as well as a small amount of steel to make, it can provide good beauty, and provide comfort and beauty bonus for bed or other furniture, generally a room can connect two lanterns of the same color. And because it uses a design similar to the permanent light, so it does not need electricity or fuel to provide lighting. Lanterns have three kinds of lighting colors, no matter which color of lanterns are placed indoors, they will be beautiful and generous\ Chinese lanterns, also known as lanterns, are ancient traditional handicrafts of the Han nationality. Originated in the Western Han Dynasty, every year around the Lantern Festival on the 15th day of the first lunar month, people hang red lanterns to create a festive atmosphere.</DengLong_White.description>

<DengLong_Yellow.label>Lantern (Yellow)</DengLong_Yellow.label>
<DengLong_Yellow.description>Lanterns usually need wood and cloth as well as a small amount of steel to make, it can provide good beauty, and provide comfort and beauty bonus for bed or other furniture, generally a room can connect two lanterns of the same color. And because it uses a design similar to the permanent light, so it does not need electricity or fuel to provide lighting. Lanterns have three kinds of lighting colors, no matter which color of lanterns are placed indoors, they will be beautiful and generous\ Chinese lanterns, also known as lanterns, are ancient traditional handicrafts of the Han nationality. Originated in the Western Han Dynasty, every year around the Lantern Festival on the 15th day of the first lunar month, people hang red lanterns to create a festive atmosphere.</DengLong_Yellow.description>

<DengLong_Blue.label>Glimmer Lantern</DengLong_Blue.label>
<DengLong_Blue.description>Unlike other lanterns, this kind of lantern emits a ghost-like gloomy light. Its lighting range is far less than that of ordinary lanterns. Instead of calling it a lantern, it is more appropriate to call it a "eternal lantern". It is suitable for those It is used by colonists who like to work in dim light-of course, it is also suitable for being placed in the dark underground palace.</DengLong_Blue.description>

<ZhongHuaJiaJu_Chuang.label>Ming-style canopy bed</ZhongHuaJiaJu_Chuang.label>
<ZhongHuaJiaJu_Chuang.description>A bed with Chinese characteristics, because of its unique decorative style, and the designer has adopted some engineering designs while taking into account its beauty, making this canopy bed a favorite indoor furniture by colonists. \n\nThis canopy bed can provide good beauty and comfort, and colonists can quickly regain energy when using this bed. However, due to its complex structure, it is time-consuming to construct, and it also requires some parts and metal materials to support its unique structure. \n\nThe four corners of the canopy bed have columns, the front is thin and the back is thick, typical of the Ming Dynasty. There are fences on the left and right and back of the bed. The fences are mostly made of small wood and assembled into linear patterns. There are three large flower panels on the front of the bed, named "Moondong Bed". There is a cover on the top, commonly known as "Chengchen". Two columns are added to the front of the bed. There is a top frame on the top of the bed, hence the name "canopy bed".</ZhongHuaJiaJu_Chuang.description>



<BaiGuoJiuHu.label>Gingko Wine Paste</BaiGuoJiuHu.label>
<BaiGuoJiuHu.description>Ginkgo wine that has not been fermented can be sold as a commodity. Because it requires more materials, the market price is higher. It can also be further fermented into ginkgo wine in a ginkgo wine distiller, which is a medicinal liquor that can prevent various diseases.</BaiGuoJiuHu.description>

<BaiMiFan.label>Ordinary white rice</BaiMiFan.label>
<BaiMiFan.description>White rice cooked with polished rice or rice (hybrid rice) is made on the original or Chinese stove. It has no other side dishes, but one serving can fill your stomach and can be sold as a commodity to passing merchants. In addition, it is the same as most dishes and is perishable, so it needs to be kept fresh. \n\nWhite rice is one of the traditional Chinese main dishes. For most people in the fringe world, this kind of food is easy to accept, but for the top palace nobles, this kind of food does not have any side dishes. It's hard to swallow. After enjoying the white rice, you will get a very small mood bonus, which is suitable as a food for the colonial transition period.</BaiMiFan.description>


<YinXingGuo.label>Ginkgo Fruit</YinXingGuo.label>
<YinXingGuo.description>Obtained from artificially cultivated or wild ginkgo trees, it can be further processed into ginkgo wine, or it can be sold on the market. It is a very good plant resource. It decays slowly, but it cannot be eaten as food.</YinXingGuo.description>

<GuoFu.label>Preserved fruit</GuoFu.label>
<GuoFu.description>Preserved fruits made from various berries or other fruits have a long shelf life just like dried meat patties. The difference is that it is usually used as a snack or dry food during travel. \n\nAfter being promoted to the fringe world, the preserved fruit soon received the love from the nobles and the common people, and it became the after-dinner snack sought after by all walks of life. Generally, one candied fruit can be used to cushion the stomach a little before the meal. \n\n There are specialties of candied fruits all over the country, among which the more famous ones are the old Beijing candied fruits and Xinjiang raisins. It is a food made from fresh fruits through main processes such as peeling, pitting, boiling in sugar and water, soaking, drying, and finishing packaging. It is bright and transparent, with a dry surface, slightly sticky, and a water content of less than 20%. There are many kinds of preserved fruits. Famous traditional products include preserved apples, preserved sour horns, preserved apricots, preserved pears, preserved peaches, preserved Taiping preserved fruits, green plums, hawthorn slices, and fruit peels.</GuoFu.description>

<Chi_BeiJingKaoYa.label>Peking Roast</Chi_BeiJingKaoYa.label>
<Chi_BeiJingKaoYa.description>As one of the most famous dishes in the traditional Chinese dishes, Beijing roast duck has become the most eye-catching delicacy in the fringe world since it was promoted to the fringe world. \n\nThe practice of Beijing roast duck has been expanded after being spread to the fringe world. Now it is not necessary to use duck meat to make roast duck, because the chefs can process all kinds of meat into the original roast duck flavor, and this is not Will not be seen by others. \n\nTo make a roast duck requires a lot of meat and a small amount of vegetarian food. After eating roast duck, there are unique health and mood benefits.</Chi_BeiJingKaoYa.description>

<ChiTableB.label>Chinese table(1x2)</ChiTableB.label>
<ChiTableB.description>The table made by the Chinese design concept is unique in design, small and exquisite. Traditional Chinese patterns are printed on the center and both sides of the chair. Suitable for any occasion. \n\nAlthough it consumes more materials than an ordinary table of the same size, it provides considerable aesthetics. In addition, because its structure is relatively complex, it requires a lot of effort during construction.</ChiTableB.description>

<ChiTableC.label>Chinese table(2x2)</ChiTableC.label>
<ChiTableC.description>The table made by the Chinese design concept is unique in design, small and exquisite. Traditional Chinese patterns are printed on the center and both sides of the chair. Suitable for any occasion. \n\nAlthough it consumes more materials than an ordinary table of the same size, it provides considerable aesthetics. In addition, because its structure is relatively complex, it requires a lot of effort during construction.</ChiTableC.description>

<ChiTableD.label>Chinese table(3x3)</ChiTableD.label>
<ChiTableD.description>The table made by the Chinese design concept is unique in design, small and exquisite. Traditional Chinese patterns are printed on the center and both sides of the chair. Suitable for any occasion. \n\nAlthough it consumes more materials than an ordinary table of the same size, it provides considerable aesthetics. In addition, because its structure is relatively complex, it requires a lot of effort during construction.</ChiTableD.description>

<ZhuanZhuo.label>Chinese rotating dining table (3x3)</ZhuanZhuo.label>
<ZhuanZhuo.description>This kind of rotating dining table was developed and promoted to the fringe world by Shenzhou civilization. It adopts a modern rotating design and at the same time renders the Chinese Shenzhou culture. This kind of table is always one of the most sought-after furniture in the market during the holidays and festivals. The revolving table reflects a strong sense of humanity and reunion atmosphere. \n\nBecause of its internal use of some mechanical devices, it requires a certain amount of steel and parts to build, which can provide a very good aesthetics and is very attractive to the colonists. \n\nAlso, colonists can speed up their meals when dining near this table. The turntable consumes very little power when rotating.</ZhuanZhuo.description>

<Chi_ZhiChengZhuA.label>Chinese support column</Chi_ZhiChengZhuA.label>
<Chi_ZhiChengZhuA.description>A supporting column similar to a Chinese-style bucket arch structure. The construction materials were first discovered in the crashed "Shenzhou" spacecraft. Because of its good stability and aesthetics, this bucket-arch type supporting column was quickly spread to the marginal world. There are such supporting pillars everywhere, whether in the halls of the nobles or in front of the common people's doors. \n\nThis support column can support the roof and provide a good aesthetic bonus. Similarly, it can meet the requirements of various title rooms. It is a structural building and also a good decoration. It needs more to be constructed. material.</Chi_ZhiChengZhuA.description>

<Chi_ZhiChengZhuB.label>Chinese Royal Support Column</Chi_ZhiChengZhuB.label>
<Chi_ZhiChengZhuB.description>A very luxurious support column with a circle of golden decoration on its periphery. This support column is imitating a dome-shaped support column. The first batch of royal support column designs are from the crashed "Shenzhou" spacecraft. \n\nThis support column has been sought after by nobles everywhere. Even though the roof area it can support is very limited, it can bring a high aesthetic bonus to the interior, so it is regarded as a noble or The decor of the deluxe room is still a very good choice. \n\nIt takes a lot of energy and materials to build this support column.</Chi_ZhiChengZhuB.description>

<Chi_ZhiChengZhuC.label>Chinese style support column with light</Chi_ZhiChengZhuC.label>
<Chi_ZhiChengZhuC.description>The support column with lamp similar to the dougong structure, designers from China cleverly combined the ever-bright-style lighting system with the support column to create this kind of Chinese-style support column with lamp. This support column takes into account the beauty and at the same time. The atmosphere of "Shenzhou Culture" is rendered vividly, while ensuring stability and practicality, whether it is placed indoors or outdoors, it can play its role well. \n\nA small amount of steel and parts are needed to support its complex structure, and there are certain requirements for the builder's construction skills.</Chi_ZhiChengZhuC.description>

<FermentingBarrel_BaiGuoJiu.label>Ginkgo Wine Distiller</FermentingBarrel_BaiGuoJiu.label>
<FermentingBarrel_BaiGuoJiu.description>A device used for distilling and fermenting ginkgo wine paste. After fermentation, ginkgo wine can be obtained (usually the fermentation time is about three to four days). Because this device is designed to follow certain aesthetic rules, it can also provide a small amount of beauty degree.</FermentingBarrel_BaiGuoJiu.description>

<WoWoTou.label>Wowotou</WoWoTou.label>
<WoWoTou.description>Wowotou made from any crudely processed vegetarian dry food, although it tastes no taste and cannot be traded as a commodity, the processed Wowotou has a relatively long shelf life and is usually enjoyed by a hungry colonist. After two wowotou can regain energy, it is suitable for simple dry food. \n\nWowotou’s value is relatively low, so it is suitable for large-scale preservation. Although nobles may not appreciate such simple and dry food, it is a good idea to provide it to prisoners or ascetics select.</WoWoTou.description>

<ZiDongRenRouJi.label>Human flesh automatic processing device</ZiDongRenRouJi.label>
<ZiDongRenRouJi.description>This is a modified version of the human flesh processor. It can process 100 human flesh in two days, and the effect is very impressive. Unlike a manual human flesh processor, it can reduce a lot of losses. All in all, this is indeed a very good "production tool". But it is not recommended for those peaceful leisure operators to build such crazy buildings. \n\nThe working speed of this machine in a high temperature or extremely low temperature environment will be greatly improved. In addition, even if it is driven by electricity, it will not short-circuit in the rain</ZiDongRenRouJi.description>


<SZ_Building_PlantShuiPei.label>Traditional hydroponic tank</SZ_Building_PlantShuiPei.label>
<SZ_Building_PlantShuiPei.description>The traditional hydroponic tank developed by Chinese colonists can cultivate characteristic plants from China, such as reed and hybrid rice, without the need of electricity, which can provide high soil fertility. However, because the dish only contains water, terrestrial plants cannot grow in it\n\n This kind of Petri dish is designed for both practicality and aesthetics, and its fire resistance is relatively good.</SZ_Building_PlantShuiPei.description>

<SZ_Building_ShuiTian.label>Water planting net</SZ_Building_ShuiTian.label>
<SZ_Building_ShuiTian.description>The water planting nets designed by the Chinese colonists according to local conditions are usually laid in rivers or mud. This kind of planting nets is very convenient to lay and will not catch fire. It is also convenient to grow plants that depend on water for survival, such as reeds and hybrid rice. \n\nOther land plants cannot be grown in it.</SZ_Building_ShuiTian.description>

<SZ_CiYao_Fire.label>Ceramic kiln (fuel)</SZ_CiYao_Fire.label>
<SZ_CiYao_Fire.description>Ceramic firing technology has always been the most proud invention of the Chinese colonists, and this ceramic kiln inherits the traditional firing technology, can complete the conversion of stone bricks, but the efficiency is not as good as the electric type. In addition, the colonists can fire quartz tiles into beautiful ceramic materials. \n\nThis ceramic kiln has been transformed by the Chinese colonists and has high fuel efficiency, and can use wood, hay, and chemical fuels as its fuel.</SZ_CiYao_Fire.description>


<EndTableSZ_ChuangTouGui_New.label>Chinese style royal bedside table</EndTableSZ_ChuangTouGui_New.label>
<EndTableSZ_ChuangTouGui_New.description>This luxurious bedside table with gilded handles was designed by Shenzhou Civilization, and its pattern design refers to the decorative art of its home country. Once this kind of bedside table was launched, it was sought after by the nobles of the marginal world. \n\nThanks to the advanced design technology of the Chinese colonists, this bedside table can provide a small amount of comfort and rest efficiency for nearby beds while providing high aesthetics.</EndTableSZ_ChuangTouGui_New.description>

<SZ_ShuZhuangTai.label>Chinese style royal dressing table</SZ_ShuZhuangTai.label>
<SZ_ShuZhuangTai.description>This luxurious style dressing table was designed by the Chinese colonists. They made this style of dressing table an indispensable decoration in the noble room in the fringe world through clever detailed design. The decorative pattern made of gold made this piece The furniture is more artistic. \n\nSimilarly, when placed in the bedroom, this decorative table can provide aesthetics and comfort, and it takes a lot of energy and materials to build.</SZ_ShuZhuangTai.description>

<SZ_ZongZi.label>Zongzi</SZ_ZongZi.label>
<SZ_ZongZi.description>Zongzi made from zong leaves, glutinous rice flour and a small amount of other materials will provide some mood and health bonuses after being eaten, and need to be made on a specific stove or steamer. \n\nZongzi, as the most traditional food in the mother country of China’s civilization, has spread to all corners of the fringe world. When the Dragon Boat Festival comes, Chinese colonists will gather to enjoy the zongzi, a symbol of reunion.</SZ_ZongZi.description>


<SZ_YiGui.label>Chinese style wardrobe</SZ_YiGui.label>
<SZ_YiGui.description>The Chinese-style wardrobe designed by the Chinese colonists, with various exquisite patterns carved on it, can provide a good aesthetic bonus to the room. When it is linked to the bed, it can also improve the resting efficiency of the corresponding bed. It is very easy to put in any room. Suitable. \n\nAfter the design of Chinese colonists, this wardrobe can also hold a small amount of clothes, which is very practical.</SZ_YiGui.description>


<SZ_ShuZhuangJing.label>Dressing mirror</SZ_ShuZhuangJing.label>
<SZ_ShuZhuangJing.description>The vanity mirror, designed by the Chinese colonists, needs to be placed on the dressing table, which can provide a higher aesthetic bonus to the colonists' room, which is common in noble rooms or ordinary colonial rooms.</SZ_ShuZhuangJing.description>

<SZ_MenMian.label>Liao rice noodles</SZ_MenMian.label>
<SZ_MenMian.description>A kind of noodles originated in the mother country of Shenzhou civilization. It originated in the Song Dynasty thousands of years ago. Unlike traditional noodles, stewed noodles are innovative creations of noodle soups. After Shenzhou civilization spreads stewed noodles to the marginal world, it has all The required raw materials have been improved, and now the colonists only need to add polished rice noodles and any raw food to make delicious braised noodles. \n\nThe stewed noodles have the effect of nourishing the spleen and stomach. The colonists can get a small amount of metabolic bonus while getting the satiety brought by the flour.</SZ_MenMian.description>

<HuangJiu.label>Rice wine</HuangJiu.label>
<HuangJiu.description>A fine wine from the home country of China's civilization, has a very long history. It is a very common entertainment in the Shenzhou colony, also known as "liquid cake". \n\nLike all Chinese wines, because the Chinese colonists added special herbal ingredients in the brewing process, rice wine is not easily addictive, and the harm to the human health system is relatively small, but once addicted, it It's harder to quit. \n\nThe brewing of rice wine adopts the traditional brewing method of the mother country of China civilization. The colonists need to ferment the glutinous rice to get the rice wine paste and then put it into a special brewing barrel for brewing. The brewing time of rice wine is similar to beer, which belongs to low-grade brewing. Wine has a considerable market value.</HuangJiu.description>

<BaiJiu.label>Baijiu kiln mud</BaiJiu.label>
<BaiJiu.description>A fine wine from the home country of China's civilization, has a very long history. It is a very common entertainment in the Shenzhou colony and one of the most famous distilled spirits. \n\nAlthough the traditional Chinese brewing method is adopted, white wine is more addictive than low-alcohol brewed wines such as rice wine, but a bottle of white wine provides much more excitement than low-alcohol brewed wines such as rice wine. , The entertainment effect is also stronger. \n\nThe brewing of liquor adopts the traditional brewing method of the mother country of the Chinese civilization. The colonists need to ferment the corn or mixed Su Shigan to obtain the liquor paste and then put it into a special brewing barrel for brewing. \n\nDue to the long brewing time and the consumption of a lot of materials, the market value of liquor is higher.</BaiJiu.description>

<BaiJiuWort.label>Fermented liquor</BaiJiuWort.label>
<BaiJiuWort.description>The preliminary product of dry corn or vegetarian starch blending needs to be further fermented in a fermentation tank. Of course, it can also be sold as a preliminary product, although the profit is very low. \n\nThanks to the improvement of the Chinese colonists, the fermented liquor has undergone preliminary treatment, so it can be stored for a long time.</BaiJiuWort.description>

<HuangJiuWort.label>Fermented rice wine</HuangJiuWort.label>
<HuangJiuWort.description>The preliminary product after mixing glutinous rice or starch needs to be further fermented in a fermentation tank. Of course, it can also be sold as a preliminary product, although the profit is very low. \n\nThanks to the improvement of the Chinese colonists, the fermented rice wine has undergone preliminary processing, so it can be stored for a long time.</HuangJiuWort.description>

<FermentingBarrel_BaiJiu.label>Liquor Kiln Mud</FermentingBarrel_BaiJiu.label>
<FermentingBarrel_BaiJiu.description>A traditional fermentation device, invented by the mother country of the Chinese civilization. Although it looks crude in appearance, thanks to its ingenious structural design, liquor fermentation products can be fermented in this kiln mud and finally produce delicious liquor. . Similarly, this kiln mud can hold a large number of fermented liquors at one time. The fermentation rate of liquor is slightly slower than beer, but the value of liquor produced by fermentation is higher. \n\nAlthough kiln mud has not been well promoted on other planets, the fermentation of Shenzhou wine has become the best choice for fermented wine due to the special environmental restrictions of the peripheral world.</FermentingBarrel_BaiJiu.description>

<FermentingBarrel_HuangJiu.label>Rice wine kiln mud</FermentingBarrel_HuangJiu.label>
<FermentingBarrel_HuangJiu.description>A traditional fermentation device, invented by the mother country of the Chinese civilization. Although it looks crude in appearance, thanks to its ingenious structural design, the fermented rice wine can be fermented in this kiln mud and finally produce delicious rice wine. . Similarly, this kiln mud can hold a large amount of fermented rice wine at one time. The fermentation rate of rice wine kiln mud is faster, and the quality of the brewed wine is also very good. \n\nAlthough kiln mud has not been well promoted on other planets, the fermentation of Shenzhou wine has become the best choice for fermented wine due to the special environmental restrictions of the peripheral world.</FermentingBarrel_HuangJiu.description>

<XiongHuangJiu.label>Realgar wine</XiongHuangJiu.label>
<XiongHuangJiu.description>Realgar wine made from realgar powder and some fermentable substances and dried in the sun is usually used as a medicinal wine, but it can also be drunk as a recreational product. \n\nLike all Chinese wines, because the Chinese colonists added special herbal ingredients during the brewing process, realgar wine is not easily addictive, and the harm to the human health system is relatively small, but once addicted, it It's harder to quit. \n\nThe brewing of realgar wine is relatively simple, only need to mix the refined realgar powder, fermentable glutinous rice flour, and polished rice noodles to make it. \n\nAlthough realgar wine can provide good additions, it is also slightly toxic, so colonists will be affected by the special state of realgar wine for a certain period of time after drinking realgar wine.</XiongHuangJiu.description>

<XiongHuangFen.label>Realgar Powder</XiongHuangFen.label>
<XiongHuangFen.description>Realgar powder, which is crushed from realgar ore, needs to be prepared on a pestle. Realgar powder is an essential raw material for realgar wine production. Of course, the profit of selling it as a material is also very good, but because its exposure to outdoor and open-air environments will accelerate its oxidation rate, it needs to be stored indoors. Similarly, it is necessary to store it in a low temperature environment. \n\nAfter studying the industrial casting technology of the industrial age, it is possible to extract a small amount of realgar powder from any stone by special means.</XiongHuangFen.description>

<BlocksXiongHuang.label>Realgarstone</BlocksXiongHuang.label>
<BlocksXiongHuang.description>Realgarite, this beautiful-looking ore is usually distributed deep in the mountains. It is a relatively rare mineral and can be distributed in small amounts in the deep stratum. \n\nThis mineral did not initially exist in the marginal world. Around 4100, the first group of Chinese geologists added the realgar mineral element to the geological layers of the marginal world experimentally and achieved success. In the geological movement for thousands of years, realgar minerals have gradually appeared in various mountains in the marginal world. \n\nRealgar ore can provide a good beauty bonus. Similarly, weapons using it as a material can effectively smash the enemy's heavy armor through bludgeoning, but the protection performance bonus it provides is extremely poor. \n\nRealgar ore can also be ground into realgar powder in a pestle, which is an essential material for brewing realgar wine. Similarly, after heating, it can be made into arsenic for use in traditional Chinese medicine.</BlocksXiongHuang.description>

<KuangMaiXiongHuang.label>Realgar vein</KuangMaiXiongHuang.label>
<KuangMaiXiongHuang.description>Realgar wine can detoxify, and colonists can get extra metabolic bonus after enjoying realgar wine, but their consciousness and mobility are slightly reduced due to the slight toxicity of realgar wine.</KuangMaiXiongHuang.description>

<SZ_MiGang.label>Rice jar</SZ_MiGang.label>
<SZ_MiGang.description>The rice tank used to store polished rice noodles or glutinous rice flour (rice and hybrid rice) has good airtightness, so the stored items will not age when placed in it. Similarly, the appearance of the rice tank is very beautiful, so it It can also provide a nice beauty bonus. \n\nThe rice tank uses the traditional method of evaporative preservation. Only a small amount of wood or hay is needed to maintain the freshness of the rice tank. Usually these materials can maintain the freshness of the rice tank for a long time.</SZ_MiGang.description>

<SZ_XiangQiA.label>Chess bench sculpture - red</SZ_XiangQiA.label>
<SZ_XiangQiA.description>The chess bench is carved into a cylindrical shape. Because of its traditional Chinese sculpture technique, every detail of the bench is vividly depicted. Therefore, it can be used as an exquisite bench as well as a valuable small sculpture. Exhibition and sale. \n\nBecause it is designed to have a "chess-like" appearance, it can provide a small furniture bonus when placed next to a Chinese or chess table.</SZ_XiangQiA.description>

<SZ_XiangQiB.label>Chess bench sculpture - black</SZ_XiangQiB.label>
<SZ_XiangQiB.description>The chess bench is carved into a cylindrical shape. Because of its traditional Chinese sculpture technique, every detail of the bench is vividly depicted. Therefore, it can be used as an exquisite bench as well as a valuable small sculpture. Exhibition and sale. \n\nBecause it is designed to have a "chess-like" appearance, it can provide a small furniture bonus when placed next to a Chinese or chess table.</SZ_XiangQiB.description>

<Plant_MuDan.label>Peony</Plant_MuDan.label>
<Plant_MuDan.description>The characteristic plants from the mother country of China's civilization have become one of the common indoor decorative flowers after being introduced into the fringe world. Similarly, peonies will also be distributed in temperate regions and a small amount in the frigid zone, which can tolerate lower temperatures. Provides more aesthetic bonuses. \n\nPeony is a relatively delicate flower. Although its vitality is relatively ordinary, it needs regular maintenance in the flowerpot, but because of its beautiful and dazzling appearance, it is still often cultivated as a decorative flower by the nobles of the fringe world and grows in the wild. The peony cluster is also a beautiful scenery.</Plant_MuDan.description>

<SZ_DaDiaoSu.label>Shenzhou-Sculpture series</SZ_DaDiaoSu.label>
<SZ_DaDiaoSu.description>The larger sculptures are designed by Shenzhou civilization. This series of sculptures portrays various scenes of Shenzhou civilization. The sculptures are extremely delicate. The sculptures of various shapes have a metaphor for the colony to prosper step by step. Such exquisite art In the fringe world, the product has become a sought-after product. \n\nThese sculptures do not have any concrete shapes, but are based on various objects that symbolize the Chinese culture, leaving people with unlimited space for association.</SZ_DaDiaoSu.description>

<SZ_XiaoDiaoSu.label>Shenzhou-Cultural Symbol Sculpture</SZ_XiaoDiaoSu.label>
<SZ_XiaoDiaoSu.description>These sculptures usually portray some cultural symbols from the motherland of China, such as the Sanxingdui symbols. They are relatively simple to carve and can also provide quite good aesthetics. \n\nThe colonists can learn about the long-distance culture from the motherland of China from these sculptures engraved with Chinese cultural symbols. The sculpture seems to have the temperature of history, touching its appearance gently, the aftermath of the ancient culture of China seems to have passed from their shell to the hearts of the viewers.</SZ_XiaoDiaoSu.description>

<SZ_XiangQiA.label>Chess Bench Sculpture-Red</SZ_XiangQiA.label>
<SZ_XiangQiA.description>The chess bench is carved into a cylindrical shape. Because of its traditional Chinese sculpture technique, every detail of the bench is depicted vividly. Therefore, it can be used as an exquisite bench as well as a valuable small sculpture. Exhibition and sale. \n\nBecause it is designed to have a "chess-like" appearance, it can provide a small furniture bonus when placed next to a Chinese or chess table.</SZ_XiangQiA.description>

<SZ_XiangQiB.label>Chess Bench Sculpture-Black</SZ_XiangQiB.label>
<SZ_XiangQiB.description>The chess bench is carved into a cylindrical shape. Because of its traditional Chinese sculpture technique, every detail of the bench is depicted vividly. Therefore, it can be used as an exquisite bench as well as a valuable small sculpture. Exhibition and sale. \n\nBecause it is designed to have a "chess-like" appearance, it can provide a small furniture bonus when placed next to a Chinese or chess table.</SZ_XiangQiB.description>

<SZ_ShiTouE.label>Lion head goose</SZ_ShiTouE.label>
<SZ_ShiTouE.description>The lion head goose breed bred by the Chinese civilization. This lion head goose is one of the largest geese in the world. It has a large amount of meat and is suitable for farming. Although it is larger in size, its food intake has not increased. Many people like to eat roughage. At the same time, it has a higher frequency of laying eggs. The market value of this animal is also very good. It is a kind of poultry with high cost performance. \n\nLion head goose is characterized by large body, big head, wide green eyes and tender meat, etc. It was introduced to the marginal world by the Shenzhou animal spacecraft in 4396 AD.</SZ_ShiTouE.description>

<SZ_PiShuang.label>Arsenic drug</SZ_PiShuang.label>
<SZ_PiShuang.description>The arsenic drug extracted from realgar powder and processed, although arsenic is highly toxic, it can still be used in a small amount of medicine after the arsenic is extracted. \n\nThis medicinal arsenic can be taken as a medicine. Because arsenic is very effective, the action time provided by arsenic drugs is also relatively long, usually about 20 days. Making arsenic drugs requires a lot of realgar Powder as a raw material. \n\nBecause arsenic drugs are very rare in the fringe world, a pack of arsenic drugs can often be sold at a high price.</SZ_PiShuang.description>

<SZ_MeiGuoCha.label>Berry tea</SZ_MeiGuoCha.label>
<SZ_MeiGuoCha.description>Berry tea brewed from berries needs to be made on the brewing table. Berry tea is a simple entertainment drink with the function of refreshing and anti fatigue. In addition, it can help the colonists alleviate the symptoms of heatstroke. \n\npeople in the Chinese colonies like to have a cup of this kind of berry tea in the hot summer or when they are tired, and the sale of berry tea as a commodity can also make a good profit. It is a very good entertainment drink.</SZ_MeiGuoCha.description>

<SZ_HuoPen.label>Chinese lighting carving cage</SZ_HuoPen.label>
<SZ_HuoPen.description>Carving cages for lighting are usually placed outdoors as decorative lamps for lighting. They also have the effect of lighting and decoration when placed indoors. They are common decorative lamps in the Chinese civilization. \n\nBecause the lighting carving cage adopts the energy-saving fuel setting of China, the frequency of replacing materials is longer and the maintenance is more convenient. The carving cage can also provide a good aesthetic bonus, and it is a very practical decorative furniture. . \n\nThe fuel and lighting of the carving cage will not be affected by rain. Similarly, hay and gasoline can also be used as fuel. \n\nBecause of its exquisite design, it can also meet the nobles' brazier needs for the Hall of Observation.</SZ_HuoPen.description>

<SZ_Plant_ChangShouHua.label>Wild longevity flower</SZ_Plant_ChangShouHua.label>
<SZ_Plant_ChangShouHua.description>The longevity flower grows in the wild. This flower was introduced to the marginal world by Chinese colonists. Compared with similar flowers, this wild flower has a longer life, so it is often given the meaning of longevity in Chinese culture \n\n these wild flowers grow rapidly and are generally widely distributed in the wild, providing a good beauty bonus for the surrounding environment.</SZ_Plant_ChangShouHua.description>


<ChiTableE.label>Chinese table (1x3)</ChiTableE.label>
<ChiTableE.description>Shenzhou civilization is generally used for sacrificial ceremonies. After design and improvement, it can also be used as a dining table. The Chinese colonists like to put some incense tables and tributes on this table to commemorate their ancestors or some gods. For them This kind of sacrificial work is also very important. \n\nThe altar table is not only a good decoration, but also a very practical dining table. Since it still has a certain sacrificial function, the colonists can meditate in front of the altar table.</ChiTableE.description>

<SZ_FoXiang.label>Majestic buddha</SZ_FoXiang.label>
<SZ_FoXiang.description>Shenzhou-style Buddha statues, this kind of Buddha statues generally appear in the sacrifice places of the Shenzhou colonists, and also appear in some Shenzhou large households. The Shenzhou colonists regard this Buddha statue as a symbol of nature, and they will worship the Buddha every month. So that nature can bless their crops to grow smoothly. \n\nBecause this Buddha statue has a strong connection with nature, even the enemy will stay away from the built Buddha statue. It is both a beautiful ornament and a solemn natural meditation building. \n\nThe great sculpture of Shenzhou can improve its meditation effect.</SZ_FoXiang.description>

<SZ_NianYaoLu.label>Medicine furnace</SZ_NianYaoLu.label>
<SZ_NianYaoLu.description>The furnace used to smelt Shenzhou medicine. Although its appearance is the same as the alchemy furnace, it can do more work. Some addictive drugs and medicines (including some powders) from Shenzhou can be manufactured here, and it is also Some other medicines can be made. After ingenious design and construction, this building can be both beautiful and efficient, and its fuel efficiency has also become very efficient after transformation. \n\nThe working mechanism of this furnace is still a mystery, and this Chinese colonist who first designed it knows, but it is certain that it can indeed produce some complex industrial medicines and complete some advanced processes. \n\nWhen put together with the drug test bench, it can speed up the work of the drug test bench.</SZ_NianYaoLu.description>

<SZ_Plant_Ambrosia.label>Artificial cultivation of fairy fruit trees</SZ_Plant_Ambrosia.label>
<SZ_Plant_Ambrosia.description>At the beginning of the period, the fairy fruit tree could not be cultivated artificially, but after the unremitting efforts of the Chinese agronomists, the fairy fruit tree has been bred into a variety that can be artificially planted. \n\nThis kind of fairy fruit tree is a variety that can be artificially planted, but it needs to be planted in a hydroponic tank or original hydroponic system and needs careful care. Its growth cycle is longer than that of the wild fairy tree. But you can harvest more fairy fruits.</SZ_Plant_Ambrosia.description>

<Plant_Qingke.label>Barley</Plant_Qingke.label>
<Plant_Qingke.description>This is a hardy crop introduced to the "New Qinghai-Tibet" area of China. This plant can tolerate a low temperature of more than ten degrees below zero and is usually grown in plateau areas. It has a short growth cycle and can harvest highland barley with a long shelf life. It is a very good crop. \n\nIn the "New Qinghai-Tibet" area of China, this plant is the most common plant on this plateau. Similarly, it has become one of the most important crops in local agriculture.</Plant_Qingke.description>


<RawQingKe.label>Barley pole</RawQingKe.label>
<RawQingKe.description>The barley rods harvested from highland barley can be used as cooking materials, and can also be further processed into highland barley powder with higher nutritional value and better properties. Of course, it can also be sold as agricultural products. \n\nAs long as the storage environment is suitable, barley poles can be stored for a long period of time.</RawQingKe.description>


<WorkedQingKe.label>Highland barley powder</WorkedQingKe.label>
<WorkedQingKe.description>The highland barley flour obtained by processing the highland barley rod in the blowing machine is a preliminary processed raw food, and its nutritional value and market value are higher, and it is easier to preserve.</WorkedQingKe.description>

<SZ_LuoHanChuangYi.label>Arhat bed chair</SZ_LuoHanChuangYi.label>
<SZ_LuoHanChuangYi.description>A simple but ancient bed chair, usually used as a chair. It comes from the motherland of Shenzhou. This kind of bed is larger in size and has a belly shaped like Luohan skin. Although from the appearance, its design and construction are very simple, but its The clever design still provides a good aesthetic for this furniture. \n\nAlthough the Luohan bed is shaped like a stool, it still belongs to a kind of bedding. Therefore, this simple furniture is still suitable for work rooms or rooms with poor conditions and can still be used as a bed, but the rest efficiency is slightly lower. \n\nAlthough the Luohan bed chair can provide good comfort and aesthetics, the nobles still like to use more expensive furniture as their beds.</SZ_LuoHanChuangYi.description>

<Chi_BaoZiMaker_Old.label>Steamer (fuel)</Chi_BaoZiMaker_Old.label>
<Chi_BaoZiMaker_Old.description>The colonists can make steamed buns and steamed buns from this steamer, two foods that can improve satiety. \n\nAfter the transformation of the Chinese colonists, the fuel steamer can use more materials as fuel, such as chemical fuel, hay, etc., and the fuel efficiency of this steamer is also very good.</Chi_BaoZiMaker_Old.description>

<WorkedJingMi.label>Polished rice noodles</WorkedJingMi.label>
<WorkedJingMi.description>The polished rice noodles obtained by dehulling rice or hybrid rice rice is a unique creation of the Chinese colonists. It can be used as a rice material or as flour for cooking. The mood penalty of eating raw and the probability of poisoning For the lower, because the polished rice noodles are partially dehydrated, they can be kept for the last month. \n\nThe nutritional value of a single serving of polished rice noodles is slightly higher than that of ordinary raw food, glutinous rice flour and other crudely processed vegetarian food. It is an indispensable raw material for egg fried rice, noodles and ordinary rice, and can also be used as a raw material for other cuisines.</WorkedJingMi.description>

<SZ_YueBing.label>Moon Cake</SZ_YueBing.label>
<SZ_YueBing.description>This kind of mass food comes from the ancient Chinese civilization and has been popular in the entire fringe world after being promoted. Chinese colonists usually hold reunion gatherings during the Mid-Autumn Festival, and moon cakes are an indispensable food in reunion and moon appreciation gatherings. It is said that this kind of moon cakes entrusts them with the beautiful meaning of "reunion and reunion". \n\nStarch materials are needed to make moon cakes, as well as any food as fillings for moon cakes. The making process is relatively simple. Compared with other cooking foods, moon cakes have a relatively longer shelf life. \n\nThe colonists can get a good mood and health bonus after eating mooncakes.</SZ_YueBing.description>


<SZ_LinkChuJu.label>China tool cabinet</SZ_LinkChuJu.label>
<SZ_LinkChuJu.description>The tool cabinet used by Shenzhou Civilization is different from other tool cabinets. It is not only a tool cabinet, but also a work of art. Although it requires more materials to build and requires a very small amount of ceramics for decoration, it can provide a good job for the workshop. In addition to its aesthetics and cleanliness, such a tool cabinet has almost become a standard item in the production workshop of the fringe world. \n\nA production facility can link up to one Shenzhou tool cabinet. The Shenzhou tool cabinet can provide more production efficiency bonuses, and its effective range is also larger.</SZ_LinkChuJu.description>

<SZ_LinkableToolBox.label>Shenzhou traditional stove</SZ_LinkableToolBox.label>
<SZ_LinkableToolBox.description>Such auxiliary stoves are usually placed next to stoves or slaughter tables, and are generally used to improve the cleanliness and work efficiency of these production facilities. These stoves are designed with aesthetics in mind, and they are one of the necessary facilities for Chinese kitchens. \n\nA facility can link up to two stoves.</SZ_LinkableToolBox.description>

<SZ_Cooler_New.label>Advanced refrigerator</SZ_Cooler_New.label>
<SZ_Cooler_New.description>The advanced refrigerator developed by the improved design of Shenzhou Civilization has a cooling efficiency more than twice that of ordinary machines. Similarly, it consumes less power, but requires more materials to build.</SZ_Cooler_New.description>

<SZ_Heater_New.label>Advanced heater</SZ_Heater_New.label>
<SZ_Heater_New.description>The advanced heater developed by the improved design of Shenzhou Civilization has better heating efficiency and lower power consumption, but it needs to consume more materials during construction.</SZ_Heater_New.description>



<SZ_ShuJia.label>Chinese bookshelf</SZ_ShuJia.label>
<SZ_ShuJia.description>This kind of bookshelf has been commonly used in the ancient Chinese civilization. It usually appears in the study or research sites of Chinese colonists. Its design is beautiful and simple. It can not only be used as interior decoration, but also a very good link facility. \n\nWhen the bookshelf is placed next to the experimental equipment, the research speed of the corresponding facility can be increased. Because it gives a simple and clean appearance in the design, it can also improve the cleanliness of the room.</SZ_ShuJia.description>


<SZ_LongSofa.label>Chinese Academy Sofa</SZ_LongSofa.label>
<SZ_LongSofa.description>Although the ancient Chinese civilization did not have the concept of "sofa", the modern Chinese colonists improved this kind of foreign furniture and developed their own style of sofa, which they turned this kind of sofa into "academy sofa". \n\nThis kind of Chinese sofa is called "shuyuan sofa" because this kind of sofa not only appears in ordinary Shenzhou rooms, but also an indispensable building in their rituals. \n\nThis kind of sofa provides good aesthetics and comfort, but it also requires more materials for construction.</SZ_LongSofa.description>

<ChiTableSA.label>Chinese table (1x1)</ChiTableSA.label>
<ChiTableSA.description>The table made by the Chinese design concept is unique in design, small and exquisite. Traditional Chinese patterns are printed on the center and both sides of the chair. Suitable for any occasion. \n\nAlthough it consumes more materials than an ordinary table of the same size, it provides considerable aesthetics. In addition, because its structure is relatively complex, it requires a lot of effort during construction.</ChiTableSA.description>

<Chi_PenJing.label>Decorative bonsai</Chi_PenJing.label>
<Chi_PenJing.description>This kind of decorative bonsai usually appears in Chinese gardens. Although the plants inside are artificially carved, it still looks lifelike and can provide a good aesthetic bonus. It can also be sold as a commodity at a good price. \n\nThis kind of decorative bonsai has become a more popular ornamental decoration in various colonies after being introduced into the fringe world. It can often add a bright color to the boring colony.</Chi_PenJing.description>

<Chi_JiaShan_A.label>Decorative rockery A</Chi_JiaShan_A.label>
<Chi_JiaShan_A.description>This kind of decorative rockery is commonly found in Chinese gardens. It usually takes a lot of energy to build. It is not so much a "rockery", as it is a garden-style stone sculpture, which can provide a very good beauty bonus. Similarly, it can also be sold as a work of art-although it is very troublesome to carry.</Chi_JiaShan_A.description>

<Chi_JiaShan_B.label>Decorative rockery B</Chi_JiaShan_B.label>
<Chi_JiaShan_B.description>This kind of decorative rockery is commonly found in Chinese gardens. It usually takes a lot of energy to build. It is not so much a "rockery", as it is a garden-style stone sculpture, which can provide a very good beauty bonus. Similarly, it can also be sold as a work of art-although it is very troublesome to carry.</Chi_JiaShan_B.description>

<Chi_DaoCaoRen.label>China Scarecrow</Chi_DaoCaoRen.label>
<Chi_DaoCaoRen.description>Unlike other styles of scarecrows, the Chinese scarecrow wears the Chinese style in the soul of the country. If you look from a distance, it looks like a traditional farmer working in the farmland. Although it can't scare away creatures in the fringe world, it can add a touch to your farm. Bright colors from the ancient east.</Chi_DaoCaoRen.description>

<Chi_GaoShiPai.label>Shenzhou decorative sign</Chi_GaoShiPai.label>
<Chi_GaoShiPai.description>A decorative sign. This sign usually appears in residential areas in Shenzhou, but usually it is pasted on trivial matters of life. Passing Shenzhou colonists usually take a short glance, but they don’t stop. Watch with confidence, so it's usually just an embellishment of these buildings.</Chi_GaoShiPai.description>

<Chi_ShuiJing.label>Shenzhou Well</Chi_ShuiJing.label>
<Chi_ShuiJing.description>Ancient wells in the architectural style of China. This type of ancient well can be seen everywhere in the countryside of ancient China. It retains the function of taking water. Also because of its simple and generous design, although it seems more laborious to build, it also gives people a kind of A good look and feel is one of the indispensable decorations in the beautiful rural landscape. \n\nWhen designing this kind of well, the Chinese colonists also adopted a fire-proof design, even if it requires some wood as a support, it will not cause a fire.</Chi_ShuiJing.description>

<SZ_XiongMaoDiaoSu.label>China - Panda Man sculpture</SZ_XiongMaoDiaoSu.label>
<SZ_XiongMaoDiaoSu.description>No one knows who sculpted this sculpture, and no one has mastered the carving method of this sculpture. It was carved into the image of a pandaman, and the fringe world does not seem to have a race like "pandaman". In addition, there is only Some special mission requests or a very small number of Shenzhou spacecraft will also trade this statue, and traders seem to be unwilling to reveal the origin of this statue. It is engraved with the vaguely "transparent" word, which seems to tell that it is remote and extraordinary. The past...\n\nThis kind of statue can provide a lot of beauty bonus-even though it sells for a very high price.</SZ_XiongMaoDiaoSu.description>

<Chi_XiangLu.label>Shenzhou decorative incense burner</Chi_XiangLu.label>
<Chi_XiangLu.description>The decorative incense burner usually placed on the offering table or the Shenzhou style table can provide an aesthetic bonus, but it is not very beautiful when placed directly on the ground. This kind of incense burner often appears in the ceremonial occasions of the Chinese civilization, and the Chinese colonists usually light it. A few sticks of incense to pray for life well-being. \n\nBut in the turbulent fringe world, who has time to put a few incense sticks to seek the sustenance of the spiritual world?</Chi_XiangLu.description>


<Chi_QiZhi.label>Diversified Symbols and Flags of China</Chi_QiZhi.label>
<Chi_QiZhi.description>These flags usually appear on the city head of the Shenzhou colony. They are not only a decoration representing various cultural symbols, but also a spiritual symbol of the Shenzhou colony. As long as these flags do not fall, China will continue to stretch, broad and profound, and the long-standing culture will never be. Die out.</Chi_QiZhi.description>


<SZ_ZhuangShiShuJia.label>Chinese-style decorative library</SZ_ZhuangShiShuJia.label>
<SZ_ZhuangShiShuJia.description>Unlike those often placed in research rooms or academies, this kind of bookshelf is full of books, and Chinese colonists usually call it "Cangshu Pavilion". Even if it has no other functions, it is suitable as a Chinese-style room. The decorative building can provide a very good beauty bonus. A room full of books will always give a good look.</SZ_ZhuangShiShuJia.description>

<Chi_Gu.label>Shenzhou Royal Drum</Chi_Gu.label>
<Chi_Gu.description>This kind of drum is generally a common decoration in the Shenzhou colony. It is plated with gold and looks very luxurious. It is commonly used in various ceremonial places of the Shenzhou colonists. In addition, the Shenzhou colonists will beat drums on the battlefield to improve morale, but In the fringe world, this kind of drum is usually only used for decoration, it can add a bright color to your colony. \n\nThe Shenzhou Royal Drum can also improve the meditation efficiency of some nearby Shenzhou buildings.</Chi_Gu.description>

<Out_DengLong_Yellow.label>Shenzhou outdoor electric lantern (yellow)</Out_DengLong_Yellow.label>
<Out_DengLong_Yellow.description>The Shenzhou electric lantern, which is usually placed outdoors, adopts the traditional design of Shenzhou, which can provide a good aesthetic bonus on the basis of ensuring practicability. \n\nIn consideration of power saving, the Shenzhou electric lantern will automatically turn off during the day. It adopts the latest rain-proof design and is also coated with a steel fireproof coating. It will not short-circuit in the rain, but compared with other electric lights, it is under construction Time consuming requires more materials, and the skill requirements of the builder are also higher.</Out_DengLong_Yellow.description>

<Out_DengLong_Red.label>Shenzhou outdoor electric lantern (red)</Out_DengLong_Red.label>
<Out_DengLong_Red.description>The Shenzhou electric lantern, which is usually placed outdoors, adopts the traditional design of Shenzhou, which can provide a good aesthetic bonus on the basis of ensuring practicability. \n\nIn consideration of power saving, the Shenzhou electric lantern will automatically turn off during the day. It adopts the latest rain-proof design and is also coated with a steel fireproof coating. It will not short-circuit in the rain, but compared with other electric lights, it is under construction Time consuming requires more materials, and the skill requirements of the builder are also higher.</Out_DengLong_Red.description>

<Out_DengLong_White.label>Shenzhou outdoor electric lantern (white)</Out_DengLong_White.label>
<Out_DengLong_White.description>The Shenzhou electric lantern, which is usually placed outdoors, adopts the traditional design of Shenzhou, which can provide a good aesthetic bonus on the basis of ensuring practicability. \n\nIn consideration of power saving, the Shenzhou electric lantern will automatically turn off during the day. It adopts the latest rain-proof design and is also coated with a steel fireproof coating. It will not short-circuit in the rain, but compared with other electric lights, it is under construction Time consuming requires more materials, and the skill requirements of the builder are also higher.</Out_DengLong_White.description>

<SZ_ZhuangShiWall.label>China retro wall</SZ_ZhuangShiWall.label>
<SZ_ZhuangShiWall.description>The retro wall built with traditional Chinese construction technology needs more materials and time. Because it inherits the traditional reinforcement technology of China, it can reduce explosion damage by half, but its ability to defend against melee weapons is still weak.\n\nThis kind of wall is also engraved with traditional Chinese patterns, giving people a good impression.</SZ_ZhuangShiWall.description>


<SZRug_San.label>Chinese pattern carpet (3x3)</SZRug_San.label>
<SZRug_San.description>Carpets printed with simple Chinese patterns are suitable for laying in any room. It is an indispensable part of interior decoration in China. In addition, this kind of carpet is easy to clean and does not easily adhere to stains, so it can also provide some cleanliness for the room. become. \n\nThe aristocratic palaces of China also have a large number of such carpets. In addition, in some areas of China, carpets made of precious animal leather, such as tiger skins, are considered to be a symbol of dignity.</SZRug_San.description>

<SZRug_Er.label>Chinese pattern carpet (2x2)</SZRug_Er.label>
<SZRug_Er.description>Carpets printed with simple Chinese patterns are suitable for laying in any room. It is an indispensable part of interior decoration in China. In addition, this kind of carpet is easy to clean and does not easily adhere to stains, so it can also provide some cleanliness for the room. become. \n\nThe aristocratic palaces of China also have a large number of such carpets. In addition, in some areas of China, carpets made of precious animal leather, such as tiger skins, are considered to be a symbol of dignity.</SZRug_Er.description>

<SZ_ZhuHuan.label>Crested Ibis</SZ_ZhuHuan.label>
<SZ_ZhuHuan.description>Originally an extremely dangerous species in China, it was introduced into the marginal world under the guidance of the China Bird Protection Association. Although the Crested Ibis population in the marginal world has expanded, it is still a relatively rare species, and its price is much higher than that of ordinary birds \n\n Crested Ibis has also undergone some evolution in the marginal world. On the one hand, it has a larger body, stronger survival ability and low requirements for food. On the other hand, it seems to have a certain intelligence. Some observers pointed out that it will act like a close master. It is also aggressive when provoked \n\n Crested Ibis generally occurs in temperate regions, and a small amount of Crested Ibis is also distributed in cold and tropical regions.</SZ_ZhuHuan.description>

<EggZhuHuanFertilized.label>Crested Ibis (fertilized)</EggZhuHuanFertilized.label>
<EggZhuHuanFertilized.description>The precious Crested Ibis can hatch young if they are taken care of carefully - it is not a good choice to use such expensive fertilized eggs for cooking.</EggZhuHuanFertilized.description>


<SZ_EYu.label>Chinese Alligator</SZ_EYu.label>
<SZ_EYu.description>Animals that were once widely distributed in the temperate zone of China are also distributed in a small amount in the frigid zone and the tropics. Due to the deterioration of their living environment, they were transferred to the fringe world with relatively better natural conditions to reproduce, but its number is still very small. , So its price is still relatively expensive. \n\nThe leather of Chinese alligator is often regarded as a symbol of dignity in Chinese society, so its leather can also be sold at a high price. \nThe Chinese alligator has evolved stronger survival skills in the fringe world. They have less feeding requirements, higher intelligence, and more aggressive when facing danger and preying. However, due to the limitations of the marginal world environment, the spawning and hatching time of Chinese alligators is longer than that of ordinary crocodiles.</SZ_EYu.description>


<Leather_EYu.label>Chinese Alligator skin</Leather_EYu.label>
<Leather_EYu.description>The skin of Chinese alligator is relatively thick, but the heat insulation function is still good. This kind of crocodile skin has high value, good defense performance and cold resistance function, and it is a very good leather material.</Leather_EYu.description>


<EggYangZiFertilized.label>Chinese alligator eggs (fertilized)</EggYangZiFertilized.label>
<EggYangZiFertilized.description>Very precious Chinese alligator eggs, if carefully taken care of, can hatch alligator larvae-using such expensive fertilized eggs for cooking is not a good choice.</EggYangZiFertilized.description>



<SZ_Ding.label>Decorative tripod</SZ_Ding.label>
<SZ_Ding.description>There is an old saying in the ancient Shenzhou: "One word has nine tripods", and this kind of decorative tripod is imitated from the ancient Chinese tripod. On the one hand, its value is highlighted under the unique design. On the other hand, it The appearance and historical characteristics of the building blend together, giving people a sense of antique beauty. \n\nAlthough this kind of tripod can no longer be used for cooking food, it is still a good decoration. Its only disadvantage is that it is very heavy and inconvenient to carry.</SZ_Ding.description>

<SZ_EDGDiaoSu.label>EDG championship trophy sculpture</SZ_EDGDiaoSu.label>
<SZ_EDGDiaoSu.description>The trophy is engraved with the text: "In November 2021, EDG won the League of Legends Global Finals." Similarly, the trophy is also engraved with a picture of unknown significance-a pig riding on a dog's back and traveling around. The events of ancient times have appeared to be particularly remote, but the light of the knight reflected by the sunlight on the trophy is still carved into the hearts of every viewer. \n\nObviously some merchants want to obtain such a sculpture for different purposes, so it can be sold at a very good price. \n\nThe founder of the sculpture style-EDG enthusiastic fan.</SZ_EDGDiaoSu.description>


<SZ_ShuiChi.label>Chinese pool</SZ_ShuiChi.label>
<SZ_ShuiChi.description>A type of pool decoration often found in traditional Chinese gardens, it is also a work of art comparable to grand sculptures. Although it cannot be transported and sold, it is the most popular type of building in Shenzhou decoration. Builders often need to have construction skills comparable to sculptors to create a good garden pond. \nThe rockery in the pool is usually inscribed with texts recording trivial matters in the colony. \n\nIn the fringe world of chaos, it is better to take a break by the pool in your spare time to reap peace and beauty.</SZ_ShuiChi.description>

<SZ_ShiTouGan.label>Lion head tangerine</SZ_ShiTouGan.label>
<SZ_ShiTouGan.description>Harvested from the lion head orange tree, lion head orange is resistant to storage, moderately sweet and sour, and has a good taste. It tastes like a processed snack. Therefore, it is unanimously loved by people in the fringe world. It can be eaten directly as food. It can also be used as a dish material, but people generally like to enjoy a few lion head tangerines as a snack when they are relaxing. \n\nLion head mandarin can also be further processed into preserved fruit or green mandarin tea, which is a very good plant product.</SZ_ShiTouGan.description>

<SZ_Plant_ShiTouGan.label>Lion Head Mandarin Tree</SZ_Plant_ShiTouGan.label>
<SZ_Plant_ShiTouGan.description>This lion head mandarin tree has the same status as the cocoa tree in the world of China. It has a unique appearance and can be harvested repeatedly. The fruit can be eaten directly like chocolate, and it can be further made into more useful green mandarin tea. The lion head mandarin tree is one of the very important economic crops in China. \n\nAfter continuous cultivation by Chinese colonists, the lion head mandarin varieties in the fringe world have a shorter growth cycle and higher value. \n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Development history:&lt;/color>The planting technology of lion head mandarin trees was introduced to the fringe world by Zhongkai Agricultural Technology Company in 5225, and its promotion process did not seem to be very smooth at the beginning , But after many selections and transformations, Zhongkai Agricultural Technology Co., Ltd. has cultivated the lion head mandarin tree suitable for the marginal world environment. The newly cultivated lion head mandarin tree grows faster and produces sweeter fruits. Lion head tangerines have received unanimous praise from the fringe China world, and Zhongkai Agricultural Technology Co., Ltd. has also leapt from an obscure small studio to one of the most successful agricultural development companies in the fringe world by virtue of the success of the lion head tangerines.</SZ_Plant_ShiTouGan.description>

<SZ_Plant_Tea.label>Shenzhou Tea Tree</SZ_Plant_Tea.label>
<SZ_Plant_Tea.description>Although it is called "tea tree", the Chinese tea tree is actually an improved shrub. The Chinese tea tree in the marginal world was originally introduced from the tea tree in the old Shenzhou area. After improvement, it has become an economic crop fully adapted to the marginal world environment. \n\nCompared with traditional tea bushes, this tea tree has a longer growth cycle, but it can be harvested repeatedly. Similarly, it produces a higher amount of tea. However, this tea tree also requires higher soil fertility.</SZ_Plant_Tea.description>

<VBE_RawTea.label>Raw Tea plant</VBE_RawTea.label>
<VBE_RawTea.description>The tea harvested from the tea plant can be used for brewing tea, but it cannot be used as a food raw material. Since the tea planting technology is only controlled by the Shenzhou region, the price of tea is relatively high, so selling the tea directly is also a good choice. \n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Compatibility description:&lt;/color>In order to avoid duplication of items of the same type, if you use Vanilla Brewing Expanded, the relevant data of the tea inside has been inherited by this mod, so this tea is also Can make Vanilla Expanded related items.</VBE_RawTea.description>

<Plant_GeSangHua.label>Galsang flower</Plant_GeSangHua.label>
<Plant_GeSangHua.description>The characteristic plants from the mother country of Shenzhou civilization have become one of the common indoor decorative flowers after being introduced into the fringe world. Similarly, peonies will also be distributed in temperate regions, and will also be distributed in a small amount in the frigid zone, which can tolerate lower temperatures. Provides more aesthetic bonuses. \n\nPeony is a relatively delicate flower. Although its vitality is relatively ordinary, it needs regular maintenance in the flowerpot, but because of its beautiful and dazzling appearance, it is still often cultivated as a decorative flower by the nobles of the fringe world and grows in the wild. The peony cluster is also a beautiful scenery.</Plant_GeSangHua.description>

<SZ_ShuiChi_B.label>Chinese Pool-B</SZ_ShuiChi_B.label>
<SZ_ShuiChi_B.description>A type of pool decoration often found in traditional Chinese gardens, it is also a work of art comparable to grand sculptures. Although it cannot be transported and sold, it is the most popular type of building in Shenzhou decoration. Builders often need to have construction skills comparable to sculptors to create a good garden pond. \nThe rockery in the pool is usually inscribed with texts recording trivial matters in the colony. \n\nIn the fringe world of chaos, it is better to take a break by the pool in your spare time to reap peace and beauty. \n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Remarks:&lt;/color> This style is designed with the kind sponsorship of Zhongkai Agricultural Technology Company. The warm stone around the pool is engraved with the company’s best product-lion head orange.</SZ_ShuiChi_B.description>


<SZ_SanHeTuWall.label>Sanhe Earth Wall</SZ_SanHeTuWall.label>
<SZ_SanHeTuWall.description>The sanhe earthen wall is a mixture of glutinous rice flour and quartz. The sanhe earthen wall is an ancient building wall in China. Although it looks simple and unattractive, it was promoted by the technicians of Shenzhou Zhongkai Agricultural Technology Co., Ltd. After the marginal world, the functionality of the sanhe earthen wall has been greatly improved. First of all, it only requires a mixture of quartz and glutinous rice flour to be constructed without consuming other materials. It is more convenient to build. In addition, after the improvement of the Chinese architects, the sanhe earthen wall Protection has also been greatly improved. \n\nThe triple earth wall has the function of self-healing, and the repair speed is faster. Similarly, it has a higher durability and can offset 70% of the explosion damage and 50% of the damage from other sources (such as bullets). Or melee weapons).</SZ_SanHeTuWall.description>

<SZ_WuYiTea.label>Wu Yi Yan tea</SZ_WuYiTea.label>
<SZ_WuYiTea.description>Wuyi Rock Tea has the fragrance of green tea and the sweetness of black tea. It is the best in Shenzhou Oolong tea. Wuyi Rock was loved by colonists after being spread to the marginal world because of its obvious scent of rock bones. \n\nLike other teas, the colonists can get a unique mood and health bonus after drinking Wuyi Rock Tea. The production of Wuyi Rock Tea is also relatively simple. You only need to brew the tea on a brewing stand or a Chinese stove. Can.</SZ_WuYiTea.description>

<SZ_MaoShiTea.label>Duck dung</SZ_MaoShiTea.label>
<SZ_MaoShiTea.description>Although Duck Dung Fragrant has a "peculiar smell" from its name alone, it is actually a semi-fermented oolong tea, named after it grows on the "Duck Dung Soil" in China. It is made because of its production. Relatively simple, the fragrance of duck shit was spread to the marginal world and received the favor of the populace. \n\nLike other teas, the colonists can get a unique mood and health bonus after drinking Wuyi rock tea. The production of duck feces tea is also relatively simple. It only needs some tea and a little vegetarian food in the brewing station or Chinese stove Just brew on. \n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Tips:&lt;/color>Many tea merchants confuse big black leaf with duck feces incense. In fact, the leaves of duck feces incense are obviously elliptical than black leaves, and the bottom of the leaves are also different, mainly to distinguish Still from the fragrance. The duck feces are fragrant and deep, and the big black leaves are deep and high.</SZ_MaoShiTea.description>

<SZApparel_FangJin.label>Ming square scarf</SZApparel_FangJin.label>
<SZApparel_FangJin.description>In ancient China, this kind of square scarf was mostly worn by literati. According to the "Ming History·Yufu Zhi" record: Ming dynasty students usually wore square flat towels, matching silk, gauze, silk and satin robes of various colors. \n\nAfter the square was spread to the marginal world, it was welcomed by the nobles of the marginal world, because in their eyes, the scholars of the ancient China were similar in status to them. Similarly, the square is a necessary dress for the position in China. \n\nBecause the square scarf is more ingenious in design, it has good heat insulation and cold protection performance. Similarly, the colonists will be full of a sense of responsibility after wearing it, learning skills will be faster, and work will be better fast. \n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Tips:&lt;/color>After using the National Soul mod, this clothing can also be used as cultural clothing and clothing for special positions in China.</SZApparel_FangJin.description>

<SZApparel_LanShan.label>Ming Sweater</SZApparel_LanShan.label>
<SZApparel_LanShan.description>This kind of clothing was very common in ancient China and was usually worn by Chinese scholars. According to the "History of Ming Dynasty·Yufu Zhi", the clothes used for the clothing of the students in the Ming Dynasty were made of jade-colored silk with wide-sleeved soap rims. \n\nBecause it symbolizes a special group of scholars, after spreading to the marginal world, the tuxedo became one of the favorite clothing types of the marginal Chinese nobles. Similarly, the commoners in the Chinese colonies also like to wear such clothes. Show your high taste. \n\nAlthough it looks heavier, the T-shirt has good heat insulation and cold protection performance. Similarly, after the colonists wear it, they will be full of a sense of responsibility, learning skills will be faster, and work will be better fast. \n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Tips:&lt;/color>After using the National Soul mod, this clothing can also be used as cultural clothing and clothing for special positions in China.</SZApparel_LanShan.description>

<SZ_Chan.label>Tussah</SZ_Chan.label>
<SZ_Chan.description>From the appearance only, this is obviously not the original species of tussah silkworm. This tussah silkworm is also called "Zhongkai Tussah". It is the newest silkworm species transformed by Zhongkai Agricultural Technology Company. Experiments have proved that Zhongkai Tussah silkworm can fully adapt to The environment of the marginal world, too, has almost zero sensitivity to poisons. With this advantage, silkworms have become one of the specialty products of the marginal Shenzhou colony. \n\nZhongkai Tussah silkworm generally appears in the temperate zone. It is also sold in many caravans or spacecraft. It has a relatively low IQ and a short lifespan. However, after transformation, it has developed into a herd animal, which can be raised by colonists. Raise it like cattle and sheep, it will also produce precious silkworm cocoons regularly every 8 days like animal hair. \n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Tips:&lt;/color>The tussah silkworm in the fringe world seems to have lost the function of full flight. This may be because it has degraded in some ways-after all, the fringe world rarely can Flying animals, for the current tussah, its wings are more like a tool to help it "walk".</SZ_Chan.description>

<SZ_ChanEgg.label>Tussah eggs (fertilized)</SZ_ChanEgg.label>
<SZ_ChanEgg.description>The fertilized eggs of the tussah silkworm, if all goes well, will be able to hatch young silkworms even though it takes a long time to hatch. Young silkworms can spit out silkworm cocoons to make silk when they reach adulthood. The colonists only need to take good care of the eggs.</SZ_ChanEgg.description>

<CanJian.label>Tussah cocoon</CanJian.label>
<CanJian.description>Unlike ordinary silkworm cocoons, Chinese tussah cocoons are like wool, which can be produced regularly by silkworms. To Chinese colonists, tussah cocoons are as precious as gold and silver because they can be further processed into precious on the textile table. And beautiful silk. \n\nOf course, selling the cocoons directly to merchants is also a good choice.</CanJian.description>

<SZSiChouCloth.label>Zhongkai Silk</SZSiChouCloth.label>
<SZSiChouCloth.description>The special silk developed by the marginal world. This kind of silk inherits the lightness and beauty of ancient Shenzhou silk, but also develops new fire resistance. Silk has always been regarded as one of the symbols of nobility. Similarly, it is also used The main material used to make the clothes of the Chinese nobles. \n\nZhongkai silk can provide a high aesthetic bonus. Because of its thin material, good air permeability, high temperature resistance and fire resistance, but like traditional silk, it has a weak resistance to damage. \n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Development history:&lt;/color>In the beginning, the promotion of traditional silk in the marginal world along the Belt and Road was not smooth, and Fang Zhongkai Agricultural Technology Co., Ltd. in charge discovered it after a large number of on-site inspections. Problem: The properties of traditional silk are not suitable for the climatic environment of the marginal world. Compared with the unique mushroom cloth of the marginal world, its performance is not good. So after a lot of research and transformation, "Zhongkai Silk" was developed and replaced Traditional silk has become a perfect product that fits the special environment of the marginal world. Once promoted, this material has been sought after by marginal aristocrats and has become one of the best-selling specialties of the Shenzhou colony.</SZSiChouCloth.description>
<SZSiChouCloth.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>silk</SZSiChouCloth.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>

<SZ_DianLiKangA.label>Electricity Smart Kang (3x2)</SZ_DianLiKangA.label>
<SZ_DianLiKangA.description>Developed from the traditional Shenzhou Kang, it can not only be used as a multi-person bed, (also has the function of a chair), it can also be used as a large and power-saving heater, although it does not look very beautiful, and the nobles also I don’t like this kind of building. Similarly, this kind of bed cannot be used as a medical bed at all, but this kind of Kang is one of the most common furniture in ordinary Shenzhou households. Especially in winter, a comfortable and warm Kang is comparable to a heating. The device is much more useful. (And this kind of smart Kang will not malfunction like a heater)\n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Tips:&lt;/color>The efficiency of the colonists’ resting on the Kang is a little higher than that of ordinary beds, and the smart Kang can be powered Heating the room like a bonfire, the larger the Kang, the higher the heating efficiency, but the energy consumption will slightly increase. (The intelligent electric kang also has a temperature control function, which can automatically set the room temperature, and the adjustable range is 20~30 degrees)</SZ_DianLiKangA.description>

<SZ_RanLiaoKangA.label>Traditional Kang (3x2)</SZ_RanLiaoKangA.label>
<SZ_RanLiaoKangA.description>The oldest Kang in the Shenzhou area, it is built entirely of stone bricks (with the function of a chair). Compared with the Kang in the ancient Shenzhou, it has no difference, but its fuel efficiency is better. Similarly, hay and chemical fuels are also used. It can be used as a fuel for this kind of Kang, although it does not look very beautiful, and the nobles do not like this monotonous brick furniture, but it is one of the most common furniture in northern China, for residents of Shenzhou, in the cold Lying on a warm Kang in winter is an extremely happy thing. \n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Tips:&lt;/color>The resting efficiency of the colonists on the Kang is higher than that of ordinary beds. As long as the fuel is sufficient, the traditional Kang can heat the room like a bonfire. The bigger the Kang, The higher the heating efficiency, the higher the energy consumption. (The colonists can increase or decrease the firewood to change the heating temperature of the traditional Kang, the temperature can be controlled in the range of 21~26 degrees)</SZ_RanLiaoKangA.description>

<SZ_RanLiaoKangB.label>Traditional Kang (5x2)</SZ_RanLiaoKangB.label>
<SZ_RanLiaoKangB.description>The oldest Kang in the Shenzhou area, it is built entirely of stone bricks (with the function of a chair). Compared with the Kang in the ancient Shenzhou, it has no difference, but its fuel efficiency is better. Similarly, hay and chemical fuels are also used. It can be used as a fuel for this kind of Kang, although it does not look very beautiful, and the nobles do not like this monotonous brick furniture, but it is one of the most common furniture in northern China, for residents of Shenzhou, in the cold Lying on a warm Kang in winter is an extremely happy thing. \n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Tips:&lt;/color>The resting efficiency of the colonists on the Kang is higher than that of ordinary beds. As long as the fuel is sufficient, the traditional Kang can heat the room like a bonfire. The bigger the Kang, The higher the heating efficiency, the higher the energy consumption. (The colonists can increase or decrease the firewood to change the heating temperature of the traditional Kang, the temperature can be controlled in the range of 21~26 degrees)</SZ_RanLiaoKangB.description>

<SZ_DianLiKangB.label>Electricity Smart Kang (5x2)</SZ_DianLiKangB.label>
<SZ_DianLiKangB.description>Developed from the traditional Shenzhou Kang, it can not only be used as a multi-person bed, (also has the function of a chair), it can also be used as a large and power-saving heater, although it does not look very beautiful, and the nobles also I don’t like this kind of building. Similarly, this kind of bed cannot be used as a medical bed at all, but this kind of Kang is one of the most common furniture in ordinary Shenzhou households. Especially in winter, a comfortable and warm Kang is comparable to a heating. The device is much more useful. (And this kind of smart Kang will not malfunction like a heater)\n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Tips:&lt;/color>The efficiency of the colonists’ resting on the Kang is a little higher than that of ordinary beds, and the smart Kang can be powered Heating the room like a bonfire, the larger the Kang, the higher the heating efficiency, but the energy consumption will slightly increase. (The intelligent electric kang also has a temperature control function, which can automatically set the room temperature, and the adjustable range is 20~30 degrees)</SZ_DianLiKangB.description>

<SZ_YuanBaoChair.label>Yuan baodeng</SZ_YuanBaoChair.label>
<SZ_YuanBaoChair.description>From the appearance, this kind of bench is like ingot, giving people a unique freshness. In fact, this kind of ingot bench can not only be used as a comfortable seat, but also a good decoration, it can provide a good Aesthetic bonus, for merchants, a bench of good quality can be sold for a good price. \n\nThe residents of the Chinese colony like to put one or two of these stools at home during the Spring Festival, to pray for the prosperity of wealth and prosperity in the new year.</SZ_YuanBaoChair.description>

<SZ_NianShou.label>Nian beast</SZ_NianShou.label>
<SZ_NianShou.description>&lt;color=#33d733>Note: &lt;/color>The Nian Beast event is currently only periodically refreshed by the original narrator and the Shenzhou series narrator, and the Nian Beast event will appear on the last day of each year. In addition, ranged damage will provoke Nian beasts. (The burning and explosion damage of the Nian Beast will be increased by four times)\n\nThe Nian Beast is a demon-like existence in the traditional Chinese mythology. There is very little information about it. This ferocious monster cannot be tamed. With thick protection, both its fangs and claws can cause huge damage to its prey. \n\nIn the marginal world, almost no one has seen this terrifying beast, and according to some Chinese businessmen, the disadvantage of this monster is that it is afraid of flames and explosions, so using firecrackers or incendiary bombs can effectively restrain live it. \n\nThe corpse of the Nian Beast will be slaughtered to produce the Nian Beast's fangs. These fangs are precious collectibles and can be sold to merchants to make a lot of money. Therefore, there is also a saying in China that "New Year's Eve brings great wealth." into" statement.</SZ_NianShou.description>

<SZWeapon_BaoZhu.label>firecrackers</SZWeapon_BaoZhu.label>
<SZWeapon_BaoZhu.description>Festive supplies from the Shenzhou area. In the traditional Shenzhou area, firecrackers are only used to celebrate the Spring Festival and increase the festive atmosphere. However, in the edge world, firecrackers have developed certain weapon properties. When they explode, they will produce flames and explosion damage. . \n\nFirecrackers only need to be crafted at crafting points or forging tables. For colonies that are still in the Middle Ages or lack weapons, firecrackers are a simplified version of grenade throwers (compared to grenades, its blast radius is Smaller), it is an artifact against Nian beasts. (Because the flames and explosions received by the Nian beast are doubled)</SZWeapon_BaoZhu.description>

<SZ_NianShouJiao.label>Year of the Beast</SZ_NianShouJiao.label>
<SZ_NianShouJiao.description>The horns cut from the Nian beast are very precious treasures and can be sold for a good price. \n\nAt the same time, it can also be used as a weapon. Nian's horns are very sharp and can penetrate certain armor.</SZ_NianShouJiao.description>

<SZ_SandWolf.label>Corsac Fox</SZ_SandWolf.label>
<SZ_SandWolf.description>The fox species native to China was later introduced to the marginal world. Due to the small size of the sand fox, in order to survive, it evolved a higher IQ in the marginal world. Similarly, its claws were sharper. \n\n Corsac Foxs are usually distributed in temperate and frigid regions, and also in small amounts in tropical, semi-arid regions and tundra.</SZ_SandWolf.description>

<SZ_DaoShiDiaoXiang.label>Taoist statue</SZ_DaoShiDiaoXiang.label>
<SZ_DaoShiDiaoXiang.description>&lt;color=#33d733>tips: &lt;/color>Before the Shenzhou Culture dlc expansion, the attributes of Taoist statues were relatively common, but after adding the dlc expansion, the attributes of Taoist statues will be greatly improved, but they will become memes Exclusive building. \n\n The first impression of the Taoist statue is "Tao law is natural". When designing this statue, the designer integrated the humanistic and natural elements of China into it. It is not only an artistic decoration, but also a A creation that can be used as a natural type of meditation. \n\nFor the colonies who are addicted to the culture of cultivating immortals and alchemy, the Taoist statue is a priceless treasure. They regard this statue as a sacred object. Similarly, there are also many buyers in the upper class who are willing to put the Taoist statue in their homes. to show its elegance.</SZ_DaoShiDiaoXiang.description>
</LanguageData>
