<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CODZP_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CallOfDutyZombiesPack_1_4</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.4</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Call of Duty: Zombies Pack has been updated to Version 1.4
|No large changes have been made other than combatibility updates to make sure everything is working smoothly.
On other news! oversized weapons are now defualt within rimworld 1.4 and no extra mods are needed. 
        </content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CODZP_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CallOfDutyZombiesPack_1_4_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.4.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Call of Duty: Zombies Pack has been updated to Version 1.4.1
|With the release of 1.4 and Biotech I have decided to solely focus on 1.4+ of rimworld and discontinued the support of 1.1, 1.2 and 1.3. These versions can still be obtained by Github.

|New:
Divinium or Element 115 is the new hot stuff that needs to be refined to be used. several of the weapons and buildings will now use Divinium as a resource to use.
Divinium can be obtained by meteorites, trading, Quest rewards or Deep drilling!

Mod combatibility:
Random Call of Duty Weapons now include Modern Warfare Weapon Pack
Added Support for Rim-Effect: Core, Drell, N7, Extended Cut and Asari and Reapers
Added Support for Cursed Guns
Added Support for Vanilla Xcom Weapons, Plasma Weapons, Magnetic Weapons, Chosen Weapons and Laser Weapons
No longer supporting Persona Bond Forge.

|Changes: 
Reearches have been reordered for better progression

        </content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CODZP_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CallOfDutyZombiesPack_1_4_5</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.4.5</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Call of Duty: Zombies Pack has been updated to Version 1.4.5
|A minor version update 
|New:
New mote for Pack a Punch Machine.
Mystery Box now opens when in use.
Added Mod settings (if XML Extensions is installed)

|Changes: 
Removed Factions from using Wonder Weapons and Pack a Punch Weapons. 
Crematior, S.D launcher and Disruptor launcher now shoot in a Arch
Pack a punch, Mystery Box and Der Wunderfizz sounds now speedup with gamespeed and can mute when paused
Changed the Amm-O-Matic Icon
Removed Fabrications from T2 Researchs
Made Weapons Sellable
Updated Preview.png again
you can multiselect Divinium Walls
Optimized some Patches
Added new Icons for style Divinium Walls (Red and Green)
Reduce the Explosion radius of most weapons

        </content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>