<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Outdoor Lighting</name>
	<author>Stormknight</author>
	<supportedVersions>
      <li>1.0</li>
      <li>1.1</li>
	  <li>1.2</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>stormknight.outdoorlighting</packageId>
	<description>Introduces a number of options for outdoor lighting.

Your colonists move slower and work slower when they are in the dark, but having a network of standing lamps around the gardens and outside of your base is a drain on power when they are busy working during the day.

Sure, you could flag them all to be turned off and a colonist could do that every morning, switching them back on again every evening, or .... you could have [b]lamps that automatically turn themselves off during the day![/b]

Clean and stackable, as it makes no changes to existing items in the game. All items are found on the furniture tab.

Includes:
- Garden Lanterns - including pumpkin lanterns!
- Garden Lamps - auto power-off during the day, in a variety of colours.
- Solar-powered Garden Lamps - auto power-off during the day, in a variety of colours.
- Lamp Posts / Street Lamps - also auto power-off during the day, in a variety of colours.

Garden Lanterns
There are three garden lanterns available that can be built without any research needed. Functionally, they are the same as a torch, but hold twice as much "fuel" lasting for 40 days without needing to be re-fuelled.
- Standard garden lantern - gives off a slightly yellow light.
- Garden lantern (blue) - the same as the standard lantern, but with slightly different graphics and a blue tint to the light.
- Pumpkin lantern - there are no pumpkins on the rim, so this is carved from wood and reinforced with a bit of steel.

Outdoor Lamps
A variant of the vanilla Standing Lamp..
- Alternative graphics for the lamps.
- Must research [i]Electricity[/i] before it is available to build.
- The outdoor lamps automatically turn off at 07:00 to save power during the day. They automatically turn back on at 17:00.
- Once [i]Colored Lighting[/i] has been researched, they can be built in a variety of colours, including: red, blue, green, purple, and orange.

Outdoor Solar Lamp
Identical to the Outdoor Lamp from this add-on, except:
- Must research [i]Solar Panels[/i] before it is available to build.
- No need to run power to these lamps - they power themselves by absorbing energy during the day! They can also be easily moved when needed.
- Visually different - the small solar panel can be seen by the lamp, making it easy to see which lamps are which.

Lamp Posts / Street Lamps
Taller and more powerful than the standard lamp:
- Larger pool of light, in a variety of colours (requires [i]Colored Lighting[/i] has been researched).
- Provides limited cover in a gun fight.
- Visually different to standards lamps - when placing, circle shows approximate area that will be lit.

Floodlights!
- 6x the power of a regular lamp, covering light in a radius of 15 squares.
</description>
</ModMetaData>