<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Improved Insectoids</name>
	<author>Carnagion</author>
	<packageId>Carnagion.ImprovedInsectoids</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadBefore/>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VFE.Insectoid</li>
		<li>sarg.alphaanimals</li>
		<li>roolo.giddyupbattlemounts</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VAECaves</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<incompatibleWith>
		<li>Carnagion.BreedableInsects</li>
		<li>Carnagion.TameableVFEInsectoids</li>
	</incompatibleWith>
	<description>Ever wanted to have an army of insectoids at your disposal? With Improved Insectoids, not only is that possible, it's also very viable.

	FEATURES

As the mod's name implies, Improved Insectoids makes vanilla insects better by allowing them to sexually reproduce.

This means you will no longer have to risk your tamer's life every time you want an insect pet. You only need a male and a female insect (of the same species, of course), and you'll be able to mass-produce all the insects you want.

Additionally, megaspiders have a small chance to scare away other creatures near them. Affected creatures will try to flee from the map (unless they belong to the player's faction, in which case they will try to hide in a room). This can be configured in the settings menu to not affect the player's faction, or to be disabled entirely.

	MOD SUPPORT

Improved Insectoids activates additional features if the following mods/DLCs are loaded:

	- Ideology
	A new meme called "Insect Primacy" becomes available. Followers believe that insectoids are the ultimate goal of evolution, and therefore place them in very high esteem - they will suffer large mood penalties for killing or slaughtering innocent insectoids or eating their meat. There are multiple other precepts that can be chosen, with issues relating to taming insects, eating insect jelly, and so on. Finally, insects can also be chosen as venerated animals - although this is not recommended.

	- Vanilla Factions Expanded - Insectoids
	All insects from VFE - Insectoids become tameable and gain a fear-inducing ability similar to the megaspiders'. Gigalocusts and megapedes get the ability to reproduce, and their wildness is reduced. Insectoid queens and royal megaspiders cannot reproduce due to having fixed genders, while larvae cannot reproduce due to never reaching adulthood.

	- Vanilla Animals Expanded - Caves
	Giant spiders of all kinds, cave crawlers, and insectoid hulks become tameable, gain the fear-inducing ability, and also become able to reproduce. Ancient and regular giant spiders will produce spidersilk every few days, and reproduce by laying eggs.

	- Alpha Animals
	All creatures with the Insectoid flesh type added by Alpha Animals are counted as insects by the "Insect Primacy" meme and its precepts (if you have Ideology, that is). Certain creatures, such as the black hive insects and the bumbledrone queen and hierophant, get a fear-inducing ability similar to the megaspiders'.

	- Anima Animals - Community Pack
	Anima megaspiders gain the fear ability. Additionally, they become able to reproduce, and their wildness is reduced. If Ideology is active, anima megaspiders are also counted as insects for the various precepts.

	- Save Our Ship 2
	Cosmopillars and stellapedes become able to reproduce and get the fear ability.

Note that the aforementioned mods must be loaded in the correct order. You will get a warning or error from RimWorld or whatever mod manager you use if you load them in the wrong order.

	FAQ

1. Do wild insects reproduce?
A. No. In vanilla, wild animals do not mate. Hostile wild insects will reproduce the usual way, i.e. by making more hives that spawn new insects every now and then. However, if you have the Wild Reproduction mod, they probably will be able to reproduce as well.

2. My colonists hide in their rooms during infestations! Why?
A. This is caused by the fear-instilling ability added to larger insects. This can be disabled for the player faction in Improved Insectoids' settings menu.

3. Is this mod compatible with:
	- Vanilla Factions Expanded - Insectoids?
	A. Yes. Some additional features are activated if it is loaded. See MOD SUPPORT.

	- Vanilla Animals Expanded - Caves?
	A. Yes. Some additional features are activated if it is loaded. See MOD SUPPORT.

	- Alpha Animals?
	A. Yes. Some additional features are activated if it is loaded. See MOD SUPPORT.

	- Anima Animals - Community Pack?
	A. Yes. Some additional features are activated if it is loaded. See MOD SUPPORT.

	- Insects Have Chitin?
	A. Yes.

	- Wild Reproduction?
	A. Yes.

	- Better Infestations?
	A. Yes.

	- Insect Husbandry?
	A. No.

	- InsectUpgrades?
	A. No.

	- Breedable Insects?
	A. No. That mod is outdated, and Improved Insectoids does everything that it does anyway.

	- Tameable Insects for VFE - Insectoids?
	A. No. That mod is outdated, and Improved Insectoids does everything that it does anyway.

	- Any other mod that changes insects/reproduction/taming?
	A. Improved Insectoids uses xpath patching to work. As long as the other mod is also only adding nodes using patches, and not replacing nodes or overwriting defs entirely, it should be fine.

4. Is it safe to add to an ongoing save?
A. Yes, absolutely. Additionally, it is good practice to make a backup of the save file before adding it, just in case something unexpectedly goes wrong.

5. Is it safe to remove from ongoing saves?
A. Yes, unless you are using Ideology. Regardless, it is good practice to make a backup of the save file before removing it, just in case something unexpectedly goes wrong. Note that tamed insects from VFE-Insectoids will become hostile if you remove the mod mid-save.

	CREDITS

Thanks to:
	- Brrainz, for making Harmony.

RimWorld and the Ideology DLC are owned by Tynan Sylvester.

	DOCUMENTATION

Improved Insectoids' source code and files can be found at: https://github.com/Carnagion/ImprovedInsectoids.
	</description>
</ModMetaData>