<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Practical Pemmican</name>
	<author>Evil Tactician</author>
	<packageId>ETRT.PracticalPemmican</packageId>	
	<supportedVersions>
	  <li>1.2</li>
	  <li>1.3</li>
	  <li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>leafzxg.MasterOfCooking</li>
	</loadAfter>	
	<description>A vanilla friendly change to make Pemmican more practical.

Part of:
&lt;size=20&gt;Evil Tactician's RimWorld Tweaks&lt;/size&gt;

Hey guys, we ran out of meals, we're down to the pemmican.
No problem, we've got 160 of it, that will last ages!
Uh, that won't even feed us for a single day!

If like me, you find the vanilla way of presenting Pemmican quantities annoying, then this is the mod for you. A single unit of Pemmican now represents a single serving, allowing you to quickly see how much food you have for your colonists.


&lt;b&gt;What does it do?&lt;/b&gt;
- TL:DR; 1 Pemmican is now equivalent to 16 in Vanilla.
- 1 Pemmican represents a single serving, like meals.
- 100% balanced as per Vanilla nutrition and work amounts.
- Crafting recipes changed to create 1 and 4 Pemmican.
- Vanilla recipes made 16 and 64 respectively.
- Nutrition, Mass and Market Value multiplied by 16.
- Stack Limit changed to 10, in line with meals.

Whilst this sounds like you'd be losing out on storage, the opposite is true. Previously, Pemmican was stored in stacks of 75, which represent 4.69 servings per stack. Now you can stack 10 servings, equivalent to 160 Pemmican previously.

I've tested this thoroughly and it works very well. Basically to the user, Pemmican behaves like meals and you can see exactly how many meals you have available in your storage.

Due to the other changes, the nutrition, market value and mass are exactly balanced as they were in Vanilla.

&lt;b&gt;Why did you make this?&lt;/b&gt;
- Because I could, and because I play Tribal starts almost exclusively. It was bugging me to have to make a mental calculation constantly just to keep track of the amount of meals I have for my pawns.

&lt;b&gt;Can you do the same to Kibble?&lt;/b&gt;
- I could, but I don't think it makes sense. For Kibble, the portions make more sense as different animals require vastly different amounts of nutrition. Therefore, it could potentially be very wasteful to change Kibble in the same way.

&lt;b&gt;Doesn't that kind of apply to Pemmican too?&lt;/b&gt;
- It can indeed happen that an animal ends up eating Pemmican. However, the same applies to 'normal' meals, which is why animals eating the food intended for your colonists is wasteful in the majority of cases regardless of this change or not. Pemmican is intended for colonists and in my view the way it is implemented in vannila makes no sense.

&lt;size=20&gt;Compatibility&lt;/size&gt;
Should be compatible with almost everything.

If you have Stack XXL, OgreStack, Increased Stack or Deep Stack installed, you'll get the Pemmican stack limits of that mod instead.
I prefer using LWM's Deep Storage myself as it's a more balanced way of handling this, plus it makes your base look nicer and more organised.
	</description>
</ModMetaData>