<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Absolutely More Cannons</name>
	<author>Faryzal2020</author>
	<url></url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>Adds a bunch of different turrets in a form of field guns, tank turrets, howitzers, AA guns, and naval gun turrets. They are relatively unbalanced for a vanilla game, so it is very recommended to use this along with other mods that extends the endgame and difficulties!
	\n
	\nChangelog:
	\nUpdate: 28 Jul @ 10:01pm
	\n- Fixed 75mm Jgr 18 crafting recipe yields wrong ammo
	\n
	\nUpdate: 24 Jul @ 2:59pm
	\n- Fixed turret top texture missing after 1.3 patch
	\n
	\nUpdate: 18 Jul @ 10:30am
	\n- Redrawn all ammo textures
	\n- Reduced the cost and power requirement of most naval guns
	\n- Reconfigured HP and accuracy of some turrets
	\n- Replaced Flak 28 with DCA 40 (still bofors gun but with 5 round clip)
	\n- Added new Howitzer: 7.5 cm le.IG 18 (light infantry support gun)
	\n
	\nUpdate: 16 Jun @ 1:07am
	\n- Fix Flak 38 and Bofors M1 doesn't need to be researched to be built.
	\n
	\nUpdate: 11 Jun @ 9:38pm
	\n- Fixed ammo recipe 75x for M247 Turret only giving 10x
	\n
	\nUpdate: 10 Jun @ 1:17pm
	\n- Reduced the cost for all turrets ammo recipe using a new formula.
	\n- Replaced all x1 ammo crafting recipe with x75 (might cause errors at the first time loading a savegame after updating the mod)
	\n
	\nUpdate: 5 Jun @ 1:49am
	\n- Reworked 88mm Pak 41 turret texture
	\n- Resized 75mm Pak 40 tile size to 3x3
	\n
	\nUpdate: 5 Jun @ 12:59am
	\n- Re-adjusted interaction tile position of all turrets
	\n- Reworked the 12.7cm SK C/34 Naval gun texture
	\n- Adjusted some more turret size and tile size of some naval gun turrets
	\n
	\nUpdate: 4 Jun @ 5:25pm
	\n- Fix FCS computer recipe missing
	\n- Adjusted tile size of some naval guns
	\n- Reworked the Twin 12.7cm Type 5 Naval gun texture
	\n
	\nUpdate: 4 Jun @ 4:49pm
	\n- Changed Karl Gerat shell impact sound effect into something more "ear-punching"
	\n- I finally figured out how to change the size of shell sprites that was shot from a turret, i increased the size of Karl Gerat and other large caliber turrets ejected shells.
	</description>
	<packageId>Faryzal2020.AMC</packageId>
</ModMetaData>